<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ArrayOfCelebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>1</ID>
<Name>Taylor Swift</Name>
<Description>Taylor Swift is a multi-Grammy award-winning American singer/songwriter who, in 2010 at the age of 20, became the youngest artist in history to win the Grammy Award for Album of the Year. In 2011 Swift was named Billboard's Woman of the Year. She also has been named the American Music Awards Artist of the Year, as well as the Entertainer of the Year for both the Country Music Association and the Academy of Country Music, among many other accolades. As of this writing, she is also the top-selling digital artist in music history.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>2</ID>
<Name>Aaron Schwartz</Name>
<Description>Aaron Schwartz is a New York native who began his career at an early age. He is known for playing the lead role of Gerald Garner in the 1995 Judd Apatow feature &quot;Heavyweights&quot; and in the cult classic &quot;The Mighty Ducks&quot;. Aaron also played Clem Lanell in eight episodes of &quot;The Adventures of Pete &amp; Pete&quot; and as a guest star in &quot;The Cosby Show.&quot; He had a recurring role as doorman Vanya on The CW&apos;s drama series &quot;Gossip Girl&quot; and its spin-off web series &quot;Chasing Dorota.&quot; Aaron most recently can be seen in the upcoming anticipated Marvel release &quot;Guardians Of The Galaxy Vol. 2&quot; as the role of young J&apos;son</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>3</ID>
<Name>Aaron Tveit</Name>
<Description>Aaron Kyle Tveit born October 21, 1983 is an American actor and singer. He is known for originating the roles of Gabe in Next to Normal and Frank Abagnale Jr. in the stage version of Catch Me If You Can on Broadway. He is also known for his recurring role as Tripp van der Bilt on The CW&apos;s teen drama series Gossip Girl and for his portrayal of Enjolras in the 2012 film adaptation of Les Misérables. Tveit also starred as Mike Warren on the USA Network series Graceland. Tveit recently starred in Grease Live as Danny Zuko.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>4</ID>
<Name>Abby Ross</Name>
<Description>Abby Ross is an actress, known for Seed (2013), Swim (2012) and Once Upon a Time (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>5</ID>
<Name>Aidan Gillen</Name>
<Description>Aidan Gillen was born on April 24, 1968 in Dublin, Ireland as Aidan Murphy. He is known for his work on Game of Thrones (2011), The Wire (2002) and Hei&apos;an qishi: Liming shengqi (2012). He has been married to Olivia O&apos;Flanagan since July 7, 2001. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>6</ID>
<Name>Aidan Turner</Name>
<Description>Aidan Turner was born in Dublin, Ireland in 1983. After graduating from the Gaiety School of Acting in 2004, Aidan appeared in a number of stage productions, many with Ireland&apos;s national theatre, The Abbey. Such productions included The Plough &amp; The Stars, Romeo &amp; Juliet and A Cry from Heaven. In 2008, Turner made the transition to movies and television with a lead role in the film Alarm and a co-starring role in the popular Irish TV drama The Clinic. In 2009, Turner moved to the UK to take on a starring role in BBC&apos;s acclaimed Being Human. Aidan played the spellbinding &quot;Mitchell&quot; for 3 seasons during which time he also starred in BBC&apos;s Desperate Romantics and BBC&apos;s top rated TV movie Hattie. In 2011, famed director Peter Jackson cast Turner in the role of Kili in JRR Tolkien&apos;s The Hobbit. The highly successful movie trilogy filmed for approximately two years in New Zealand during which time Aidan also starred in Cassandra Clare&apos;s The Mortal Instruments.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>7</ID>
<Name>Alan Dale</Name>
<Description>Alan Dale was born on May 6, 1947 in Dunedin, South Island, New Zealand. He is best known for his eight year role as Jim Robinson in the long running Australian soap opera Neighbours (1985), played Caleb in the hit Fox series The O.C. (2003), featured on Lost (2004) and has a long list of recurring roles. These include 24 (2001), NCIS: Naval Criminal Investigative Service (2003), The West Wing (1999), ER (1994) and The X Files (1993). His film credits include The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo (2011), Priest (2011), After the Sunset (2004), Hollywood Homicide (2003) and Star Trek: Nemesis (2002). Alan has extensive theater credits. He played the lead role of King Arthur in &quot;Spamalot&quot; on the West End, London. He has hosted his own radio shows and is a successful voice-over artist in both Australia, the United Kingdom and the United States.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>8</ID>
<Name>Alex Kingston</Name>
<Description>Alex Kingston was born on March 11, 1963 in London, England as Alexandra Elizabeth Kingston. She is an actress, known for ER (1994), Like Crazy (2011) and Doctor Who (2005). She has been married to Jonathan Stamp since July 18, 2015. She was previously married to Florian Haertel and Ralph Fiennes.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>9</ID>
<Name>Alfie Allen</Name>
<Description>Alfie Allen was born on September 12, 1986 in Hammersmith, London, England as Alfie Evan Allen. He is an actor, known for John Wick (2014), Game of Thrones (2011) and Atonement (2007).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>10</ID>
<Name>Alfre Woodard</Name>
<Description>Alfre Woodard was born on November 8, 1952 in Tulsa, Oklahoma, the youngest of three children of Constance, a homemaker, and Marion H. Woodard, an interior designer. She was named by her godmother, who claimed she saw a vision of Alfre&apos;s name written out in gold letters. A former high school cheerleader and track star, she got the acting bug after being persuaded to audition for a school play by a nun at her school. She went on to study acting at Boston University and enjoyed a brief stint on Broadway before moving to Los Angeles, California. She got her first break in Remember My Name (1978) which also starred Jeff Goldblum. She lives in Santa Monica, California with her husband, writer Roderick M. Spencer, and their two adopted children: Mavis and Duncan. She was named one of the Most Beautiful People in America by People Magazine.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>11</ID>
<Name>Alice Callahan</Name>
<Description>Alice Callahan is an actress, known for Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles: Out of the Shadows (2016), Morning Glory (2010) and Good Ol&apos; Boy (2015). She has been married to W. Kyser Thompson since January 9, 2010.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>12</ID>
<Name>Amanda Setton</Name>
<Description>Amanda Setton was born on December 16, 1985 in Great Neck, New York City, New York, USA. She is an actress, known for What Happens in Vegas (2008), Sex and the City (2008) and One Life to Live (1968).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>13</ID>
<Name>Amy Manson</Name>
<Description>Amy Manson was born on September 9, 1985 in Aberdeenshire, Scotland. She is an actress, known for Not Another Happy Ending (2013), Pumpkinhead: Blood Feud (2007) and Two Down (2015).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>14</ID>
<Name>Anastasia Griffith</Name>
<Description>Anastasia trained at the London Academy of Music and Dramatic Art having already completed a degree in History of Art at Bristol University. Born to her Northern Irish mother (once an actress herself) and American father she was brought up along with her six elder brothers in West London where she still remains today.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>15</ID>
<Name>Andrea Bowen</Name>
<Description>Andrea Lauren Bowen began acting at age 6 as &quot;Young Cosette&quot; in the Broadway production of &quot;Les Miserables&quot;. She went on to star in the original Broadway casts of &quot;Jane Eyre&quot; (Adele) and &quot;The Sound of Music&quot; (Marta). Other New York stage credits include the role of &quot;Young Dorothy&quot; in a Lincoln Center Workshop production called &quot;WAS&quot; and Alison in Disney&apos;s new production, &quot;When You Wish&quot;, written and directed by Tina Landau. As a recording artist, she can be heard on Original Cast Recordings of &quot;Jane Eyre&quot; and &quot;The Sound of Music&quot;, the concept CDs of &quot;Night of the Hunter&quot; and &quot;Z the Masked Musical&quot; and on recordings for &quot;Sugar Beats&quot; and &quot;The Broadway Kids&quot;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>16</ID>
<Name>Andrea Parker</Name>
<Description>Parker is a native Californian. She began ballet study at age 6, trained with youth programs around the country and, at age 15, joined the San Francisco Ballet. After three years of touring, she switched to contemporary dance and began studying acting while working as a bartender. Shortly thereafter, she landed her first speaking part on an episode of Married with Children (1987). Parker likes to ride horses, spend time with family and friends and drive hot wheels. She even attended the Motion Picture Stunt Driving Course in San Bernardino, California.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>17</ID>
<Name>Anne Hathaway</Name>
<Description>Anne Jacqueline Hathaway was born in Brooklyn, New York, to Kate McCauley Hathaway, an actress, and Gerald T. Hathaway, a lawyer, both originally from Philadelphia. She is of mostly Irish descent, along with English, German, and French. Her first major role came in the short-lived television series Get Real (1999). She gained widespread recognition for her roles in The Princess Diaries (2001) and its 2004 sequel as a young girl who discovers she is a member of royalty, opposite Julie Andrews and Heather Matarazzo.She also had a notable role in Nicholas Nickleby (2002) opposite Charlie Hunnam and Jamie Bell, and a starring role in Ella Enchanted (2004). A former top-ranking soprano in New York, Hathaway was reportedly a front-runner for the role of &quot;Christine&quot; in the 2004 The Phantom of the Opera (2004). However, due to scheduling conflicts with The Princess Diaries 2: Royal Engagement (2004), she couldn&apos;t take the role, which was later given to newcomer Emmy Rossum.Hathaway soon started to move away from family-friendly films. Following The Princess Diaries 2: Royal Engagement (2004), she appeared topless in the films Havoc (2005) opposite Josh Peck and Brokeback Mountain (2005) opposite Heath Ledger and Jake Gyllenhaal. Her desire to break out of her &quot;Princess Diaries&quot; image parallels that of her one-time co-star, Julie Andrews, who went topless in the film S.O.B. (1981) in order to break away from the image she created from her 1960s musicals. In interviews, Hathaway said that doing family-friendly films didn&apos;t mean she was similar to their characters or mean she objected to appearing nude in other films.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>18</ID>
<Name>Arthur Darvill</Name>
<Description>Thomas Arthur Darvill, known professionally as Arthur Darvill, is an English actor and musician. He is perhaps most recognized as Rory Williams, one of the Eleventh Doctor&apos;s companions in Doctor Who (2005), and as Rev. Paul Coates in Broadchurch (2013). In 2013-2014 he appeared in the lead role in the theatre musical Once in the West End and on Broadway. Darvill&apos;s mother Ellie is an actress and during Arthur&apos;s early childhood she worked with masks, puppets and live acting as a member of Cannon Hill Theatre, which was based at Midlands Arts Centre, and toured Britain and the world. She is also known as the puppeteer and voice behind Why Bird from Playdays. Prior to the birth of his sister, Darvill went on some of the tours, helping with the setting up of the shows. His father Nigel played the Hammond organ for artists including Edwin Starr, Ruby Turner, Fine Young Cannibals and UB40. Darvill attended Bromsgrove School in Worcestershire from 1993 to 2000.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>19</ID>
<Name>Ashley Benson</Name>
<Description>Ashley Victoria Benson was born on December 18, 1989 in Anaheim Hills, California, to Shannon (Harte) and Jeff Benson. She has Irish, English, and German ancestry. She has been dancing competitively since she was 2 with hip hop, jazz, ballet, tap and lyrical. She has been singing since she was about 5 and she hopes to pursue that, along with her acting. Ashley started modeling at the age of 5 for dance catalogs. Ashley was then pursued by The Ford Modeling Agency at the age of 8. She worked steadily in print and is still with the Agency. At the age of 10, she wanted to pursue acting. Ashley went on to do 35 commercials, and then on to theatrical roles. Acting was now Ashley&apos;s passion. Ashley put all her focus into acting, which left little time for modeling and dancing, anymore. Ashley&apos;s most recent role is &quot;Hanna Marin&quot; on ABC Family&apos;s Pretty Little Liars (2010). Ashley also had a cameo in Romeo Miller (aka Lil Romeo) and Solange Knowles&apos;s music video for the song &quot;True Love&quot;. She did a photo shoot with Britney Spears for Vogue Magazine. She is in NLT&apos;s music video, &quot;That Girl&quot;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>20</ID>
<Name>Ashley Madekwe</Name>
<Description>Ashley Madekwe was born on December 6, 1981 in London, England. She is an actress, known for Revenge (2011), Cassandra&apos;s Dream (2007) and Venus (2006). She has been married to Iddo Goldberg since June 17, 2012.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>21</ID>
<Name>Barbara Hershey</Name>
<Description>Barbara Hershey was born Barbara Lynn Herzstein in Hollywood, California, to Melrose (Moore) and Arnold Nathan Herzstein, a horse racing columnist. Her father, born in Manhattan, was from a Jewish family (from Hungary and Russia), and her mother, originally from Arkansas, had English and Scots-Irish ancestry. Hershey was raised in a small bungalow, and had aspirations of being an actress from her earliest memories.The multi-award-winning actress has been in some of Hollywood&apos;s most memorable films. She has been a winner of an Emmy and a Golden Globe for A Killing in a Small Town (1990). She won two consecutive Best Actress awards at the Cannes Film Festival, (which is unprecedented) for Shy People (1987) and A World Apart (1988). She won a Gemini Award for Anne of Green Gables: A New Beginning (2008) for PBS and a Lifetime Achievement Award at the Vienna International Film Festival.Hershey was nominated for an Academy Award for The Portrait of a Lady (1996).She&apos;s worked with some of the world&apos;s great directors, among them - Martin Scorsese, William Wyler, Woody Allen, Jane Campion and Darren Aronofsky.The versatile actress was first discovered by a talent agent while she was attending Hollywood High School. She began working in television, The Monroes (1966), and film, With Six You Get Eggroll (1968), with Doris Day. And with roles in The Baby Maker (1970) and Boxcar Bertha (1972), Hershey quickly advanced to starring roles.The 1980&apos;s catapulted Hershey&apos;s film career, when she starred in The Stunt Man (1980) with &apos;Peter O&apos;Toole&apos;, The Right Stuff (1983), The Natural (1984) with Robert Redford, Hannah and Her Sisters (1986) with Woody Allen, Hoosiers (1986) with Gene Hackman, Tin Men (1987), Shy People (1987), The Last Temptation of Christ (1988), A World Apart (1988) and Beaches (1988) with Bette Midler.Hershey returned to television in 1990 with her highly-lauded performance in A Killing in a Small Town (1990), Paris Trout (1991), Return to Lonesome Dove (1993), the British mini-series, Daniel Deronda (2002) and the last season of Chicago Hope (1994).During the same period, Hershey remained active in features. She was nominated for an Oscar and Golden Globe for The Portrait of a Lady (1996). She also starred in Merchant-Ivory&apos;s A Soldier&apos;s Daughter Never Cries (1998) and the award-winning Australian film, Lantana (2001).Recently, Hershey has recently performed in James Wan&apos;s cult-hit, Insidious (2010) and Darren Aronofsky&apos;s award-winning Black Swan (2010), playing Natalie Portman&apos;s insane mother.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>22</ID>
<Name>Barnaby Edwards</Name>
<Description>Barnaby Edwards is known for his work on Children of Men (2006), Doctor Who (2005) and Doctor Who: The Adventure Games - Blood of the Cybermen (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>23</ID>
<Name>Barry Sloane</Name>
<Description>Born and raised in Liverpool, England. Probably best known for his role as &apos;Aiden Mathis&apos; in the US hit show &apos;Revenge&apos;. His career began in England where he has appeared in numerous TV shows, notably the BAFTA award winning dramas &quot;Pleasureland&quot; and &quot;The Mark of Cain.&quot; Barry appeared as Troy Whitworth in Jez Butterworth&apos;s critically acclaimed new play Jerusalem at The Royal Court Theatre London. The play received a West End transfer in January 2010, after a record breaking sell out run it then transferred once again, this time to Broadway. Sloane made his Broadway debut in &apos;Jerusalem&apos; at the Music Box Theatre in New York in 2011 having previously made his West End debut in Willy Russell&apos;s Blood Brothers in 2005. In 2007, Sloane began playing serial killer Niall Rafferty in Channel 4&apos;s Hollyoaks. He was nominated twice for &apos;Villian of the year&apos; 2008 and 2009 and for &apos;Best Newcomer&apos; at the National Television awards. In 2010 he appeared in the ITV Drama adaptation of PeterRobinsons novel &apos;Aftermath&apos; and later that year played Kieran Callaghan in the BBC serial medical drama &quot;Holby City.&quot;. In 2011 &apos;Variety&apos; announced that Barry landed the role of Chad in Joseph Rueben&apos;s &apos;Penthouse North&apos; starring alongside Michael Keaton and Michelle Monaghan. In early 2012 &apos;Deadline&apos; reported that Barry had landed the male lead in the ABC/20th TV Pilot &apos;Gotham&apos; playing &apos;Boyo&apos;. Barry appeared in the epic movie &apos;Noah&apos; from Darren Aronofsky and in March 2014 it was announced that he would play &apos;Wes Lawrence&apos; in &apos;The Whispers&apos; exec produced by Steven Spielberg.Barry is represented by Jeff Golenberg at Silver Lining Entertainment and Ken Lee at Innovative Artists.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>24</ID>
<Name>Ben Crompton</Name>
<Description>Ben Crompton was born in 1974 in Stockport, Greater Manchester, England. He is known for his work on Before I Go to Sleep (2014), Game of Thrones (2011) and 102 Dalmatians (2000). He has been married to Liv Lorent since 2008. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>25</ID>
<Name>Bernard Cribbins</Name>
<Description>An actor since the age of 14, Bernard Cribbins had become a major star on the London stage by his mid-20s, but it was another ten years before he became a national star by his success in film comedies and with a string of hit records. He appeared in several of the &quot;Carry On&quot; series, and also achieved a great degree of success doing voiceovers for cartoons and TV commercials.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>26</ID>
<Name>Beverley Elliott</Name>
<Description>Beverley Elliott is an actress, known for Unforgiven (1992), Once Upon a Time (2011) and 2012 (2009).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>27</ID>
<Name>Bianca Lawson</Name>
<Description>Bianca Lawson was born on March 20, 1979 in Los Angeles, California, USA as Bianca Jasmine Lawson. She is an actress and producer, known for Save the Last Dance (2001), Saved by the Bell: The New Class (1993) and Dead &amp; Breakfast (2004).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>28</ID>
<Name>Billie Piper</Name>
<Description>Billie Piper studied at the prestigious Sylvia Young Theatre School. She caught the eyes of record producers who were interested in signing a young vocalist when she was the poster girl for the ad campaign of a British pop music magazine, &quot;Smash Hits&quot;. She released her first single, &quot;Because We Want To&quot;, which debuted at #1 at age 15. Her second single, &quot;Girlfriend&quot;, was also a #1 hit. By the time she turned 16, Billie had released 4 singles that all made the top three on the charts. She has been labeled the &quot;Pop Princess&quot; of England, UK.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>29</ID>
<Name>Blake Lively</Name>
<Description>Blake Lively was born Blake Ellender Brown in Tarzana, California, to a show business family. Her mother, Elaine Lively (née McAlpin), is an acting coach and talent manager, and her father, Ernie Lively (born Ernest Wilson Brown, Jr.), is an actor and teacher. Her brother is actor Eric Lively, and her half-siblings are actors Lori Lively, Robyn Lively and Jason Lively. She followed her parents&apos; and siblings&apos; steps. Her first role was Trixie, the Tooth Fairy in the musical movie Sandman (1998), directed by her father. Her big break came along a few years later, though. Blake was up to finish high school when she got the co-starring role of Bridget in The Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants (2005).Blake was so perfect for the role of Bridget that, with no big references or even auditioning, she landed the role. According to her, all she did was walk in and leave a photo of herself. It was clear that she was the Bridget needed. After the film, Blake went back to high school for her senior year to have the life of a regular teenager -- or a very busy regular teenager. She was class president, a cheerleader, and performed with the choir.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>30</ID>
<Name>Brant Daugherty</Name>
<Description>Brant Daugherty was born on August 20, 1985 in Mason, Ohio, USA. He is known for his work on The Starving Games (2013), Pretty Little Liars (2010) and Merry Kissmas (2015).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>31</ID>
<Name>Brenda Strong</Name>
<Description>Brenda Strong was born on March 25, 1960 in Brightwood, Oregon, USA as Brenda Lee Strong. She is an actress and producer, known for Yu luan jiue ching chi (2004), Starship Troopers (1997) and Red Dragon (2002). She has been married to John Farmanesh-Bocca since May 2015. She was previously married to Tom Henri.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>32</ID>
<Name>Brendan Robinson</Name>
<Description>Brendan Robinson born March 1, 1990 in Portland, Oregon, USA is an American actor known for playing Lucas Gottesman, Cold Case(Evan), Miss Behave(Jordan), Review with Forrest MacNeil (Pilot), How I Met Your Mother(Ned), Weeds(Gordon), Bones(Shane)on the ABC Family series Pretty Little Liars. And movies Campus Daze(Robin), The Afterparty(Andy), The River Why(Kernie), Rid of Me(Young Man), The Do-Deca Pentathlon(Young Mark), Feels So Good(Allan).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>33</ID>
<Name>Brian Austin Green</Name>
<Description>Brian Green was born on July 15th 1973 in Van Nuys, California to parents Joyce and George L. Green. He has a brother Keith and sister Lorelei. Brian&apos;s father was a Country &amp; Western artist and used to frequently take him along to gigs and soon got him interested in the world of music. His first full-time television acting job came when he portrayed the role of &quot;Brian Cunningham&quot; on Knots Landing (1979) between 1986 and 1989. He later went on to star as &quot;David Silver&quot; in the long-running teen show Beverly Hills, 90210 (1990). He also appeared in several television movies, such as Her Costly Affair (1996) and Unwed Father (1997) and guest-starred on other shows such as Saved by the Bell: The College Years (1993) and Sabrina, the Teenage Witch (1996). He released an album in 1996 called &quot;One Stop Carnival&quot; and still continues to work on producing music, especially hip-hop, with his production company and in his home studio. More recently, he has had roles as &quot;Luke Bonner&quot; in Resurrection Blvd. (2000) as well as in independent films as &quot;Randy Mecklin&quot; in Purgatory Flats (2003) and &quot;Jack O&apos;Malley&quot; in Southside (2003). He was engaged to his Beverly Hills, 90210 (1990) co-star Vanessa Marcil and the couple have a son named Kassius Lijah Marcil-Green, born on March 30, 2002.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>34</ID>
<Name>Brian Hallisay</Name>
<Description>Brian Hallisay began his career in show business by appearing in The Inside (2005) episode, The Inside: Aidan (2005), playing &quot;Jake Carrington&quot;, with Rachel Nichols and Adam Baldwin. He was next seen as &quot;Dr. George Harmon&quot; on the Lifetime network&apos;s series, Strong Medicine (2000), in the episode, Strong Medicine: Chief Complaints (2005). In 2006, he was given a role in the Kevin Rodney Sullivan-directed TV movie, A.K.A. (2006), a crime drama which also starred John Leguizamo. Hallisay made his feature film debut in the comedy, Bottoms Up (2006), where he portrayed &quot;Hayden Field&quot;, alongside Jason Mewes, David Keith and Paris Hilton. This was followed by a series of television appearances. He was in Jerry Bruckheimer&apos;s Without a Trace (2002) as &quot;Alex Stark&quot;, Meredith Stiehm&apos;s Cold Case (2003) and CSI: NY (2004) opposite Gary Sinise. He was also given a guest spot in the drama series, Bones (2005), which stars Emily Deschanel and David Boreanaz. His next project became Bionic Woman (2007), where he played &quot;Dr. Mark Stevens&quot; for the 2007 episode, Bionic Woman: Faceoff (2007). In 2008, he was given the role of &quot;Ryan Haas&quot; in Medium (2005), an NBC drama series starring Patricia Arquette. Hallisay was then approached to play the role of the wealthy and charming bachelor &quot;Will Davis&quot; in The CW&apos;s Privileged (2008). Will Davis is the potential love interest of the lead character, the smart and endearing &quot;Megan Smith&quot;, played by JoAnna Garcia Swisher. After &quot;Privileged&quot; was canceled, he went on to another television series, The Client List (2012), starring Jennifer Love Hewitt, where he played her ex-husband. In real life, he and Hewitt became engaged in 2013.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>35</ID>
<Name>Bryce Johnson</Name>
<Description>Bryce Johnson was born on April 18, 1977, and raised in Sioux City, Iowa, where he lived with his mother and two brothers. For a short time his family lived in Denver, Colorado, during his high school years, which is where his dream to become an actor came to life. Similar to his character on Popular (1999), Johnson was the captain of the varsity soccer team and co-captain of the school&apos;s golf team. Also, he was elected Class president of both his Junior and Senior classes.Soon after graduating high school in 1995, Bryce packed his belongings into the back of his car and headed for Los Angeles, California. There he trained at the American Academy of Dramatic Arts. He quickly landed a series starring role in The WB pilot Saving Graces (1999), but when that series didn&apos;t make the schedule, he was cast in Popular (1999). He also appeared in five episodes of the MTV comedy Undressed (1999).Currently residing in Hollywood, California, Bryce is making a name for himself on television. After the cancellation of &quot;Popular,&quot; he went on to make a few more projects, such as the independent film Puzzled (2001) and the made-for-television movie. Bryce won Best Supporting actor at the 2008 Glitter Awards for his performance of Freshman Orientation. In My Life (2002). When not working, he enjoys playing all sports, especially golf, beach volleyball, and American football.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>36</ID>
<Name>Camilla Luddington</Name>
<Description>Camilla Luddington was born on 15 December 1983. Luddington&apos;s hometown is Berkshire, England. She has traveled to the U.S. and has lived in Texas, Pennsylvania, New York, and California. She has spent the last 10 years in the United States, gaining a Mid-Atlantic hybrid accent.She was educated at an all-girls school in Ascot, Berkshire. She later attended the American School in England at Thorpe in Surrey. She also lived in suburban Austin, Texas for a year when she was fourteen, and attended Westwood High School.When she was eighteen, she enrolled in Susquehanna University in Pennsylvania. She moved to New York City, studying at New York Film Academy and later moved to Los Angeles.She has since worked mainly in the USA, and appeared in small roles in several high profile TV shows, before rising to prominence as &quot;Catherine Middleton&quot; in the Lifetime TV movie, William &amp; Kate (2011). She went on to appear in Californication (2007) and True Blood (2008). Luddington was a guest star during the ninth season of ABC&apos;s Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005) as &quot;Dr. Jo Wilson&quot;. She was upgraded to series regular for the tenth season. In June 2012, Crystal Dynamics confirmed Luddington would voice &quot;Lara Croft&quot; in the new Tomb Raider (2013) video game reboot. She did both the voice and the motion capture in the course of three years. She is set to appear in The Pact II (2014) in 2014. She is also returning to the role of &quot;Lara Croft&quot; for the latest Tomb Raider Game, Rise of the Tomb Raider (2015).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>37</ID>
<Name>Camille Coduri</Name>
<Description>Camille Coduri was born on April 18, 1965 in Wandsworth, London, England as Camille F. Coduri. She is an actress, known for Doctor Who (2005), King Ralph (1991) and Nuns on the Run (1990). She has been married to Christopher Fulford since April 1992. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>38</ID>
<Name>Carice van Houten</Name>
<Description>Carice Anouk van Houten was born in Leiderdorp (near Leiden) on 5 September 1976. Her parents are Margje Stasse, who is on the board of Dutch educational TV, and writer and broadcaster Theodore van Houten. She is the elder sister of actress and designer Jelka van Houten. Her paternal grandmother was Scottish. When she was five, her father took her to a screening of Abel Gance&apos;s epic Napoléon vu par Abel Gance (1927), which fascinated her. She has demonstrated great interest in cinema since. Carice convincingly demonstrated her acting talents at the Bonifatius Lyceum high school, &quot;Utrecht&quot;, in the early 90s. One of her first parts was the title role in Hugo Claus&apos; play, &quot;Tijl Uilenspiegehel&quot;. She also developed a skill in clarinet playing. In 1995, she was rather uniquely accepted by both the Maastricht and Amsterdam drama academies, and started her TV career (Labyrint, VPRO TV 1997) as a student of the Kleinkunst Academie Amsterdam. There, she was awarded the 1999 Pisuisse Prize, and the 2000 Top Naeff Prize for her theatre work. A day before the Top Naeff Prize, she was awarded the &apos;Gouden Kalf&apos; as best TV actress in Martin Koolhoven&apos;s Suzy Q (1999). In 2001, she starred in AmnesiA (2001), by the same director. In September 2000, she joined the Noord-Nederlands Toneel, starring as a both singing and acting &quot;Polly&quot; in a contemporary staging of the Threepenny Opera to fabulously stunning reviews. Her great talent for dark comedy was demonstrated in a parody on City Lights (1931)&apos; blind girl in the Amsterdam Kleine Komedie. Carice is a great admirer of American silent comedies - particularly Charles Chaplin and Laurel &amp; Hardy - although she can display an equally dramatic talent. In 2001, she made Minoes (2001), in the title role of the cat-woman after Annie M.G. Schmidt. In the 2001-02 season, she won the main role in a theatre production of Schmidt&apos;s musical, &quot;Foxtrot&quot;.Van Houten&apos;s role in Zwartboek (2006) launched her international career. She went on to play in films such as Valkyrie (2008), alongside Tom Cruise, who asked for her to specifically play his wife after seeing her performance in &quot;Zwartboek&quot;. However, after this, her international career was unsuccessful, until she was offered the role of &quot;Melisandre&quot; in the HBO series, Game of Thrones (2011), in 2011.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>39</ID>
<Name>Caroline Lagerfelt</Name>
<Description>Though known to millions as Celia &quot;CeCe&quot; Rhodes on Gossip Girl (2007) and for her extensive film and TV credits, Caroline Lagerfelt has established a distinguished career in international theatre and Broadway. The recipient of Outer Critics Circle and Obie Awards, as well as a Drama Desk nomination, her career began under the auspices of theatrical legends Eva Le Gallienne and Sir Ralph Richardson.She appeared in nine Broadway shows for some of the most celebrated directors of the English-speaking world, among them Sir Peter Hall (&quot;Betrayal,&quot; opposite Raul Julia and Roy Scheider), Sir John Gielgud (&quot;The Constant Wife,&quot; with Ingrid Bergman and a then-unknown Sigourney Weaver), Harold Pinter, Cyril Ritchard, Mike Nichols, Jerry Zaks and Abe Burrows.She has appeared in every major Off-Broadway venue, receiving critical acclaim for &quot;The Prime of Miss Jean Brodie&quot; opposite Cynthia Nixon, &quot;Moonlight&quot; with Jason Robards, Blythe Danner and Liev Schreiber, &quot;Quartermaine&apos;s Terms&quot; with Kelsey Grammer, and for multiple collaborations with Harold Pinter, Simon Gray and Nicolas Kent, among others.In addition, Lagerfelt has played many of the US and UK&apos;s top regional theatres (Kennedy Center, Guthrie, Williamstown, etc.), highlights including: &quot;Night and Day&quot; with Ralph Fiennes, &quot;The Resistible Rise of Arturo Ui&quot; with Paul Giamatti, &quot;Les Liaisons Dangereuses&quot; with Dianne Wiest, &quot;The Physicists&quot; with Brian Bedford, George Grizzard and Len Cariou, and Garland Wright&apos;s &quot;The Misanthrope.&quot; She is perhaps best known for her portrayal of Elizabeth I in multiple productions of &quot;Mary Stuart,&quot; directed by Carey Perloff.In 2010, Lagerfelt starred as Greta Garbo in &apos;Frank McGuinness&apos;&apos; &quot;Greta Garbo Came to Donegal,&quot; voted one of London&apos;s &quot;Top Five Plays of the Year.&quot;、</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>40</ID>
<Name>Caterina Scorsone</Name>
<Description>Caterina Scorsone has been a professional actress since the age of eight, when she was a regular on the daytime children&apos;s program Mr. Dressup (1967) for Canada&apos;s CBC. A veteran of series television, her other series credits include Shock Treatment (2004), Once a Thief (1996) and Power Play (1998), which garnered her a nomination for a Gemini Award, the Canadian equivalent of the Emmy. She starred with Vivica A. Fox in &quot;Missing&quot; (aka 1-800-Missing (2003)) (2003-6). She has also appeared in episodes of The Border (2008) and The Guard (2008). Scorsone&apos;s TV movies include My Horrible Year! (2001), directed by Eric Stoltz; Common Ground (1990); Rated X (2000), directed by Emilio Estevez; The Devil&apos;s Arithmetic (1999); and Rescuers: Stories of Courage: Two Families (1998). Her feature film credits include The Third Miracle (1999) with Ed Harris and Anne Heche; Borderline Normal (2001) and Strike! (2002). Born and raised in Toronto, Canada, Scorsone is the middle child in a family of five siblings that includes two older twin sisters and a younger brother and sister. She got her first taste of acting in the family living room, where her older sister would play director and all the other kids were in the cast. She completed the final credits in her studies toward an Arts and Science BA at the University of Toronto while filming Missing.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>41</ID>
<Name>Catherine Tate</Name>
<Description>Catherine Tate was born on May 12, 1968 in Bloomsbury, London, England as Catherine Ford. She is an actress and writer, known for Doctor Who (2005), Starter for 10 (2006) and The Catherine Tate Show (2004).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>42</ID>
<Name>Chace Crawford</Name>
<Description>Christopher Chace Crawford was born in Lubbock, Texas, the son of Dana (Plott), a teacher, and Chris Wayne Crawford, a dermatologist. He grew up in Plano, Texas, and has a younger sister, Candice Crawford, who studied broadcast journalism and won the Miss Missouri USA title in 2008. Chace played football and golf in high school, and is a talented artist. He graduated from Trinity Christian Academy in 2003. Although he worked as a model in Dallas, he never pursued acting. He moved to Malibu, California, to attend Pepperdine University after high school where he was a member of the Sigma Nu fraternity. He struggled to identify a career path, vacillating between advertising, business and communications majors. Midway through his second year, his mother encouraged him to pursue acting. He credits her for initiating this move. She stated that &quot;it was a practical move,&quot; based on a career aptitude test he had taken in high school, which revealed he was best suited for a career in the performing arts. He was signed by the first talent agent that interviewed him and then committed full-time to acting studies.In 2006, Chace appeared in Lifetime&apos;s television movie Long Lost Son (2006), where he plays the son of Gabrielle Anwar&apos;s character. That same year, he starred alongside Steven Strait, Taylor Kitsch, Sebastian Stan and Toby Hemingway in the horror/thriller movie, The Covenant (2006). The year 2007 was a big break for Chace. He became one of the leads in CW&apos;s drama, Gossip Girl (2007). Among his cast members on the show are Penn Badgley, Leighton Meester &amp; Ed Westwick. In the year 2008, Chace was seen in the movie Loaded (2008), opposite Jesse Metcalfe. He also got involved in the independent movie, The Haunting of Molly Hartley (2008) with Haley Bennett. His other guest appearance includes a stint on the Family Guy (1999) episode Family Guy: The Former Life of Brian (2008). Other than being involved in more acting projects, the year 2008 proved to be an even better year for Chace as he won the Choice TV Breakout Star Male at the Teen Choice Award.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>43</ID>
<Name>Chad Lowe</Name>
<Description>Chad Lowe is an American actor, director, and producer.He was born Charles Davis Lowe II in Dayton, Ohio, to Barbara Lynn (Hepler), a school teacher, and Charles Davis Lowe, a trial lawyer. He is the younger brother of actor Rob Lowe. Chad first appeared opposite Rob in the movie Oxford Blues (1984), in which he played a computer hacker. He quickly followed this up with a starring role in Silence of the Heart (1984) opposite childhood friend and fellow actor Charlie Sheen. Silence of the Heart (1984) is a dark drama about the problems teenagers often face and the subsequent danger of suicide relating to these problems. It was the first film to properly address the subject. The film also features then up-and-coming actors Sherilyn Fenn and Casey Siemaszko.There Must Be a Pony (1986), a drama shot for TV, saw Chad starring alongside Elizabeth Taylor and Robert Wagner. He then co-starred with Donald Sutherland and Mia Sara in the occult horror film Apprentice to Murder (1988). Chad saw the eighties out with the thriller True Blood (1989) with Jeff Fahey, James Tolkan, and Sherilyn Fenn.Next, he and Tommy Lee Jones headlined the long-running Hallmark Hall of Fame (1951) anthology, in the TV Movie segment &apos;April Morning&apos; (1987). The movie is based upon the novel by the late Howard Fast and is set during the American Revolution or American War of Independence (1775-1783).He worked steadily throughout the nineties, acting in both TV and film. In 1990 he starred with David Soul and Edward Herrmann in the TV drama So Proudly We Hail (1990). The witty drama An Inconvenient Woman (1991) followed the next year. Chad then played Charlie Sykes in the oddball fantasy-comedy-horror road movie Highway to Hell (1991).But his role as AIDS victim Jesse McKenna in Life Goes On (1989) (1991-1993) is perhaps his most well-known. He starred with Bill Smitrovich and Patti LuPone. His performance won him an Emmy Award.In 2000 Chad played country and western legend John Denver in Take Me Home: The John Denver Story (2000), a movie based on the musician&apos;s life and book.Chad then starred with Richard Gere and Diane Lane in the ambitious thriller, Unfaithful (2002). He has since clocked up over sixty film and TV roles including recurring roles in ER (1994) and 24 (2001) with Kiefer Sutherland.Chad is married to Kim Painter and they have a daughter, Mabel.He is (2010) starring in the hit TV series Pretty Little Liars (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>44</ID>
<Name>Chandra Wilson</Name>
<Description>Houston, Texas native Chandra Wilson began performing in musicals at the age of five with Theatre Under the Stars. She attended Houston&apos;s High School for the Performing and Visual Arts, and later went on to acquire her BFA in Drama from NYU&apos;s Tisch School of the Arts through which she spent four years at the Lee Strasberg Theatre Institute. Chandra&apos;s first series regular job was on ABC&apos;s Bob Patterson (2001) in the role of Claudia Hopper. She has made numerous other television appearances including guest-starring and recurring roles. She has also appeared in national television commercials for Blockbuster Video, Burger King, Scope, and the United Negro College Fund as well as numerous radio commercials.Aside from film and television, she has several New York stage credits. Her portrayal of Bonna Willis in the production of &quot;The Good Times are Killing Me&quot; by Lynda Barry (both at the Second Stage and Minetta Lane Theatres) won her a Theatre World Award for Outstanding Debut Performance.Some of her other stage credits include &quot;Paper Moon: The Musical&quot; at the Papermill Playhouse, &quot;The Family of Mann&quot; by Theresa Rebeck, &quot;Believing&quot; for the Young Playwright&apos;s Festival and the Broadway production of &quot;On the Town&quot; directed by George C. Wolfe.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>45</ID>
<Name>Charles Dance</Name>
<Description>Charles Dance was born on October 10, 1946 in Redditch, Worcestershire, England as Walter Charles Dance. He is an actor and director, known for The Imitation Game (2014), Alien³ (1992) and Last Action Hero (1993). He was previously married to Joanna Haythorn.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>46</ID>
<Name>Charlie Carver</Name>
<Description>Charlie Carver was born July 31st, 1988 in San Francisco, California. At a young age, he moved up to a small town in the Napa Valley, California&apos;s wine country. It was there, in school, that Charlie had his first exposure to acting. He went on to study acting at ACT San Francisco, the Interlochen Arts Academy, the University of Southern California, and at a private studio, The Imagined Life in Los Angeles.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>47</ID>
<Name>Chris Evans</Name>
<Description>On the advice of friends, he landed an internship at a casting office and befriended a couple of the agents he regularly communicated with - one of whom later took him on as a client. The screen - not the stage - then became his focus; Evans soon began auditioning for feature films and series television. Evans made one of his first appearances on The Fugitive (2000) (CBS, 2000-2001), a remake of the 1960s series and feature film starring Harrison Ford. In the episode &quot;Guilt&quot;, Evans played the son of a small-town sheriff who tries to exact revenge after Dr. Kimble - incognito as a liquor store owner - refuses to sell him and his friends alcohol. After small roles in Cherry Falls (2000) and The Newcomers (2000) - two unknown low-budget features - Evans appeared in Boston Public (2000) (Fox, 2000-2004) as a murder suspect. He then appeared in his first major feature, Not Another Teen Movie (2001), a spoof on teen comedies wherein he played a jock who makes a bet that he can turn an unpopular and unkempt girl (Chyler Leigh) into prom queen.After filming a couple of television pilots he was confident would be successful - Just Married (2003) and Eastwick (2002) - he appeared in another listless teen comedy, The Perfect Score (2004), playing an average, ho-hum student who takes part in a plot to steal the SAT test. Hijinks naturally ensue. Then, Evans broke through to the Big Time, grabbing the lead in the kidnapping thriller, Cellular (2004), a suspenseful B movie with a cheesy gimmick - a random wrong number on his cell phone forces him into a high-stakes race to save an unknown woman&apos;s life. Despite an unassuming performance from Evans and Kim Basinger as the damsel in distress, Cellular (2004) failed to break any box office records or please a wide majority of critics. Evans then prepared himself for super stardom when he signed on to play &quot;Johnny Storm&quot; (a.k.a. The Human Torch)in Fantastic Four (2005), 20th Century Fox&apos;s long-awaited adaptation of the Marvel comic. Although the film was wildly uneven and disappointing, Evans nearly stole the show with his energetic, unfettered performance. In that year itself, Chris was noticed by critics and made it into magazine and Internet countdowns, scoring himself a third position of the hot body countdown from Gay.com and #18 on E! Television&apos;s 2006 101 Sexiest Celebrity Bodies.The year 2007 also proved to be one successful year for Chris, as he had two movies released around the world that same year, starting with the second installment of the Marvel franchise Fantastic Four. Chris received positive reviews for his performance. The Nanny Diaries (2007), where Evans played &quot;Harvard Hottie&quot;, showed his sensitive. The year 2008 saw Chris Evans part of the movie Street Kings (2008), playing the character &quot;Detective Paul Diskant&quot;. Street Kings is a movie about police officers trying to cover up their wrongdoings and audiences got to see a serious side of Chris. In the same year, Chris also worked on the movie The Loss of a Teardrop Diamond (2008).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>48</ID>
<Name>Chris Gauthier</Name>
<Description>Chris Gauthier was born on January 27, 1976 in Luton, Bedfordshire, England. He is an actor and writer, known for Watchmen (2009), Insomnia (2002) and Eureka (2006).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>49</ID>
<Name>Chris Hemsworth</Name>
<Description>Chris Hemsworth was born in Melbourne, Australia, to Leonie (van Os), a teacher of English, and Craig Hemsworth, a social-services counselor. His brothers are actors Liam Hemsworth and Luke Hemsworth. He is of Dutch (from his immigrant maternal grandfather), Irish, English, Scottish, and German ancestry. His uncle, by marriage, was Rod Ansell, the bushman who inspired the film Crocodile Dundee (1986).Chris saw quite a bit of the country in his youth, after his family moved to the Northern Territory before finally settling on Phillip Island, to the south of Melbourne. In 2004, he unsuccessfully auditioned for the role of Robbie Hunter in the Australian soap opera Home and Away (1988) but was recalled for the role of Kim Hyde which he played until 2007. In 2006, he entered the Australian version of Dancing with the Stars (2004) and his popularity in the soap enabled him to hang on until show 7 (Dancing with the Stars: Episode #5.7 (2006) when he became the fifth contestant to be eliminated.His first Hollywood appearance was in Star Trek (2009), but it was his titular role in Thor (2011) which propelled him to prominence worldwide. He reprised the character in the science fiction blockbuster The Avengers (2012).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>50</ID>
<Name>Christa B. Allen</Name>
<Description>Christa B. Allen was born on November 11, 1991 in Wildomar, California, USA as Christa Brittany Allen. She is an actress, known for Revenge (2011), 13 Going on 30 (2004) and Youth in Revolt (2009).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>51</ID>
<Name>Christie Laing</Name>
<Description>Christie Laing was born April 10th, in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada. In love with performing, Christie was trained in both dance and piano at the age of three and began acting at the age of seven. Juggling both school, acting and dancing throughout her youth, Christie landed roles on popular television shows such as Smallville and Supernatural. Christie made her feature film debut in Scary Movie 4, followed by a leading role in Tucker and Dale vs. Evil which premiered at the Sundance Film Festival.Christie is known for her roles as Carly Diggle on the CW series Arrow and as Marian on ABC&apos;s Once Upon A Time.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>52</ID>
<Name>Christopher Eccleston</Name>
<Description>Christopher Eccleston trained at the Central School of Speech and Drama and first came to public attention as Derek Bentley in Let Him Have It (1991). However, it was a regular role in the television series Cracker (1993) that made him a recognizable figure in the United Kingdom. He appeared in the low-budget thriller Shallow Grave (1994), and in the same year, won the part of Nicky Hutchinson in the epic BBC drama serial Our Friends in the North (1996). It was the transmission of the latter series on BBC Two that really made him into a household name in the United Kingdom. In his film career, he has starred as a leading man alongside a number of major actresses, such as Renée Zellweger in A Price Above Rubies (1998), Cate Blanchett in Elizabeth (1998), and Cameron Diaz and Jordana Brewster in The Invisible Circus (2001), and Nicole Kidman in The Others (2001).In addition to his successful film career, he has continued to work in his favourite medium, appearing in some of the most challenging and thought-provoking British television dramas of recent years. These have included Clocking Off (2000) and Flesh and Blood (2002) for the BBC and Hillsborough (1996), the Iago character in a modern adaptation of Shakespeare&apos;s &quot;Othello&quot;, and the religious epic The Second Coming (2003), playing Steve Baxter, the son of God. His stage career, while not as extensive as his screen credits, has nevertheless shown him to be a formidable actor. He has given intense, focused performances in such plays as &quot;Hamlet&quot;, &quot;Electricity&quot; and &quot;Miss Julie&quot;, for which he received excellent reviews.A very highly regarded actor, Eccleston has twice been nominated in the Best Actor category at the BAFTA Television Awards, the British premiere television awards ceremony. His first nomination came in 1997 for &quot;Our Friends in the North&quot;. Although he didn&apos;t win those awards, however, he did triumph in the Best Actor categories at the 1997 Broadcasting Press Guild Awards and the Royal Television Society Awards, winning for &quot;Our Friends in the North&quot;. He won the RTS Best Actor award for a second time in 2003, this time for his performance in &quot;Flesh and Blood&quot;. In 2005, he received the Most Popular Actor award in the National Television Awards for Doctor Who.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>53</ID>
<Name>Chyler Leigh</Name>
<Description>Born in Charlotte, North Carolina and raised in Virginia Beach and Miami Beach, Chyler began her career in front of the camera at age 12 modeling for magazines and catalogues. Her success in print later led to national commercials for Coca Cola and Wendy&apos;s, among others.By age 16, she had already completed several pilots (ABC&apos;s Wilder Days (2000) and the WB&apos;s Saving Graces (1999)) at the onset. Aaron Spelling confirmed the young actress&apos;s talent when he hired her a few years ago as a series regular in the WB series Safe Harbor (1999) after seeing her performance on Saving Graces (1999). She also guest-starred on 7th Heaven (1996) in a powerful three-story arc wherein her character, &quot;Frankie&quot;, a young, inept mother had adversely influenced the family.Leigh made her film debut in the Colombia/Tri-Star hit comedy spoof Not Another Teen Movie (2001), which opened nationwide December, 2001. She originally auditioned for a smaller role, but the producers and directors were so impressed with her performance that they invited her to read for the lead. Leigh was stunned by her good fortune.By January of 2002, Leigh had already landed a series role on the Fox comedy That &apos;80s Show (2002) (from the producers of &quot;That &apos;70s Show&quot;). The mid season comedy series portrayed Leigh as a rebellious teenager on the Fox Network. After the short-lived run, the series was canceled, and Leigh was immediately brought to executive producer David E. Kelley for consideration in his new Fox series Girls Club (2002). Three days later, Leigh was flown for the New York up-fronts where she was introduced as one of the new series leads, &quot;Sarah Mickle&quot;, a young attorney, on Fox&apos;s 2002 Girls Club (2002).After only two episodes of Girls Club (2002) had aired, Leigh received a personal phone call from Kelley informing her of the show&apos;s cancellation and his desire to bring her forward to his already established series The Practice (1997). With only a matter of weeks between shows, Leigh was at work on the set of ABC&apos;s The Practice (1997) as &quot;Claire Wyatt&quot;, a new Series Regular for the 2002-2003 season. In 2004, Leigh was reunited with Fox for their new half hour comedy pilot &quot;Lucky Us&quot;. Chyler landed the starring role of the free-wheeling conservative young architect, &quot;Lucy Reed&quot;. Weeks later, Leigh made a guest starring appearance as &quot;Kate Spangler&quot;, a feisty young ad exec, in Fox&apos;s new drama series North Shore (2004)&quot;.Later in the season, Leigh took a brief break from Fox to shoot a series lead role opposite Billy Campbell in the WB&apos;s drama pilot Rocky Point (2005). The series was centered on a young woman (Leigh) living on Hawaii&apos;s North Shore who takes in her estranged father (Campbell).Most recently, Leigh has been tapped as a series regular on Fox&apos;s 2005 one hour pilot Reunion (2005). Leigh will star as &quot;Carla&quot;, the quirky good girl who we see transform throughout the emotional, dramatic series which follows her and her five closest friends from their high school graduation in 1986 to their 20th reunion. Reunion (2005) from Warner Bros. TV and Class IV Productions was written/created by Jon Harmon Feldman and will be directed by Jon Amiel. The pilot&apos;s executive producers include Stephen Pearlman, Andrew Plotkin and Jon Harmon Feldman.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>54</ID>
<Name>Clark Gregg</Name>
<Description>Clark Gregg was born on April 2, 1962 in Boston, Massachusetts, USA as Robert Clark Gregg. He is an actor and writer, known for The Avengers (2012), Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. (2013) and Iron Man (2008). He has been married to Jennifer Grey since July 21, 2001. They have one child.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>55</ID>
<Name>Cody Christian</Name>
<Description>Cody Allen Christian is an American actor. He is best known for his recurring role as Mike Montgomery in the series &quot;Pretty Little Liars&quot;. His other credits include &quot;Back to You&quot;, &quot;True Blood&quot; and &quot;Grey&apos;s Anatomy&quot;. He also appeared in the 2011 film &quot;Kill the Irishman&quot;. Now he is starring in the series &quot;Teen Wolf&quot;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>56</ID>
<Name>Cody Kasch</Name>
<Description>Cody Kasch was born on August 21, 1987 in Camarillo, California, USA as Cody Reed Kasch. He is an actor, known for Yu luan jiue ching chi (2004), The Last Rescue (2015) and Asylum (2008).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>57</ID>
<Name>Colin O&apos;Donoghue</Name>
<Description>O&apos;Donoghue was born and raised in Drogheda, County Louth, in a Roman Catholic family. He initially attended Dundalk Grammar School, and then The Gaiety School of Acting in Dublin. At age 16, O&apos;Donoghue went to Paris, France, for a month to learn the French language. Colin&apos;s early career was mainly split between theatre and television work in Ireland and the UK. In 2003, Colin won the Irish Film and Television Award for &quot;Best New Talent&quot; for his role as Norman in &quot;Home For Christmas.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>58</ID>
<Name>Conleth Hill</Name>
<Description>Conleth Hill was born on November 24, 1964 in Ballycastle, County Antrim, Northern Ireland. He is an actor and writer, known for Game of Thrones (2011), Whatever Works (2009) and Salmon Fishing in the Yemen (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>59</ID>
<Name>Connor Paolo</Name>
<Description>Connor Paolo was born July 11, 1990 in New York City, New York, to Julia Mendelsohn, a vocal coach and classical pianist, and Colin Paolo, a writer. In 2006, he attended the professional performing arts school featured in the movie Fame. Then he began taking acting classes at the Lee Strasberg Theater Institute and now studies with Peggy Lewis. For several summers beginning in 2005, he has attended Appel Farm Arts and Music Center Summer Arts Camp located in Elmer, New Jersey.Paolo acting career began at the age of nine, with his first TV appearance on the soap opera All My Children. In 2002, he played Zachary Connor, a preteen murderer-rapist in an episode of Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit. His motion picture debut was in 2003 Clint Eastwood&apos;s Oscar-nominated Mystic River, playing Young Sean.In 2004, Paolo got a recurring role in the daytime soap opera One Life To Live as Travis O&apos;Connell. He also appear in the motion picture Alexander as Young Alexander. Paolo in 2006, made a second appearance on Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit, as Teddy Winnock, a disturbed teenager (based on the real case of Justin Berry). His latest motion picture role was Steven McLoughlin in World Trade Center for Oliver Stone in 2006. He has also starred in two other films that are soon to be released in 2007: Warren Hardesty in Snow Angels, directed by David Gordon Green, and Ross Embry in Favorite Son, his first leading role in a movie.Paolo has a background in theatre, and commercials. He appeared on the Broadway stage in the hit musical The Full Monty and off-Broadway in the New York public theater production of Shakespeare&apos;s, Richard III. Paolo also played Bottom in an abridged production of Shakespeare&apos;s Midsummer Night&apos;s Dream.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>60</ID>
<Name>Dan Starkey</Name>
<Description>Dan Starkey is an actor, known for Wizards vs. Aliens (2012), Doctor Who (2005) and Act of Kindness (2015).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>61</ID>
<Name>Dana Delany</Name>
<Description>Dana Welles Delany was born on March 13, 1956, in New York City and raised in Stamford, Connecticut. Dana knew early in life that she wanted to be an actress. Following graduation from Wesleyan University, this tall (5&apos;7&quot;) beauty moved to New York and developed her skills working in daytime television and theater. Dana starred in the Broadway show &quot;A Life&quot; and received critical acclaim in a number of off-Broadway productions as well. Her role in Nicholas Kazan&apos;s controversial &quot;Bloodmoon&quot; in New York led her to Hollywood. Dana acted in a number of TV series, working steadily until she could get her own starring vehicle. That happened in 1988 when Dana became identified with Army nurse Colleen McMurphy in ABC TV&apos;s critically acclaimed series China Beach (1988), the role earning her three Emmy nominations and two Emmy Awards as Best Actress.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>62</ID>
<Name>Daniel Portman</Name>
<Description>Daniel was born in Glasgow on 13 February 1992 and is the son of the actor Ron Donachie. Brought up in Strathbungo, Glasgow, he attended Shawlands Academy, where he was head boy, before gaining an HNC in acting at Reid Kerr Colege, Paisley. Aged sixteen he had his first role in supernatural thriller &apos;Outcast&apos;, starring James Nesbitt and then had an ongoing role in the Scottish soap &apos;River City&apos;. When he was nineteen he was cast as loyal squire Poldrick Payne in the unstoppable &apos;Game of Thrones; series - in which his father also appeared - and to date has managed not to join that series&apos; rather lengthy list of dead.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>63</ID>
<Name>Daniella Baltodano</Name>
<Description>Daniella Baltodano is best known for her character &quot;Celia Solis&quot; on ABC&apos;s hit show &quot;Desperate Housewives&quot; for 4 Seasons, taking it to the shows final 8th Season. She began acting at the age of 4 and continues to pursue her love for acting. She has appeared on the 5th Season of Showtimes &quot;Shameless&quot;, character name &quot;Denise&quot;. Daniella has two younger sisters Alexandria and Isabella who are following in her foot steps.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>64</ID>
<Name>Darcy Rose Byrnes</Name>
<Description>Darcy Rose Byrnes was born on November 4, 1998 in Burbank, Los Angeles, California, USA. She is an actress, known for The Young and the Restless (1973), Sofia the First (2013) and The Legend of Korra (2012).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>65</ID>
<Name>David Anders </Name>
<Description>David Anders was born on March 11, 1981 in Grants Pass, Oregon, USA as David Anders Holt. He is an actor, known for The Revenant (2009), Alias (2001) and iZombie (2015).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>66</ID>
<Name>David Avalon</Name>
<Description>David Avalon was born on December 10, 1958 in Calgary, Alberta, Canada. He is an actor, known for Elf (2003), The Santa Clause (1994) and Ed, Edd, &apos;n&apos; Eddy (1999).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>67</ID>
<Name>David Call</Name>
<Description>David Call is an actor and producer, known for James White (2015), Tiny Furniture (2010) and Did You Hear About the Morgans? (2009).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>68</ID>
<Name>David Tennant</Name>
<Description>David Tennant was born David John McDonald in West Lothian, Scotland, to Essdale Helen (McLeod) and Sandy McDonald, who was a Presbyterian minister. He is of Scottish and Ulster-Scots descent. When he was about 3 or 4 years old, he decided to become an actor, inspired by his love of Doctor Who (1963).He was brought up in Bathgate, West Lothian and Paisley, Renfrewshire, Scotland and was a huge fan of the band The Proclaimers. He attended Paisley Grammar school and while there he wrote about how he wanted to become a professional actor and play the role of the Doctor in Doctor Who (1963).He made his first television appearance (which was also his first professional acting job) when he was 16, after his father sent some photos of him to a casting director at Scottish television. He also attended a youth theatre group at weekends run by the Royal Scottish Academy of Music and Drama (RSAMD - now renamed the Royal Conservatoire of Scotland [RCS]). When he was 16 he auditioned for and won a place at the RSAMD; the youngest student to ever do so, and started as a full time drama student when he was 17.He worked regularly in theatre and TV after leaving drama school, and his first big break came in 1994 when he was cast in a lead role in the Scottish drama Takin&apos; Over the Asylum (1994). He then moved to London where his career thrived. Amongst other things, he spent several years as a member of the Royal Shakespeare Company, and became famous from his lead roles in TV dramas Blackpool (2004) and Casanova (2005).In 2005, his childhood wish came true. David was cast to play the role of the Doctor in Doctor Who (2005) alongside Billie Piper, after Christopher Eccleston decided to leave. Playing the Doctor made him a household name. Since leaving the series in 2010 his career has continued to rise, with lead roles in films, TV series and theatre.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>69</ID>
<Name>Desmond Harrington</Name>
<Description>Desmond Harrington was raised in the Bronx New York. Prior to acting Desmond attended Manhattan college briefly, worked as a laborer, landscaper, a cold caller at a brokerage firm, and finally a bartender in Manhattan, where a co-worker invited him to attend an acting class. Harrington landed his first role in Luc Besson&apos;s The Messenger: The Story of Joan of Arc.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>70</ID>
<Name>Doug Savant</Name>
<Description>Doug Savant was born on June 21, 1964 in Burbank, California, USA as Douglas Peter Savant. He is an actor, known for Yu luan jiue ching chi (2004), Melrose Place (1992) and Godzilla (1998). He has been married to Laura Leighton since May 1998. They have two children. He was previously married to Dawn Dunkin.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>71</ID>
<Name>Dre Davis</Name>
<Description>Dre Davis is an actress, known for Pretty Little Liars (2010), Scavenger Killers (2014) and Emily &amp; Tim (2015).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>72</ID>
<Name>Dreama Walker</Name>
<Description>Dreama Walker was born in Tampa, Florida. She graduated from Henry B. Plant High School in 2004 and, in 2006, made her debut on the screen. In 2012, Walker starred as &quot;June&quot;, a small town girl with great ambition, on the ABC comedy series Don&apos;t Trust the B---- in Apartment 23 (2012), opposite Krysten Ritter and James Van Der Beek. Previously, she appeared on the CBS drama, The Good Wife (2009) (2009-2011) and the CW&apos;s Gossip Girl (2007) (2008-2009). On the big screen, Walker appeared in the films, Goodbye Baby (2007), Sex and the City (2008), Wherever You Are (2008), Gran Torino (2008), The Invention of Lying (2009), Chlorine (2013) and many more. She also guest-starred on Law &amp; Order (1990), Ugly Betty (2006), Royal Pains (2009) and Mercy (2009). She resides in Los Angeles.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>73</ID>
<Name>Drew Van Acker</Name>
<Description>Drew Van Acker was born in Philadelphia, but lived in Medford, New Jersey his entire life. He began acting in high school drama classes, where he also played on his school&apos;s soccer and lacrosse teams. His soccer abilities led him to receive a soccer scholarship to Towson University in Maryland. While attending Towson, Drew took a number of theater courses in order to refocus on acting. He then made the decision to move to New York City, followed by a move to Los Angeles.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>74</ID>
<Name>Dylan Schmid</Name>
<Description>As a toddler Dylan spent hours play-fighting and doing skits with older brother T.J; he is known as the family&apos;s dramatic child who could always make you laugh with his funny expressions and weird movements. Started acting at the age of six, hand picked for 2 short student movies, did a pilot mini series called Gibson Gus, played &quot;Prince of York&quot; in eight summer performances with Victoria Shakespeare Society; later chosen for lead with the Pacific Opera Victoria in Rodelina, played her son Flavio. In 2010 went to L.A. with AIPA (Marg Haynes) did a 2 week intense acting course with Patrick Day, Nora Eckstein at Young Actors Space, and was given rave reviews.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>75</ID>
<Name>Ed Browning</Name>
<Description>Ed Browning is an actor, known for Poldark (2015), Down the Dark Road (2011) and Teachers (2001).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>76</ID>
<Name>Ed Westwick</Name>
<Description>Ed Westwick was born on June 27, 1987 in Stevenage, Hertfordshire, England as Edward Westwick. He is an actor, known for Gossip Girl (2007), Children of Men (2006) and J. Edgar (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>77</ID>
<Name>Eion Bailey</Name>
<Description>Eion is known for his performances in the critically acclaimed HBO miniseries Band of Brothers, and the long-standing television drama ER. Some of his film credits include Fight Club, Almost Famous, Center Stage, and Mindhunters. He also co-starred with Antonio Banderas in the HBO original movie, And Starring Pancho Villa As Himself.He has won, and been nominated for numerous awards, and is the recipient of a Day- time Emmy for his Outstanding Performance in the movie Life of the Party. Most recently he has received critical acclaim as rogue CIA agent Ben Mercer, opposite Piper Perabo in USA&apos;s Covert Affairs.Eion can be seen in ABC&apos;s Once Upon A Time, where he has been introduced as a series regular.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>78</ID>
<Name>Eleanor Tomlinson</Name>
<Description>Eleanor Tomlinson was born on May 19, 1992 in England as Eleanor May Tomlinson. She is an actress, known for Jack the Giant Slayer (2013), The Illusionist (2006) and Alice in Wonderland (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>79</ID>
<Name>Elena Satine</Name>
<Description>Elena Satine was born in Tbilisi, Georgia (former USSR), and raised on the Black Sea coast of the &quot;Russian Riviera&quot; (Sochi). She began her professional career at the tender age of 6 when she appeared on the popular children&apos;s variety show &quot;Utrennaya Zvezda&quot; (&quot;Morning Star&quot;). At age 9, already a winner of numerous international awards, Elena became the youngest performer to headline at &quot;Kinotavr&quot;-International Film Festival. On a spontaneous trip to New York City, the young actress attended an open call for at the Professional Performing Arts School, and got accepted on the spot. After graduating with honors, Elena continued her dramatic studies at the legendary Moscow Art Theater School, founded by Konstantin Stanislavski.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>80</ID>
<Name>Elizabeth Banks</Name>
<Description>Elizabeth Banks was born Elizabeth Mitchell in Pittsfield, a small city in the Berkshires in western Massachusetts near the New York border, on February 10, 1974. She is the daughter of Ann (Wallace), who worked in a bank, and Mark P. Mitchell, a factory worker. Elizabeth describes herself as having been seen as a &quot;goody two-shoes&quot; in her youth who was nominated for the local Harvest Queen.Banks left home to attend college at the University of Pennsylvania--from which she graduated Magna cum Laude--and went on to attend the Advanced Training Program at the prestigious American Conservatory Theater in San Francisco, graduating in 1996. She then moved to New York and worked in the theater, and began getting small roles in films and on television. Seeking more screen work, she moved to Los Angeles and was soon cast in supporting roles. She also had to change her last name, to Banks, in order to avoid confusion with actress Elizabeth Mitchell.Her breakthrough role was as Betty Brant, the secretary of the cantankerous newspaper tycoon in Sam Raimi&apos;s Spider-Man (2002). She followed up this performance with small roles in other movies: Swept Away (2002), Steven Spielberg&apos;s Catch Me If You Can (2002), Seabiscuit (2003) and The 40 Year Old Virgin (2005). In 2003 she won the Exciting New Face Award at the Young Hollywood Awards.The winsome, beautiful Banks projected an exceptionally charming screen presence that drew comparisons to Audrey Hepburn, and Hollywood eventually began to take notice, Banks being cast in the lead in such films as Kevin Smith&apos;s Zack and Miri Make a Porno (2008) and in Oliver Stone&apos;s biopic of George W. Bush, W. (2008), as Laura Bush.In television Banks was a recurring guest star on Scrubs (2001) as Dr. Kim Briggs, the love interest of Zach Braff&apos;s J.D. In 2010 she was cast as Alec Baldwin&apos;s love interest in season four of 30 Rock (2006). Originally scheduled to appear in only four episodes, she was brought back as a recurring character for two more seasons, and earned Emmy nominations for Outstanding Guest Actress in a Comedy Series for two consecutive years.Banks has more recently appeared in such films as Our Idiot Brother (2011), Man on a Ledge (2012), What to Expect When You&apos;re Expecting (2012), People Like Us (2012), and Pitch Perfect (2012). She also won the coveted role as Effie Trinket in The Hunger Games (2012) and The Hunger Games: Catching Fire (2013).Banks married Max Handelman, a sports writer and producer, in 2003. They have two sons, Felix, who was born in March 2011, and Magnus, born in Nov. 2012, both by gestational surrogacy.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>81</ID>
<Name>Elizabeth Hurley</Name>
<Description>Elizabeth Jane Hurley was born in Basingstoke, Hampshire, to Angela Mary (Titt), a teacher, and Roy Leonard Hurley, an army major. Wanting to be a dancer, Hurley went to ballet boarding school at 12, but soon returned home. When it came time to go to college, Hurley won a scholarship to the London Studio Centre which taught courses for dance and theater. Soon, Hurley wore the punk rock look with pink hair and a nose ring, but to get work, she had to change her image to one that was castable. After college, Hurley worked in the theater and made her screen debut in Aria (1987). Roles in Television and a film, Remando al viento (1988), which included a young actor named Hugh Grant, soon followed. European films followed her appearance in the BBC serial Christabel (1988). Her film debut in a Hollywood movie was in the Wesley Snipes action drama Passenger 57 (1992). When Hugh Grant was picked up with Divine Brown, Hurley became headline news. Added to this was the fact that she was the model representing top cosmetics house Estée Lauder, and there was nowhere Hurley could go to get away from the press. In 1994, Hurley and Hugh Grant set up Simian Films in partnership with Castle Rock Entertainment. As Head of Development, Hurley found the script and produced her first film Extreme Measures (1996), which stars Hugh Grant.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>82</ID>
<Name>Elizabeth Lail</Name>
<Description>Elizabeth Lail was born on March 25, 1992 in Williamson County, Texas, USA as Elizabeth Dean Lail. She is an actress, known for Model Airplane (2011), Once Upon a Time (2011) and Without (2014).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>83</ID>
<Name>Elizabeth Mitchell</Name>
<Description>Elizabeth Mitchell was born in Los Angeles in 1970. Shortly after her birth, her parents moved to Dallas, Texas. She was graduated from Booker T. Washington High School for the Performing and Visual Arts located in the Arts District of downtown Dallas. Later, she earned a BFA degree in acting from Stephens College and also studied at the British American Drama Academy. Additionally, she spent six years at the respected Dallas Theatre Center and one year with that theater&apos;s Encore Company. Before her big screen debut, she started her acting career from theaters. Her theatrical stage credits include productions of &quot;As You Like It&quot;, &quot;A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum&quot;, &quot;Measure for Measure&quot;, &quot;Baby&quot; and &quot;Chicago&quot;, among many others.Her breakthrough performance was opposite Angelina Jolie in Michael Cristofer&apos;s acclaimed HBO telefilm Gia (1998) endearing her to audiences and critics, alike. Following with the sci-fi time-travel adventure, Frequency (2000) with Dennis Quaid and Neil LaBute&apos;s highly anticipated Nurse Betty (2000) opposite Renée Zellweger, Elizabeth showed her charismatic acting skills. With numerous credits from theaters, TV series and movies, Elizabeth Mitchell continues to give her best in the acting field.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>84</ID>
<Name>Ella Rae Peck</Name>
<Description>Ella Rae Peck was born on September 8, 1990 in Minneapolis, Minnesota, USA. She is an actress, known for The Call (2013), Young Adult (2011) and Bachelorette (2012).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>85</ID>
<Name>Ellen Pompeo</Name>
<Description>Ellen Kathleen Pompeo was born in Everett, Massachusetts, to Kathleen B. (O&apos;Keefe) and Joseph E. Pompeo, a salesman. She is of Italian (from her paternal grandfather), Irish, and some English, ancestry.Pompeo made her major studio screen debut in Brad Silberling&apos;s Moonlight Mile (2002), starring alongside Susan Sarandon, Dustin Hoffman and Jake Gyllenhaal. She received outstanding reviews for her portrayal of an outspoken young woman carrying a silent burden that&apos;s breaking her heart.Pompeo starred opposite Luke Wilson, Vince Vaughn and Will Ferrell in the wildly successful Old School (2003) and, before that, in Steven Spielberg&apos;s Catch Me If You Can (2002), opposite Leonardo DiCaprio.Pompeo has starred in several independent features, including In the Weeds (2000) and Coming Soon (1999), and Life of the Party (2005). Since 2005, she has played Dr. Meredith Grey on the television series Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>86</ID>
<Name>Elliot Knight</Name>
<Description>Elliot Knight grew up in the second largest city of the UK, Birmingham. In school, he excelled at drama and began winning awards for his talents, including the Three Musketeers Award for Drama Excellence and an additional regional title in the Acting Award from the Birmingham City Council for his leading role performance of Alfred Ill in The Visit. While attending drama school at Manchester Metropolitan University, where he lead as &quot;Macbeth&quot; in a string of local tour performances of the classic Shakespeare play, he won his first professional role as the titular hero in Sky 1&apos;s popular adventure series &quot;Sinbad&quot;, beating out hundreds after an extensive worldwide search. Subsequently, he was lauded by Screen International as one of the much anticipated &quot;Stars of Tomorrow&quot; of 2011. After screen testing for leading roles in many TV pilots, Knight made his US network television debut in 2014 in ABC&apos;s hit series &quot;How To Get Away With Murder&quot; and is quickly being recognised as one of the industry&apos;s most exciting and fresh new talents.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>87</ID>
<Name>Emilia Clarke</Name>
<Description>Emilia Clarke is a British actress. She was born in London and grew up in Berkshire, England. Her father is a theatre sound engineer and her mother is a businesswoman. Her father was working on a theatre production of &quot;Show Boat&quot; and her mother took her along to the performance. This is when, at the age of 3, her passion for drama began. From 2000 to 2005, she attended St. Edward&apos;s School of Oxford, where she appeared in two school plays. She went on to study at the prestigious Drama Centre London, where she took part in 10 plays. During this time Emilia first appeared on television with a guest role in the BBC&apos;s Doctors (2000).In 2010, after graduating from the Drama Centre London, Emilia got her first film role in the TV movie Triassic Attack (2010). Her breakthrough role came in 2011 when she replaced fellow newcomer Tamzin Merchant in Game of Thrones (2011) after the filming of the initial pilot. Emilia won the 2011 EWwy Award for Best Supporting Actress in a Drama for her role.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>88</ID>
<Name>Emilie de Ravin</Name>
<Description>Emilie was born on 27th December 1981, and grew up in Mount Eliza, Victoria, Australia. When she was 15, she was accepted at the highly selective Australian Ballet School in Melbourne. However, after only a year, she dropped out and undertook acting courses.Her first starring role was on the fantasy drama, BeastMaster (1999). When her agent told her of a role in the US, as newcomer Tess in the hit series Roswell (1999), she flew out and auditioned. After landing the role, she was written out of BeastMaster (1999) and started work as &quot;Tess&quot;, an alien. She relocated to California and was on Roswell (1999) before she even owned an apartment.After 2 years on the show, she then made notable guest appearances in CSI: Miami (2002) and The Handler (2003).She stayed in TV, playing the bad girl Chris in Carrie (2002), a movie made for TV. She also changed genres, starring in Santa&apos;s Slay (2005), a black comedy.Emilie has shown her versatility by branching out into film, making her debut at Sundance 2005 with the the award-winning indie film Brick (2005). She starred in the remake The Hills Have Eyes (2006) in 2006, which debuted at No.1 in the UK box office.She was on the Emmy-award winning ABC series Lost (2004), playing &quot;Claire&quot;, a young Australian who gave birth on the mysterious island and has a close relationship with &quot;Charlie&quot;, played by Dominic Monaghan.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>89</ID>
<Name>Emily Alyn Lind</Name>
<Description>Emily Alyn Lind&apos;s body of work would be impressive for any Hollywood actress, but for a rising star at such a young age, it is quite remarkable. It is not surprising though, given her family&apos;s film background. She is the middle daughter of producer and assistant director John Lind, and actress Barbara Alyn Woods, best known for her role as Deb Scott in the long-running CW series, &quot;One Tree Hill.&quot; Emily began her acting career with the role of &apos;Young Lily,&apos; in &quot;The Secret Life of Bees.&quot; At the age of five years old, she played &apos;Young Linda&apos; in Gaspar Noe&apos;s &quot;Enter the Void&quot; and the following year was the red carpet darling when the film premiered at the Cannes Film Festival. In 2009, Emily&apos;s venture into television began when she became a popular face, recurring as &apos;Emily Gardener&apos; on the ABC series &quot;Eastwick&quot; and on the daytime drama &quot;All My Children&quot; as &apos;Emma Lavery.&apos; She continued to be seen on hit television series such as &quot;Medium,&quot; &quot;Criminal Minds,&quot; &quot;Hawaii 5-O,&quot; &quot;Suburgatory,&quot; Lifetime&apos;s &quot;Who is Clark Rockefeller?&quot;, and &quot;Sundays at Tiffany&apos;s.&quot; She is also widely known for the ABC hit series, &quot;Revenge,&quot; playing &apos;Young Amanda Clarke.&apos; In 2011, Emily was given the amazing opportunity to play Shirley Temple in Clint Eastwood&apos;s &quot;J. Edgar,&quot; opposite Leonardo DiCaprio. And in 2012, she had two films premiere; the thriller, &quot;The Haunting in Connecticut 2,&quot; playing the lead role of &apos;Heidi,&apos; and &quot;Won&apos;t Back Down,&quot; playing &apos;Malia Fitzpatrick,&apos; a young girl struggling with dyslexia where she starred opposite Maggie Gyllenhaal. Following, Emily starred in the movie musical &quot;Dear Dumb Diary,&quot; playing the lead role of &apos;Jamie Kelly,&apos; based on the popular children&apos;s book series. Alongside the release of the critically acclaimed film, her soundtrack for the film is currently available on iTunes. One of her favorite projects was Venice Film Festival&apos;s &quot;Jackie and Ryan&quot; (2014), co- starring Katherine Heigl and Ben Barnes, where she was able to once again show off her musical skills. From there, she went straight into production on the Warner Brothers thriller, &quot;Hidden&quot; (2015), where she takes on the challenging role of a young girl surviving underground, co-starring alongside Alexander Skarsgard and Andrea Riseborough. Along with working on the ABC pilot &quot;Code Black&quot; and the comedy/action series for CBS, &quot;Rush Hour&quot;, Emily has just completed production on the New Line horror film, &quot;Lights Out&quot;, playing &apos;Sophie&apos; (a young Maria Bello) and the highly anticipated New Line feature comedy/horror film &quot;The Babysitter&quot; directed by McG and playing the lead love interest, &apos;Melanie&apos;. Not only is Emily a talented young actress, but she feels strongly about giving back. She is passionate about the Make-A-Wish Foundation, an organization that grants the wish of a child diagnosed with a life-threatening medical condition, and has raised thousands of dollars for the charity. Her love for Make-A-Wish began when she played the part of &apos;Vanessa Marks,&apos; a young girl battling cancer, in the movie &quot;November Christmas.&quot; Emily created a &apos;love box&apos; to keep on the set of &quot;November Christmas,&quot; which encouraged people to donate to the charity. Emily raised so much money that she decided that she would create a &apos;love box&apos; for every set she was on. From then on, her love and passion for the foundation only grew.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>90</ID>
<Name>Emily VanCamp</Name>
<Description>Emily VanCamp was born on May 12, 1986 in Port Perry, Ontario, Canada as Emily Irene VanCamp. She is an actress, known for Revenge (2011), Captain America: The Winter Soldier (2014) and Everwood (2002).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>91</ID>
<Name>Emma Caulfield</Name>
<Description>Born and raised in San Diego, Emma Caulfield began studying drama in at the La Jolla Playhouse and the Old Globe Theatre where she won the distinguished honor of &quot;Excellence in Theatre Arts.&quot; She picked up her drama studies once again at The American School in Switzerland (TASIS) in London, all before finishing high school.Emma is an award winning actress known for her starring role as the young and beautiful demon-turned-mortal, &quot;Anya&quot; on the hit series Buffy the Vampire Slayer (1997) starting in 1999. Caulfield&apos;s role originally started out as a guest, demon-of-the-week, appearance in a December 1998 episode. She was called back for a few more guest spots for plot reasons, which is when Joss Whedon, the creator of Buffy, realized her talent. She appeared in most of the episodes the following season, and after that, was promoted to a full time series regular. Caulfield&apos;s humor and levity was a favorite among critics and added a comedic dimension to the show, which made its final bow in May 2003.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>92</ID>
<Name>Eric Dane</Name>
<Description>Eric Dane is an American actor known as &quot;Dr. Mark Sloan&quot; on Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005) and as a co-star in Marley &amp; Me (2008) and Valentine&apos;s Day (2010).He was born on November 9, 1972, in San Francisco, California, the older of two brothers. His father is an architect and interior designer based in San Francisco. His mother, Leah (Cohn), was a homemaker. His ancestry includes English, German, Finnish, Russian Jewish, and Austrian Jewish, and Eric had a Bar Mitzvah ceremony.Young Eric was a good athlete in high school. There, he started amateur stage work by playing &quot;Joe Keller&quot; in Arthur Miller&apos;s &quot;All My Sons&quot;, and realized that this was all he wanted to do.He moved to Los Angeles and made his television debut in 1993 on The Wonder Years (1988). In his early career, he also played bit parts on the TV series Married with Children (1987) (1995), Silk Stalkings (1991) (1996) and Roseanne (1988) (1996). Dane played medical doctors more than once, first appearing as a &quot;Dr. Cooper&quot; in Gideon&apos;s Crossing (2000). From 2003-2004, he has been a recurrent guest star as &quot;Jason Dean&quot; in the hit show Charmed (1998). In 2006, he appeared as handsome &quot;Dr. Mark Sloan&quot;, the plastic surgeon on the show Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005). Dane landed his first leading role on the big screen in the German-made feature, Open Water 2: Adrift (2006).On October 29, 2004, in Las Vegas, Eric Dane married actress Rebecca Gayheart, who was previously engaged to producer/director Brett Ratner, the director of X-Men: The Last Stand (2006). In it, Dane plays the character of &quot;Jamie Madrox&quot;, the Multiple Man. Dane and Gayheart became the parents of a girl on March 3, 2010 in Los Angeles.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>93</ID>
<Name>Eric Keenleyside</Name>
<Description>Born in St. Stephen, New Brunswick, he grew up in London, Ontario, with a year and a half in Brisbane, Australia. He apprenticed at the Stratford Festival after graduating from the University of Windsor. Now living near Vancouver, British Columbia, he and his wife, Peg, became naturalized US citizens after living in Los Angeles and in upstate Washington for many years. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>94</ID>
<Name>Ethan Embry</Name>
<Description>Ethan Embry was born Ethan Philan Randall on June 13, 1978 in Huntington Beach, California, to Karen and Charles Randall. Before he started acting in movies, Ethan appeared in more than 100 TV and Radio commercials. In 1991, at the age of thirteen, he appeared in three films and has continued acting ever since. On average, Ethan released or filmed at least two films per year, which continued up until 1999, when he filmed about five films.Ethan spent most of his childhood in Southern California, growing up with his older brother, Aaron (said to be one of the best musicians in LA), and his little sister, Kessia. In 1998, he bought a home of his own.In the Fall of 1999, Ethan co-starred as Sebastian in the short-lived CBS sitcom Work with Me (1999). Sadly, due to lack of ratings, the show ended after only four episodes. 1999, however, did bring a happy event, Ethan&apos;s then-wife, Amelinda Smith, gave birth to their first child, whom they named Cogeian, after the Latin word &quot;cogeo,&quot; which means &quot;to think over.&quot;In the fall of 2000, Ethan starred as Derek Barnes in FreakyLinks (2000) on Fox. Thirteen episodes were shot, but the series was soon canceled after its debut. Later success include a role as detective Frank Smith on Dick Wolf&apos;s remake of the classic series Dragnet (2003), a part in the recent cult classic Harold &amp; Kumar Go to White Castle (2004), and a guest-starring role on the series Numb3rs (2005).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>95</ID>
<Name>Eva Longoria</Name>
<Description>Eva Longoria was born in Corpus Christi, Texas, to Ella Eva (Mireles) and Enrique Longoria, Jr. The youngest of four sisters who grew up on a ranch near Corpus Christi, Longoria attended Texas A&amp;M University-Kingsville, where she received a Bachelor of Science degree in Kinesiology. After graduating from college, she entered a talent contest that brought her to Los Angeles, where she was spotted and subsequently signed by a theatrical agent. After landing roles on The Bold and the Beautiful (1987), General Hospital (1963) and co-starring on Beverly Hills, 90210 (1990), she auditioned for and won the role of &quot;Isabella&quot; on the popular series, The Young and the Restless (1973). After Y&amp;R, Eva Longoria became well known worldwide thanks to Yu luan jiue ching chi (2004) where she plays adulteress &quot;Gabrielle Solis&quot;. She also has a contract with L&apos;Oreal and has been named one of the most beautiful people. A passionate advocate of education she founded The Eva Longoria Foundation which helps Latinas build better futures for themselves and their families through education and entrepreneurship and earned a Masters in Chicano Studies presenting her thesis on &quot;Success STEMS From Diversity: The Value of Latinas in STEM Careers.&quot; Eva has also contributed writing to publications on the subject of education.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>96</ID>
<Name>Faustino Di Bauda</Name>
<Description>Faustino Di Bauda is an actor, known for Once Upon a Time (2011), Seventh Son (2014) and Monster Trucks (2017).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>97</ID>
<Name>Felicity Huffman</Name>
<Description>Felicity Huffman was born on December 9, 1962 in Bedford, New York, USA as Felicity Kendall Huffman. She is an actress, known for Yu luan jiue ching chi (2004), Transamerica (2005) and Phoebe in Wonderland (2008). She has been married to William H. Macy since September 6, 1997. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>98</ID>
<Name>Freema Agyeman</Name>
<Description>Freema Agyeman was born on March 20, 1979 in London, England as Frema Agyeman. She is an actress, known for Doctor Who (2005), Law &amp; Order: UK (2009) and Old Jack&apos;s Boat (2013).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>99</ID>
<Name>Freya Tingley</Name>
<Description>Freya Tingley was born on March 26, 1994 in Perth, Western Australia, Australia. She is an actress, known for X (2011), The Choking Game (2014) and Hemlock Grove (2013).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>100</ID>
<Name>Gabriel Mann</Name>
<Description>Gabriel Mann was born on May 14, 1972 in Middlebury, Vermont, USA. He is an actor, known for The Bourne Supremacy (2004), The Bourne Identity (2002) and Revenge (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>101</ID>
<Name>Gaius Charles</Name>
<Description>Gaius Charles was born on May 2, 1983 in New York City, New York, USA. He is an actor and director, known for Salt (2010), Friday Night Lights (2006) and The Messenger (2009).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>102</ID>
<Name>Georgina Haig</Name>
<Description>Georgina Haig was born on August 3, 1985 in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia as Georgina Hagg. She is an actress, known for Road Train (2010), The Sapphires (2012) and The Mule (2014). She has been married to Josh Mapleston since 2014.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>103</ID>
<Name>Geraldine James</Name>
<Description>Geraldine James, Officer of the Order of the British Empire (OBE) was born on July 6, 1950 in Maidenhead, Berkshire. She was educated at Downe House, a girls&apos; independent school in Newbury, Berkshire, and later, at Drama Centre London. Geraldine has made several film and television appearances, she was nominated four times a BAFTA TV Award for her performances in Dummy (1979), The Jewel in the Crown (1984), Band of Gold (1995), and The Sins (2000).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>104</ID>
<Name>Ginnifer Goodwin</Name>
<Description>Ginnifer Goodwin was born Jennifer Michelle Goodwin on May 22, 1978, in Memphis, Tennessee, to Linda (Kantor), who worked at FedEx and Apple, and Tim Goodwin, who had a recording studio. Bright and talented, Ginnifer carried her love for theater and acting through her high school years. She graduated from Lausanne Collegiate School in 1996 and spent a year at Hanover before going to Boston University where she received her BFA in Acting. She went on to receive accolades in London, including receiving a Certificate from the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art and trained with the Royal Shakespeare Company. She lived briefly in New York before moving to California, where she lives. She made her television debut on the series Law &amp; Order (1990) but had her first recurring television role on Ed (2000) in 2001. Her first movie role was Maya in the first Comedy Central original movie Porn &apos;n Chicken (2002). She then went on to shine as Connie Baker in the major motion picture hit Mona Lisa Smile (2003).Ginnifer appeared in the movie Walk the Line (2005), where she played Johnny Cash&apos;s first wife. She also worked on the television drama Big Love (2006) with Bill Paxton and Jeanne Tripplehorn.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>105</ID>
<Name>Greg Germann</Name>
<Description>A native of Houston raised on Lookout Mountain outside of Golden, Colorado, Greg Germann was exposed to the performing arts at an early age, particularly through his father, an award-winning children&apos;s playwright and theater professor. As a Theater major at the University of Northern Colorado, a constant stream of plays led him to the gradual realization that acting would be his professional future. Buckling down at UNC, he graduated in two years and moved to New York. He became a member of Circle Repertory Company and Ensemble Studio Theatre, accumulating credits in such off-Broadway and Broadway plays as Steven Sondheim musical &quot;Assassins&quot;, &quot;The Person I Once Was&quot; opposite Holly Hunter, and David Mamet&apos;s &quot;War Games&quot;, among others. He has distinguished himself on the big screen portraying roles in various films. In addition to acting he also devotes himself to writing. His short film, Pete&apos;s Garden (1998), for which he also served as director and star, premiered in competition at the 1998 Sundance Film Festival and went on to air on The Sundance Channel in January 1999. He also wrote &quot;The Observatory&quot; a play performed at New York&apos;s Ensemble Studio Theatre.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>106</ID>
<Name>Gwendoline Christie</Name>
<Description>Gwendoline Christie was born in Worthing, West Sussex, England and trained in dance and gymnastics as a child. She graduated from Drama Centre London with a First Class BA (Hons) in 2005 and her first job was with Declan Donellan in &apos;Great Expectations&apos; at the Royal Shakespeare Company that autumn. She then went on to work in regional theatre, world tours and the West End. Her striking appearance motivated photographer Polly Borland to collaborate with her as the subject of a noted series of photographs.In 2011 Gwendoline was cast in the role of Brienne of Tarth in the successful HBO TV adaptation Game of Thrones (2011). She plays the role of Commander Lyme in the last two Hunger Games movies: The Hunger Games: Mockingjay - Part 1 (2014) and The Hunger Games: Mockingjay - Part 2 (2015). She has also been cast as Captain Phasma in Star Wars: Episode VII - The Force Awakens (2015) and Absolutely Fabulous:The Movie (2016). Gwendoline is the face of the Vivienne Westwood A/W 2015 campaign.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>107</ID>
<Name>Harriet Sansom Harris  </Name>
<Description>Born in Texas, Harriet Sansom Harris got involved in acting as a youngster. At seventeen, Harris was accepted at New York&apos;s famed Juilliard School. Upon graduation, Harris joined The Acting Company, a repertory group formed by the first alumni of John Houseman&apos;s Drama Division of The Juilliard School. She spent three years with the Company before she left to work primarily in regional theater. This led to a successful Broadway and Off-Broadway career. Her life changed after appearing as the sole female in the original cast of &quot;Jeffrey&quot;, Paul Rudnick&apos;s smash Off-Broadway hit about love in the time of AIDS. &quot;Jeffrey&quot; led to guest shots on series television, including Frasier (1993), where she created the memorable role of &quot;Bebe Glazer&quot;, Frasier&apos;s cutthroat, neurotic, chain-smoking agent. She also won raves from critics for her role of &quot;Vivian Buchanan&quot; on CBS&apos;s The 5 Mrs. Buchanans (1994). She now calls New York her home, but frequently travels to California for film and television appearances.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>108</ID>
<Name>Heida Reed</Name>
<Description>Heida Reed was born on May 22, 1988 in Reykjavik, Iceland as Heiða Rún Sigurðardóttir. She is an actress, known for One Day (2011), True Bloodthirst (2012) and Poldark (2015).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>109</ID>
<Name>Helena Bonham Carter</Name>
<Description>Helena Bonham Carter is an actress of great versatility, one of the UK&apos;s finest and most successful.In the late 1990s, Bonham Carter embarked on the next phase of her career, moving from capable actress to compelling star. Audiences and critics had long been enchanted by her delicate beauty, evocative of another time and place. Her late &apos;90s and early and mid 2000s roles included Mick Jackson&apos;s Live from Baghdad (2002), alongside Michael Keaton, receiving a nomination for both an Emmy and a Golden Globe; Paul Greengrass&apos; The Theory of Flight (1998), in which she played a victim of motor neurone disease; Trevor Nunn&apos;s Twelfth Night or What You Will (1996), in which she played Olivia; opposite Woody Allen in his Mighty Aphrodite (1995); Mort Ransen&apos;s Margaret&apos;s Museum (1995); Kenneth Branagh&apos;s Mary Shelley&apos;s Frankenstein (1994); and Franco Zeffirelli&apos;s Hamlet (1990).Other notable credits include her appearance with Steve Martin in Novocaine (2001), Tim Burton&apos;s remake of Planet of the Apes, in which she played an ape, Thaddeus O&apos;Sullivan&apos;s The Heart of Me (2002), opposite Paul Bettany, and Big Fish (2003), her second effort with Tim Burton, in which she appeared as a witch.In between her films, Helena has managed a few television appearances, which include her portrayal of Jacqui Jackson in Magnificent 7 (2005), the tale of a mother struggling to raise seven children - three daughters and four autistic boys; as Anne Boleyn in the two parter biopic of Henry VIII starring Ray Winstone; and as Morgan Le Fey, alongside Sam Neill and Miranda Richardson, in Merlin. Earlier television appearances include Michael Mann&apos;s Miami Vice (1984) as Don Johnson&apos;s junkie fiancée, and as a stripper who wins Rik Mayall&apos;s heart in Dancing Queen (1993). Helena has also appeared on stage, in productions of Trelawney of the Wells, The Barber of Seville, House of Bernarda Alba, The Chalk Garden, and Woman in White.Bonham Carter was nominated for a Golden Globe for the fifth time for her role in partner Tim Burton&apos;s film adaptation of the Stephen Sondheim musical, Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street (2007), for which Burton and co-star Johnny Depp were also nominated. For the role, she was awarded Best Actress at the Evening Standard British Film Awards 2008. Other 2000s work includes playing Mrs Bucket in Tim Burton&apos;s massive hit Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (2005), providing the voices for the aristocratic Lady Campanula Tottington in The Curse of the Were-Rabbit (2005) and for the eponymous dead heroine in Tim Burton&apos;s spooky Corpse Bride (2005), and co-starring in Conversations with Other Women (2005) opposite Aaron Eckhart.Since their meeting while filming Planet of the Apes (2001), Bonham Carter and Tim Burton have made seven movies together. They live in adjoining residences in London, sharing a connecting hallway, and have two children: Billy Ray Burton, 4, and Nell Burton, who was born December 15, 2007. Ironically, a mutual love of Sweeney Todd was part of the initial attraction for the pair. Despite that, Bonham Carter has said in numerous interviews that her audition process for the role of Mrs. Lovett was the most grueling of her career and that, ultimately, it was Sondheim who she had to convince that she was right for the role.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>110</ID>
<Name>Henry Czerny</Name>
<Description>Henry Czerny was born on February 8, 1959 in Toronto, Ontario, Canada. He is an actor, known for Mission: Impossible (1996), Revenge (2011) and The A-Team (2010). He has been married to Claudine Cassidy since 2001. They have one child.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>111</ID>
<Name>Holly Marie Combs</Name>
<Description>Holly moved to New York at the tender age of 7. Already her stunning looks had turned heads, resulting in jobs in print ads and commercials. Soon these experiences lead to a desire to act, a dream shared by Holly&apos;s mother, who herself was only 24. After a few bit parts, Holly landed a leading role as Kimberly in TV drama Picket Fences (1992). This show ran for 4 years, winning Holly critical acclaim and a Young Actors award. After the show ended, Holly starred in more roles in TV movies, enjoying her marriage and career success. This wasn&apos;t to last; in 1997, she divorced husband Bryan Travis Smith and yearned for more challenging roles. Then in 1998, Holly&apos;s good friend Shannen Doherty told her about a new television show based around three sisters who happen to be witches, who save the world from evil. Holly auditioned for the middle sister, won the role and is now known world wide for her portrayal of Piper Halliwell in the WB smash hit show Charmed (1998). Holly now lives in Burbank with her husband and their three sons.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>112</ID>
<Name>Hugo Becker</Name>
<Description>Hugo was born on May 13 1987. Brought up in Metz, France he graduated from both the French Conservatory of Dramatic Art and RADA and in 2010 received the Young Cannes Talent Award. His breakthrough role came in the American comedy series &apos;Gossip Girl&apos; as Prince Louis of Monaco but, being bilingual, has appeared in films and TV on both sides of the Atlantic, including the French cop series &apos;Jo&apos; and the British &apos;Silent Witness&apos;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>113</ID>
<Name>Huw Collins</Name>
<Description>Huw Collins is an actor and composer, known for Pretty Little Liars (2010), Hobby (2012) and Close to Heaven (2013). He has been married to Molly Shaheen since January 4, 2015.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>114</ID>
<Name>Iain Glen</Name>
<Description>Iain Glen is a Scottish actor, he was born on June 24, 1961 in Edinburgh, Scotland. He was educated at the Edinburgh Academy, an independent school for boys (now co-educational), followed by the University of Aberdeen. He graduated from the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art, where he was the winner of the Bancroft Gold Medal. He has appeared onstage as &quot;Macbeth&quot; (Tron Theatre), &quot;Henry V&quot; (Royal Shakespeare Company), starred in &quot;Martin Guerre&quot; and in &quot;The Blue Room&quot; with Nicole Kidman. He also received much acclaim for his role in &quot;Silent Scream&quot;. He and his wife, Susannah Harker (House of Cards (1990), Pride and Prejudice (1995), Ultraviolet (1998)) have a son, Finlay.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>115</ID>
<Name>Ian Harding</Name>
<Description>Ian Harding was born on September 16, 1986 in Heidelberg, Baden-Württemberg, Germany. He is an actor, known for Pretty Little Liars (2010), Love &amp; Other Drugs (2010) and Adventureland (2009).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>116</ID>
<Name>Ian McElhinney</Name>
<Description>Ian McElhinney was born on August 19, 1948 in Belfast, Northern Ireland. He is an actor and director, known for City of Ember (2008), Game of Thrones (2011) and Leap Year (2010). He is married to Marie Jones.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>117</ID>
<Name>Ingrid Torrance</Name>
<Description>Ingrid Torrance; actor, coach, producer, director and author has appeared in numerous movies and television series since 1994. She has also been an acting teacher since 1995 and an on set and off set coach since 1998. Ingrid has worked on such shows as Once Upon A Time, The Killing, Fringe, The Good Wife and Blade: The Series. She has appeared in such films as Double Jeopardy, Act of War, Scooby Doo 2: Monsters Unleashed, The Auburn Hills Breakdown, and Driven to Kill, Ingrid has been nominated for a Leo Award as Best Actress and was featured in Entertainment Weekly as a &quot;Breakout&quot; Actress.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>118</ID>
<Name>Isaac Hempstead Wright</Name>
<Description>Isaac has been acting since he was age 11. Currently, he is still studying at school and balancing acting jobs.Isaac Hempstead-Wright is an English actor. Beginning his professional acting career at the age of eleven, Hempstead-Wright is best known for his role as Bran Stark on the HBO series Game of Thrones, which earned him a Young Artist Award nomination as Best Young Supporting Actor in a TV SeriesHe started acting in commercials, and studied acting at the Kent Youth Theatre in Canterbury, England.He made it his screen debut in the horror film, The Awakening (2011). But, the big break came when he was cast as Bran Stark on Game of Thrones (2011), which earned him two Screen Actors Guild Awards nominations as Oustanding Performance by an Ensemble in Drama Series at the 18th and 20th Screen Actors Guild Awards.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>119</ID>
<Name>Isaiah Washington</Name>
<Description>Isaiah Washington was born on August 3, 1963 in Houston, Texas, USA. He is an actor and producer, known for Romeo Must Die (2000), True Crime (1999) and Ghost Ship (2002). He has been married to Jenisa Marie Washington since February 14, 1999. They have three children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>120</ID>
<Name>Jack Gleeson</Name>
<Description>Jack Gleeson was born on May 20, 1992 in Cork, Ireland. He is an actor, known for Game of Thrones (2011), Batman Begins (2005) and A Shine of Rainbows (2009).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>121</ID>
<Name>Jacob Anderson</Name>
<Description>Jacob Anderson was born on June 18, 1990 in London, England. He is an actor, known for Game of Thrones (2011), Adulthood (2008) and Comedown (2012).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>122</ID>
<Name>Jacqueline King</Name>
<Description>Jacqueline King is an actress, known for Star Trek Into Darkness (2013), Hello Herman (2012) and The Riverside Shuffle (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>123</ID>
<Name>Jakob Davies</Name>
<Description>Jakob Davies began acting in 2009 and was featured in several National and International Commercials. Jakob quickly transitioned to Television and Movies where he has been cast in 24 productions to date. He has been fortunate to portray iconic characters such as &quot;Lex Luther&quot; (Smallville) and the recurring role of &quot;Pinocchio&quot; on ABC&apos;s &quot;Once Upon a Time&quot;. He has worked with Director Jean-Pierre Jeunet (Amelie) in &quot;The Young and Prodigious Spivet&quot;, and co starred with Chloe Grace Moretz in the feature film &quot;If I Stay&quot;. Despite his acting credits, Jakob remains grounded attending public school where he enjoys spending time with his friends. He participates in team sports (Football) and continues to love acting where strives to be his best in each and every project put before him.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>124</ID>
<Name>James Denton</Name>
<Description>The second of three children born to a dentist and his wife in Nashville, Tennessee, Denton grew up in Goodlettsville, Tennessee, attended Goodlettsville High School, briefly played basketball at a junior college, then went on to graduate with honors from the (national champion) University of Tennessee at Knoxville, snagging a degree in advertising as a television/journalism major on the way out the door. Even though his father was involved in community theater, Jamie didn&apos;t jump in until he was 23, during the Tennessee bicentennial in Nashville, Tennessee. His role as &quot;George Gibbs&quot; in a production of &quot;Our Town&quot; turned out to be only the first in a long line of plays that he would do, first in Nashville and then, later, in North Carolina, Chicago and California. Although he spent the next four years selling advertising for two radio stations and then for the CBS affiliate in Nashville, Jamie&apos;s heart was already in another place and, after a short stint in North Carolina, he headed to Chicago to try his hand at acting full-time. In Chicago, his first role was as &quot;Stanley&quot; in &quot;A Streetcar Named Desire&quot; and his last was as the terrorist &quot;Bebert&quot; in the French farce &quot;Lapin Lapin&quot;. In the years that came between the two, JD was a company member at The Griffin Theater and at Strawdog Theater Ensemble. He added a steady string of roles and accolades to his quickly growing list of achievements, including one of the leads in the world premiere of &quot;Flesh and Blood&quot;, performing in and composing the music for &quot;the Night Hank Williams Died&quot;, and his portrayal of Kentucky preacher &quot;C.C. Showers&quot; in &quot;The Diviners&quot; - which gained him a much coveted nomination for a Best Actor Joseph Jefferson Award (Chicago&apos;s only theater award). A small part in The Untouchables (1993) (the series, not the movie), JAG (1995), Sliders (1995) and Dark Skies (1996). A spot on Moloney (1996), a pilot for ABC called &quot;L.A. Med&quot; and a stint on the silver screen in That Old Feeling (1997), were preludes to his first appearance as &quot;Mr. Lyle&quot; on The Pretender (1996). Immediately afterward, JD made another pilot, this time for his own series, &quot;The Hanleys&quot;. When ABC shelved the sitcom at the last minute, Denton continued producing chilling portrayals as &quot;Mr. Lyle&quot; on NBC&apos;s The Pretender (1996), as a series regular. Summer of 1999 found Jamie heading back to the theater, starring in the world premiere of the play, &quot;In Walked Monk&quot;. During the 4th season of The Pretender (1996), Jamie added three more guest-starring roles to his credits - the first on Two Guys, a Girl and a Pizza Place (1998), another on Ally McBeal (1997) and the last on the hugely popular The West Wing (1999). That summer, he co-starred in &quot;Asylum&quot;, at The Court Theatre and, at the end of the year, headed for Canada to film two MOWs for TNT - The Pretender 2001 (2001) and The Pretender: Island of the Haunted (2001). 2001 found Jamie back at ABC after Steven Bochco cast him as &quot;Judge Augustus &quot;Jack&quot; Ripley&quot;, in his struggling new series, Philly (2001). Viewers liked &quot;Judge Ripley&quot; and hopes were high that the sizzling on-screen chemistry between Jamie&apos;s character and the one portrayed by Kim Delaney would convince ABC to give the show another season to improve its ratings. Ironically, Jamie was in Australia, promoting Philly (2001), when he received word that ABC had passed on renewing the show for a second season. Jamie ended 2002 with a two-part guest-starring role on The Drew Carey Show (1995). Jamie returned as a guest star on JAG (1995) in 2003, and pilot season landed him the opportunity to once again head up the cast of an ABC series in Threat Matrix (2003), a Touchstone production offering up fictionalized events relating to terrorist activity around the world. Jamie played &quot;John Kilmer&quot;, the man who lead the ultra-covert team of anti-terrorist specialists and who answered solely to the President of the United States. The timely and serious role also gave Jamie the opportunity to change his professional billing from &quot;Jamie Denton&quot; to &quot;James Denton&quot;. Only days before the annual up-fronts in New York, where the major networks announce their new fall season line-ups, ABC picked up the show for September, 2003. Although Threat Matrix (2003) held its own in one of the worst time-slots of the season (sandwiched between the hugely popular &quot;Survivor&quot; and the last season of Friends (1994)), ABC nonetheless pulled the series after only fourteen episodes aired (sixteen episodes were filmed). Threat Matrix (2003) was officially canceled on the same day as Jamie&apos;s role as &quot;Mike Delfino&quot; on Desperate Housewives (2004), a new ABC series scheduled for the Fall, was announced at the 2004 up-fronts in New York. On October 3, 2004, Desperate Housewives (2004) garnered incredible ratings with its debut episode and ABC picked up the rest of the first season before the end of the month. Less than three months later, Jamie was included in People Magazine&apos;s 2004 &quot;Sexiest Men Alive&quot; issue. During the first and second seasons of Desperate Housewives (2004), Jamie managed to schedule a sweeps week guest star spot on Reba (2001) and, toward the end of the second season, played the role of &quot;Brother John Brown&quot; in Ascension Day (2007). Years after composing the music for and performing in &quot;The Night Hank Williams Died&quot; - a play from his days in Chicago - Jamie accepted an invitation that was proffered to him by Greg Grunberg (Heroes (2006)) and became a singer and guitar player for a band that was first known as &quot;16:9&quot; and then, later, as &quot;The Band From TV&quot;. Other members of the band include, and have included, (the founder and drummer)Greg Grunberg, Hugh Laurie (keyboards, House M.D. (2004)), &apos;Bonnie Somerville&apos; (singer, Cashmere Mafia (2008)) and Bob Guiney (singer, Bachelor #4 on The Bachelor (2002)). The band largely plays at Hollywood events but does, on occasion, play elsewhere. The band donates any money that it makes to charities that are selected by each of its primary members. When the WGA writer&apos;s strike of 2007 shut down production on TV series, there was talk of a tour for the temporarily unemployed band members. A CD that the band made in 2007, &quot;Hoggin&apos; All The Covers&quot; is available for sale at Amazon.com. In addition, at least one of the band&apos;s songs are on the soundtrack for House M.D. (2004) and two of its songs, &quot;Minnie the Moocher&quot; and &quot;You Can&apos;t Always Get What You Want&quot;, are available for purchase on iTunes. While on hiatus, between the second and third seasons of Desperate Housewives (2004), Jamie teamed up with Chris Kattan in the straight-to-DVD film, Undead or Alive: A Zombedy (2007). 2007 was a busy year for Denton. In addition to traveling all over the country in order to lend his celebrity to dozens of charitable causes, he also completed three projects - ABC&apos;s Masters of Science Fiction (2007)&apos;s episode, Masters of Science Fiction: The Discarded (2007); Custody (2007), which aired on Lifetime and Tortured (2008). The same year, Denton, a lifelong fan of baseball, joined an Orange County investment group that purchased the Golden Baseball League Team, &quot;The Fullerton Flyers&quot;. Shortly after the purchase and, although the team&apos;s home field remained at Cal State Fullerton, the group changed the name of the team to &quot;The Orange County Flyers&quot;. Not content to merely be an investor, Jamie took as active a role as his schedule and the team structure allowed, attending try-outs, where he had a hand in selecting some of the players during his first season as a co-owner, and attending quite a few of the home games. When &quot;Housewives&quot; isn&apos;t in production, JD still takes part in other productions. These have included Group Sex (2010) and bringing the voice of &quot;Superman&quot; to life in the animated video, All-Star Superman (2011). He played the role of &quot;Slim&quot; in the independent film, Karaoke Man (2012). Jamie announced on the Christopher Gabriel radio program that he and his family were moving to Minnesota in August of 2012 and that he would pursue whatever comes next from there. His fans didn&apos;t have to wait long to hear from him again. In 2013 JD took on the role of Johnny Trey in &quot;Grace Unplugged&quot; and in short order won an award for Outstanding Performance by an Actor. The film won a Top Ten Family Film of the Year and the Grand Prize, &quot;The Epiphany Award&quot; for Most Inspirational Film of 2013. Jamie went on to do the Hallmark Channel&apos;s &quot;Stranded In Paradise&quot;, &quot;Ovation&quot;, &quot;Strangers&quot;, &quot;The Dancer and the Dame&quot; and &quot;Revelation Road 3: The Black Rider&quot;. 2014 found Jamie making a deal with The Hallmark Channel to become (as &quot;Dr. Sam&quot;) part of their original series, &quot;The Good Witch&quot;. His episodes will begin airing in February, 2015. On the home front, a lot of JD&apos;s free time is now spent at Bring It! Studios and Crossfit Channhassen, MN, which is the latest business venture which Jamie and his wife have undertaken.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>125</ID>
<Name>James Naughton</Name>
<Description>James Naughton, a handsome charmer and solid, reliable player on film and TV, is best-known for his magnetic work on the musical stage. The two-time Tony award winner for his cynical, &quot;Sam Spade&quot;-like detective in &quot;City of Angels&quot; (1990) and slick, shyster lawyer/razzle dazzler &quot;Billy Flynn&quot; in the revival of &quot;Chicago&quot; (1997), hails from Yale (School of Drama) and began scoring on Broadway in the 70s with his sharp portrayal as &quot;Edmund&quot; in &quot;Long Day&apos;s Journey Into Night&quot;, and in his Broadway debut with &quot;I Love My Wife&quot;. He has also directed stage plays, such as Arthur Miller&apos;s &quot;The Price&quot; and &quot;Our Town&quot; with Paul Newman and Jane Curtin. A number of TV series throughout the decades failed, however, to light up his name in Hollywood with Making the Grade (1982), Trauma Center (1983) and The Cosby Mysteries (1994), coming and going. The same goes with his steady, restrained work in the films, The Paper Chase (1973), The Glass Menagerie (1987), The Good Mother (1988) and The First Wives Club (1996). Best-known for his trustworthy husbands (well, not always) and well-dressed professionals, he has one of those strong, worldly faces you recognize but can&apos;t place. Recently, Naughton has taken to the cabaret circuit where his simple, relaxed singing style has caught on, especially in his award-winning one-man show &quot;Street of Dreams&quot; which was comprised of a number of eclectic songs from country and western to contemporary pop to classic standards. His children Greg and Keira are also in the business.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>126</ID>
<Name>James Pickens Jr.</Name>
<Description>James Pickens Jr. was born October 26, 1954 in Cleveland, Ohio. While attending college at Bowling Green State University, Pickens began pursuing an interest in acting. He graduated from BGSU with a Bachelor of Fine Arts in 1976. Afterwards, Pickens began work on the stage at the Roundabout Theatre in New York City. During his time on the stage, he starred in the Negro Ensemble Company&apos;s production of &quot;A Soldier&apos;s Play&quot; with famous Black American actors Denzel Washington and Samuel L. Jackson. Ten years since graduating and beginning his career in acting, Pickens first came to the screen as an ambulance driver in F/X (1986). In that same year, he appeared on the soap opera Another World (1964) from 1986-1990. Pickens also made several appearances on the popular romance drama Beverly Hills, 90210 (1990), and the comedy series Roseanne (1988) among a steady line-up of work during the 1990s.Throughout his extensive work on television, Pickens is best known to audiences as Dr. Richard Webber, on the medical drama Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005). It is also the same role in which he would reprise on the spin-off series Private Practice (2007) two years later. In later years, namely beginning in the 2010s, Pickens could also be seen in the sports drama 42 (2013) starring Harrison Ford and Chadwick Boseman. Outside of acting, Pickens spends much of his time around horses and often indulges in horseback riding roping cattle. As a competitive roper, Pickens is part of the United States Championship Roping team and often travels across country to various events. He is married to Gina Pickens (nee Taylor) and is father of two sons Carl and Gavyn who both are into the entertainment business.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>127</ID>
<Name>James Tupper</Name>
<Description>James Tupper was born on August 4, 1965 in Dartmouth, Nova Scotia, Canada as James Howard Tupper. He is an actor and writer, known for Revenge (2011), Mr. Popper&apos;s Penguins (2011) and Playing for Keeps (2012). He was previously married to Katherine Mayfield.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>128</ID>
<Name>Jamie Chung</Name>
<Description>Jamie Chung was born and raised in California, the daughter of Korean parents. She studied Economics at the University of California, Riverside. Chung&apos;s break came in 2004, when she was working in a sports bar. MTV held auditions for The Real World (1992) there, she tried out, and was successful, appearing in the San Diego based fourteenth season.Chung went on to successfully launched an acting career, making her debut with a small part in Veronica Mars (2004). Roles in other TV series followed, including Days of Our Lives (1965) and Greek (2007). She also transitioned into feature films with such projects as Sorority Row (2009), Sucker Punch (2011) and The Hangover Part II (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>129</ID>
<Name>Jamie Dornan</Name>
<Description>Jamie Dornan was born on May 1, 1982 in Belfast, Northern Ireland as James Dornan. He is an actor, known for Fifty Shades of Grey (2015), Marie Antoinette (2006) and The Fall (2013). He has been married to Amelia Warner since April 27, 2013. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>130</ID>
<Name>Janel Parrish</Name>
<Description>Janel Parrish was born on October 30, 1988 in Oahu, Hawaii, USA as Janel Meilani Parrish. She is an actress, known for Pretty Little Liars (2010), Bratz (2007) and Celeste &amp; Jesse Forever (2012).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>131</ID>
<Name>Jared Gilmore</Name>
<Description>Jared Gilmore was born on May 30, 2000 in San Diego, California, USA as Jared Scott Gilmore. He is an actor, known for Once Upon a Time (2011), The Back-up Plan (2010) and Mad Men (2007).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>132</ID>
<Name>Jason Burkart</Name>
<Description>Jason was born in the small hockey town of Trail, British Columbia, Canada. He spent most of his youth playing hockey at the triple A and Junior levels. He later turned towards officiating and eventually worked professionally in the Western Hockey League and the East Coast Hockey League. His on-ice skills landed him jobs in the movie Miracle (Kurt Russell) and The Tooth Fairy (Dwayne Johnson). While working on the Tooth Fairy and sending Dwayne The Rock Johnson to the penalty box he decided to pursue something that he always wanted to do... act and write. Weeks later he had booked his first ever audition and he was hooked. Jason jumped in head first and within two years he was acting/producing/writing the comedy feature Jackhammer (Jamie Kennedy, Pamela Anderson, Robb Wells and Nicole Sullivan) with his friends. The movie would go on to open in four film festivals and get distribution with Phase 4 Films (eOne) and is currently available on demand, Hulu, and iTunes. Shortly after Jason booked a recurring role on ABC&apos;s hit show Once Upon A Time playing the legendary role of Little John.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>133</ID>
<Name>Jason George</Name>
<Description>Jason George was born on February 9, 1972 in Virginia Beach, Virginia, USA as Jason Winston George. He is an actor and producer, known for Sunset Beach (1997), Eve (2003) and Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005). He has been married to Vandana Khanna since July 10, 1999. They have one child.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>134</ID>
<Name>Jenna Coleman</Name>
<Description>Jenna Coleman was born on April 27, 1986 in Blackpool, England as Jenna-Louise Coleman. She is an actress, known for Emmerdale Farm (1972), Doctor Who (2005) and Captain America: The First Avenger (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>135</ID>
<Name>Jennifer Lawrence</Name>
<Description>Academy Award-winning actress Jennifer Lawrence is best known for playing Katniss Everdeen in The Hunger Games (2012), Tiffany Maxwell in Silver Linings Playbook (2012), and Rosalyn Rosenfeld in American Hustle (2013).Jennifer Shrader Lawrence was born on August 15, 1990 in Louisville, Kentucky, to Karen (Koch), who manages a children&apos;s camp, and Gary Lawrence, who works in construction. She has two older brothers, Ben and Blaine, and has English, German, Irish, and Scottish ancestry.Before Jennifer became an actress, she was involved in cheer-leading, field hockey, softball, and modeling, none of which she held a passion for. Her career began when she traveled to Manhattan at the age of 14. After conducting her first cold read, agents told her mother that &quot;it was the best cold read by a 14- year-old they had ever heard&quot;, and tried to convince her mother that she needed to spend the summer in Manhattan. After leaving the agency, Jen was spotted by an agent in the midst of shooting an H&amp;M ad and asked to take her picture. The next day, that agent followed up with her and invited her to the studio for a cold read audition. Again, the agents were highly impressed and strongly urged her mother to allow her to spend the summer in New York City. As fate would have it, she did, and subsequently appeared in commercials such as MTV&apos;s &quot;My Super Sweet 16&quot; and played a role in the movie, The Devil You Know (2013).Her big break came when she played Ree in Winter&apos;s Bone (2010), which landed her Academy Award and Golden Globe nominations. Shortly thereafter, she secured the role of Mystique in franchise reboot X: First Class (2011), which went on to be a hit in Summer 2011. Around this time, Lawrence scored the role of a lifetime when she was cast as Katniss Everdeen in the big-screen adaptation of literary sensation The Hunger Games (2012). That went on to become one of the highest-grossing movies ever with over $407 million at the domestic box office, and instantly propelled Lawrence to the A-list among young actors/actresses.Three Hunger Games sequels are scheduled for release in November 2013, 2014, and 2015, with Lawrence reprising her role at least for the first one (The Hunger Games: Catching Fire (2013)). In 2012 the romantic comedy Silver Linings Playbook earned her the Academy Award, Golden Globe Award, Screen Actors Guild Award, Satellite Award and the Independent Spirit Award for Best Actress, amongst other accolades, making her the youngest person ever to be nominated for two Academy Awards for Best Actress and the second-youngest Best Actress winner.Lawrence can also be seen in The Beaver (2011), Like Crazy (2011), House at the End of the Street (2012), and American Hustle (2013). She played the title role, Joy Mangano, in the 2015 David O. Russell film Joy (2015).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>136</ID>
<Name>Jennifer Morrison</Name>
<Description>Jennifer Marie Morrison was born in Chicago, Illinois, the oldest child of teachers David and Judy Morrison. She was raised in Arlington Heights, IL, with a younger sister and brother. She attended the same school her parents taught at, Prospect High School. As a child, she did some work as a model. After graduating from high school, she attended Loyola University in Chicago, where she studied Theater and English. She then moved on to study at the Steppenwolf Theater Company, before relocating to Los Angeles, California to pursue her acting career. Morrison&apos;s movie debut came in 1994, playing the daughter of Richard Gere and Sharon Stone in Intersection (1994). Success followed with various film and television roles, including the lead in Urban Legends: Final Cut (2000). She came to wide scale public attention in 2004 for her role as Dr. Allison Cameron in the television series House M.D. (2004), for which she was nominated for a prestigious Screen Actors Guild Award. Since leaving &quot;House M.D.&quot;, her career has continued to progress with roles in Star Trek (2009), How I Met Your Mother (2005) and Warrior (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>137</ID>
<Name>Jeremy Renner</Name>
<Description>In Los Angeles, Renner devoted himself to theater, most notably starring in and co-directing the critically acclaimed &quot;Search and Destroy.&quot; He pursued other projects during this time as well, landing his first film role in 1995&apos;s Senior Trip (1995). After several commercials and supporting roles in television movies and series, Renner captured the attention of critics with his gripping, complex portrayal of the infamous serial killer in the 2002 film Dahmer (2002). Renner&apos;s performance, which earned him an Independent Spirit Award nomination, is especially remarkable for painting a humane and sympathetic, yet deeply disturbing, portrait of the title character.In 2003, Renner took a break from small indie films to work on his first commercially successful movie, S.W.A.T. (2003), with Colin Farrell. In 2005, he played the leading role in Neo Ned (2005) as an institutionalized white supremacist in love with a black girl, winning the Palm Beach International Film Festival&apos;s best actor award. Renner&apos;s pivotal supporting roles in 2005&apos;s 12 and Holding (2005) and North Country (2005) earned him accolades from critics, and his 2007 turn in Take (2007) garnered him the best actor award at California&apos;s Independent Film Festival. Also in 2007, Renner played a leading role in the horror film 28 Weeks Later (2007) as well as a supporting role in the underrated Western epic The Assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford (2007), with Casey Affleck, Brad Pitt, and Sam Rockwell.Renner&apos;s depiction of Jeffrey Dahmer in 2002 caught the attention of director Kathryn Bigelow, and, in 2008, she cast him in his most famous role as Sergeant First Class William James in The Hurt Locker (2008). Renner&apos;s performance as a single-minded bomb specialist scored him an Academy Award nomination for best actor. He also earned best actor nominations from the Independent Spirit Awards, the Screen Actors Guild, and the BAFTA Awards, as well as wins in this category from several film critics groups.In 2009, Renner starred in the short-lived TV series, The Unusuals (2009), and in 2010 he played the chilling but loyal criminal Jem in Ben Affleck bank-heist thriller The Town (2010). In the fall of 2010, Renner began filming Mission: Impossible - Ghost Protocol (2011). He has also since starred in The Avengers (2012), American Hustle (2013), and Kill the Messenger (2014).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>138</ID>
<Name>Jerome Flynn</Name>
<Description>Jerome Flynn was born on March 16, 1963 in Bromley, Kent, England as Jerome Patrick Flynn. He is an actor, known for Game of Thrones (2011), Ripper Street (2012) and Soldier Soldier (1991).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>139</ID>
<Name>Jerrika Hinton</Name>
<Description>Jerrika Hinton was born on September 28, 1981 in Dallas, Texas, USA as Jerrika Delayne Hinton. She is an actress and producer, known for Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005), The Roommate (2011) and A Christmas Kiss (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>140</ID>
<Name>Jesse Metcalfe</Name>
<Description>Jesse Eden Metcalfe was born in Carmel Valley, California, to Nancy (DeMaio) and Jeff Metcalfe. He has Italian, Portuguese, English, French, and Irish ancestry. He was raised in Southeastern Connecticut. Metcalfe attended the Williams School, a private high school in New London, Connecticut. He pursued his higher education at New York University where he studied acting and film at the prestigious Tisch School of the Arts.Metcalfe first appeared on the small screen in NBC&apos;s daytime drama, &apos;Passions&apos;, but rose to fame on the mega-hit series, &apos;Desperate Housewives&apos; playing teenage boy-toy, John Rowland. He&apos;s since been the lead in both studio and independent features. Best known for carrying Twentieth Century Fox&apos;s successful teen-comedy &quot;John Tucker Must Die&quot; and starring opposite Michael Douglas in &quot;Beyond A Reasonable Doubt&quot;.2011 saw Jesse cast in TNT&apos;s reboot of the iconic series, &apos;Dallas&apos;. Playing the Christopher Ewing, son of Bobby Ewing (Patrick Duffy).Metcalfe is an avid art enthusiast and collector, plays both guitar and piano, enjoys basketball, boxing and weight training.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>141</ID>
<Name>Jesse Williams</Name>
<Description>Jesse Wesley Williams born August 5, 1981 is an American actor, model, and activist, best known for his role as Dr. Jackson Avery on the ABC Television series Grey&apos;s Anatomy. He also appears in the hit 2013 film Lee Daniels&apos; The Butler as real life civil rights leader Rev. James Lawson. Previous roles include Holden in The Cabin in the Woods (2012), Officer Eddie Quinlan in Brooklyn&apos;s Finest (2009) and as Leo, Lena&apos;s boyfriend, in the film sequel The Sisterhood of the Traveling Pants 2 (2008).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>142</ID>
<Name>Jessica Capshaw</Name>
<Description>Jessica Capshaw was born in Columbia, Missouri, the daughter of actress Kate Capshaw (née Kathleen Sue Nail) and salesman Robert Capshaw. Her parents were both students at the University of Missouri. The family moved to New York to pursue Kate&apos;s modeling career. Her parents divorced when she was three and Jessica got drawn into her mother&apos;s new world. Kate married director Steven Spielberg when Jessica was 15. Among her three parents, she is one of 10 biological and adopted siblings. Jessica graduated from Brown University in 1998 with an English degree. She then attended acting classes at the Royal Academy of Dramatic Arts in London. From there, she got her first acting role on TV&apos;s Odd Man Out (1999).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>143</ID>
<Name>Jessica Szohr</Name>
<Description>Jessica Szohr was born on March 31, 1985 in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, USA as Jessica Karen Szohr. She is an actress, known for Gossip Girl (2007), Two Night Stand (2014) and The Internship (2013).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>144</ID>
<Name>Joana Metrass</Name>
<Description>Born in Lisbon, Portugal with Italian, French, Argentinian, Chinese and Cape Vert heritage.She moved to the U.S.A at 17 to do her senior year as an exchange student.She went back to Portugal where she attended the Portuguese National Conservatory, in between studies in New York and Italy . Worked for several years in the Portuguese film and TV industry. Moved to London in June 2013. Where she landed her first parts in International movies.Wins a Gulbenkian scholarship to study in L.A for 3 months in Feb 2014. Returns to her work in London until moving to L.A in Jan 2015.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>145</ID>
<Name>JoAnna Garcia Swisher </Name>
<Description>Born and raised in Tampa, Florida, USA, she first got into performing at the age of 10 when she auditioned for a local theater production and landed the lead. She continued to act in high school where she was discovered by Nickelodeon and commuted from Florida to Montreal, Canada to star for two seasons in the television series Are You Afraid of the Dark? (1990). After graduating from high school, she spent a year attending Florida State University, but dropped out to move to Hollywood where she worked extensively in television and then in popular movies.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>146</ID>
<Name>John Barrowman</Name>
<Description>Born in Glasgow, Scotland, and raised in Joliet, Illinois. He returned to the UK, for a 6 month Shakespeare semester with the United States International University of San Diego, but left to star in the musical production of &quot;Anything Goes,&quot; with Elaine Page. He went on to star in &quot;Miss Saigon,&quot; &quot;Matador,&quot; &quot;Rope,&quot; and &quot;Hair&quot; at London&apos;s West End. Barrowman has homes in London and Cardiff, Wales.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>147</ID>
<Name>John Bradley</Name>
<Description>John was born as John Bradley-West in 1988. Brought up in Wythenshawe, South Manchester, he attended St Paul&apos;s High School and Loreto College, Hulme before going on to Manchester Metropolitan University from where he graduated in 2010 with a B.A. degree in acting. It was via his college website that he obtained his first big television role in the epic fantasy series &apos;Game of Thrones&apos; though he has since moved nearer home to appear in &apos;Shameless&apos;. He is also an accomplished drummer and has experience in stand up comedy.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>148</ID>
<Name>Johnny Depp</Name>
<Description>Johnny Depp is perhaps one of the most versatile actors of his day and age in Hollywood.He was born John Christopher Depp II in Owensboro, Kentucky, on June 9, 1963, to Betty Sue (Wells), who worked as a waitress, and John Christopher Depp, a civil engineer.Depp was raised in Florida. He dropped out of school when he was 15, and fronted a series of music-garage bands, including one named &apos;The Kids&apos;. However, it was when he married Lori Anne Allison (Lori A. Depp) that he took up the job of being a ballpoint-pen salesman to support himself and his wife. A visit to Los Angeles, California, with his wife, however, happened to be a blessing in disguise, when he met up with actor Nicolas Cage, who advised him to turn to acting, which culminated in Depp&apos;s film debut in the low-budget horror film, A Nightmare on Elm Street (1984), where he played a teenager who falls prey to dream-stalking demon Freddy Krueger.In 1987 he shot to stardom when he replaced Jeff Yagher in the role of undercover cop Tommy Hanson in the popular TV series 21 Jump Street (1987).In 1990, after numerous roles in teen-oriented films, his first of a handful of great collaborations with director Tim Burton came about when Depp played the title role in Edward Scissorhands (1990). Following the film&apos;s success, Depp carved a niche for himself as a serious, somewhat dark, idiosyncratic performer, consistently selecting roles that surprised critics and audiences alike. He continued to gain critical acclaim and increasing popularity by appearing in many features before re-joining with Burton in the lead role of Ed Wood (1994). In 1997 he played an undercover FBI agent in the fact-based film Donnie Brasco (1997), opposite Al Pacino; in 1998 he appeared in Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas (1998), directed by Terry Gilliam; and then, in 1999, he appeared in the sci-fi/horror film The Astronaut&apos;s Wife (1999). The same year he teamed up again with Burton in Sleepy Hollow (1999), brilliantly portraying Ichabod Crane.Depp has played many characters in his career, including another fact-based one, Insp. Fred Abberline in From Hell (2001). He stole the show from screen greats such as Antonio Banderas in the finale to Robert Rodriguez&apos;s &quot;mariachi&quot; trilogy, Once Upon a Time in Mexico (2003). In that same year he starred in the marvelous family blockbuster Pirates of the Caribbean: The Curse of the Black Pearl (2003), playing a character that only the likes of Depp could pull off: the charming, conniving and roguish Capt. Jack Sparrow. The film&apos;s enormous success has opened several doors for his career and included an Oscar nomination. He appeared as the central character in the Stephen King-based movie, Secret Window (2004); as the kind-hearted novelist James Barrie in the factually-based Finding Neverland (2004), where he co-starred with Kate Winslet; and Rochester in the British film, The Libertine (2004). Depp collaborated again with Burton in a screen adaptation of Roald Dahl&apos;s novel, Charlie and the Chocolate Factory (2005), and later in Alice in Wonderland (2010) and Dark Shadows (2012).Off-screen, Depp has dated several female celebrities, and has been engaged to Sherilyn Fenn, Jennifer Grey, Winona Ryder and Kate Moss. He was married to Lori Anne Allison in 1983, but divorced her in 1985. Depp has two children with French singer/actress Vanessa Paradis: Lily-Rose Melody, born in 1999 and Jack, born in 2002. He married actress/producer Amber Heard in 2015.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>149</ID>
<Name>Josh Bowman</Name>
<Description>Josh Bowman was born on March 4, 1988 in Windsor and Maidenhead, Berkshire, England as Joshua Tobias Bowman. He is an actor, known for Revenge (2011), So Undercover (2012) and Prowl (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>150</ID>
<Name>Josh Dallas</Name>
<Description>Josh Dallas was born in Louisville Kentucky. He grew up right across the Ohio River in New Albany Indiana. He attended New Albany Senior Public High School, and was heavily involved in the school&apos;s award-winning performing Arts programs. This is where the fire was lit, that would push Josh to continue pursing the arts. While at New Albany High School at the age of sixteen, Josh received the Sarah Exley Scholarship, a full ride scholarship given to one American student every three years to study acting at the prestigious &quot;Mountview Conservatoire for the Performing Arts&quot; in London, England. At the age of 20, Josh landed his first professional job as an actor with the acclaimed Royal Shakespeare Company. He then went on to perform with some of the most renowned theater companies in the world, including the Royal National Theatre, The English National Opera, The New Shakespeare Company, The Young Vic, to name a few. Never leaving Theatre far behind, Josh began landing parts in Television and Independent Films. Missing the USA after spending ten years in London, Josh made the move back stateside and landed in Hollywood. Five days after being back in the states, Josh got the call that he was being offered the leading role of &quot;Fandral&quot; in 2011&apos;s blockbuster, Thor (2011), by Marvel Studios, directed by the Oscar-nominated director/actor Kenneth Branagh.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>151</ID>
<Name>Josh Hutcherson</Name>
<Description>Joshua Ryan Hutcherson was born on October 12, 1992 in Union, Kentucky to Michelle Fightmaster Hutcherson, who worked for Delta Air Lines, and Chris Hutcherson, an EPA analyst. He has one younger brother, Connor Hutcherson. From the age of four, Josh knew that he wanted to be an actor. In order to pursue his goal, Josh and his family moved to Los Angeles when he was nine-years-old.In 2002, Josh landed his first acting role in the TV film, House Blend (2002), with Amy Yasbeck, Dan Cortese and Sean Faris. The same year, Josh was cast in the pilot, Becoming Glen (2002), but Fox did not order it to series (though, several years later, it was reconfigured as the short-lived series, The Winner (2007), starring Rob Corddry, and co-written/produced by Seth MacFarlane). Toward the end of 2002, Josh appeared on an episode of ER (1994).Josh made his big-screen debut, in 2003, with a bit part in the Oscar-nominated American Splendor (2003). His career began its measured ascent in 2005 with a supporting slot as one of Will Ferrell&apos;s kids in Kicking &amp; Screaming (2005), a co-starring role in the indie hit Little Manhattan (2005), and another co-starring role in Zathura: A Space Adventure (2005), which was originally conceived as a sequel to Jumanji (1995). Despite underperforming at the box office, &quot;Zathura&quot; helped earned for Josh his first Young Artist Award for &quot;Leading Young Actor&quot;.2006 saw bigger returns for Josh&apos;s burgeoning film career with a role as one of Robin Williams&apos; sons in the modest hit, RV (2006). The following year, he landed his first breakthrough role in Bridge to Terabithia (2007), the kid-approved adaptation of Katherine Paterson&apos;s novel that co-starred AnnaSophia Robb, whose career was also taking off at this time.Josh starred as Brendan Fraser&apos;s nephew in another family-film hit, Journey to the Center of the Earth (2008), and he had a smaller role in the Crash-like drama, Fragments (2008), though by now his face and name were being used in movie-marketing materials. Though it wasn&apos;t a hit, Josh&apos;s character in Cirque du Freak: The Vampire&apos;s Assistant (2009) served as a major plot device early in the story.In 2010, Josh co-starred in the critically-acclaimed film, The Kids Are All Right (2010), alongside Annette Bening, Julianne Moore, Mark Ruffalo, and Mia Wasikowska. The film received several awards and four Academy Award nominations, including Best Picture. Josh&apos;s performance as the youngest child in a family, led by two mothers, earned him acclaim from audiences and the industry, alike. Josh followed up with an expanded role in Journey 2: The Mysterious Island (2012), which saw Dwayne Johnson take over as the main character from Brendan Fraser. Between the star power and the allure of 3D, the sequel was a worldwide hit and a third installment is in development.With the announcement that he would portray the beloved &quot;Peeta Mellark&quot; in The Hunger Games (2012), the film adaptation of the best-selling novel written by Suzanne Collins, Josh became an instant celebrity. In the wake of the movie&apos;s massive worldwide success, Detention (2011), a horror/comedy that Josh made before &quot;The Hunger Games&quot;, was released. Josh was also an executive producer on that feature.Before Josh reprises his role as &quot;Peeta&quot; in The Hunger Games: Catching Fire (2013), we will see him in the long-delayed remake of Red Dawn (2012); the omnibus 7 días en La Habana (2012) (aka &quot;7 Days in Havana&quot;) (Josh&apos;s segment was directed by Benicio Del Toro); The Forger (2012) opposite Lauren Bacall, Alfred Molina, and Hayden Panettiere; and the animated Epic (2013) from Ice Age (2002) co-director (and voice of &quot;Scrat&quot;), Chris Wedge.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>152</ID>
<Name>Joshua Logan Moore</Name>
<Description>Originally from Texas, Joshua Logan Moore began performing at an early age in student film projects with the University of Texas as well as Austin Film School.Known for his stand-up comedy performances, in 2005 Moore won Austin&apos;s Funniest Kid at Cap City Comedy Club for ages 9-12, and was first runner up for all age groups. Following a move to LA in 2007, he performed at the Hollywood Improv with a teen comedy group, and also starred in Ray Bradbury&apos;s &quot;Dandelion Wine&quot; at the Fremont Centre Theatre in South Pasadena. But the highlight for Moore as an actor was the opportunity he had to work with legendary actor/director Clint Eastwood in the film &quot;Changeling.&quot;</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>153</ID>
<Name>Joy Jorgensen</Name>
<Description>Joy Lauren (born Lauren Joy Jorgensen) was born and raised in Atlanta, Georgia. She starting acting in regional theater and television in the Southeast, before moving to Los Angeles in 2001. After working in film and television, including four seasons on ABC&apos;s &quot;Desperate Housewives,&quot; Joy began her college education at the Columbia University, where she majored in American History.Joy now resides in Brooklyn, New York where she is writing and directing films under the tutelage of the graduate film program at New York University.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>154</ID>
<Name>Julian Glover</Name>
<Description>Julian Wyatt Glover was born on March 27, 1935 in Hampstead, London, England, to Honor Ellen Morgan (Wyatt), a BBC journalist, and Claude Gordon Glover, a BBC radio producer. He is of English, Scottish and Welsh ancestry. Primarily a classical stage actor, Glover trained at the National Youth Theatre, performed with the Royal Shakespeare Company and became a familiar face to British television viewers by appearing in many popular series during the 1960s and 1970s. His talent for accents and cold expression made him an ideal choice for playing refined villains. During the 1980s, Glover achieved some fame in Hollywood by playing roles in such popular films as Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back (1980), For Your Eyes Only (1981) and Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade (1989). He was awarded Commander of the Order of the British Empire in the 2013 Queen&apos;s Birthday Honours List for his services to drama.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>155</ID>
<Name>Julian Morris</Name>
<Description>Julian Morris began acting at the Anna Scher Theatre in London. After training under Scher, he went on to spend three seasons with the Royal Shakespeare Company, which he merits as being a major influence on his craft.He has played popular characters in several of the most successful shows of the last decade: Agent Owen in &apos;24&apos;, as Dr Andrew Wade in &apos;ER&apos;, as Prince Phillip in &apos;Once Upon A Time&apos;, and as part of the original cast in &apos;Pretty Little Liars&apos;.In film, he&apos;s appeared alongside Jon Voight in &apos;Beyond&apos; and Tom Cruise in &apos;Valkyrie&apos;, starred in Universal&apos;s &apos;Cry Wolf&apos;, the British cult-hit &apos;Donkey Punch&apos;, and the BAFTA winning movie, &apos;Kelly + Victor&apos; directed by Kieran Evans.He recently played a popular guest-arc in &apos;New Girl&apos; opposite Zooey Deschanel, and the lead in Universal&apos;s sequel to &apos;Dragonheart&apos;, produced by Raffaella De Laurentiis.He&apos;s currently shooting the Amazon series &apos;Hand of God&apos; directed by Marc Forster.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>156</ID>
<Name>Justin Chambers</Name>
<Description>Justin Willman Chambers was born on July 11, 1970 in Springfield, Ohio, USA. His is one of five children of Pamela Sue (Willman) and John William Eugene Chambers II, and has English, Irish, and German ancestry. He has a twin brother named Jason, one older brother and two older sisters. While on vacation in Paris, he was spotted by an agent and soon went on modeling for Calvin Klein, Giorgio Armani, and others throughout Europe, Japan and the United States. In the 1990s, he settled in New York, where he studied at H.B. Studios for 4 years. That schooling yielded him appearances in several off-Broadway stage productions and a few television roles.Chambers&apos; first break came in 1995, a four-month gig on a long-running NBC&apos;s daytime soap Another World (1964), then he appeared opposite Lolita Davidovich in Harvest of Fire (1996) and in CBS&apos;s Rose Hill (1997) opposite Jennifer Garner. After that, he catapulted to the &quot;IT&quot; list of the late 1990s and was described as &quot;part-James Dean, part-&apos;Marlon Brando&apos;&quot; by Harper&apos;s Bazaar in 1998. He made his big screen debut in the featured role of a rich WASP who befriended a Jewish kid in Liberty Heights (1999), a Barry Levinson drama. He then starred as &quot;D&apos;Artagnan&quot; in The Musketeer (2001) alongside Catherine Deneuve and Mena Suvari, then co-starred with Matthew McConaughey and Jennifer Lopez in The Wedding Planner (2001). His career slowed down for a few years, yielding little meaningful exposure in films and on TV, with the exception of a supporting role alongside Uma Thurman and Gena Rowlands in HBO&apos;s Hysterical Blindness (2002). In 2005, Chambers made a comeback starring as &quot;Dr. Alex Karev&quot; opposite Katherine Heigl on ABC&apos;s Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005). He also starred as obsessed police detective, &quot;Sgt. Matt Parish&quot;, in the thriller The Zodiac (2005).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>157</ID>
<Name>Karen Gillan</Name>
<Description>Karen was born and raised in Inverness, Scotland, the daughter of Marie (Paterson) and John Gillan, who is a singer and recording artist. She developed a love for acting very early on, attending several youth theatre groups and taking part in a wide range of productions at her school, Charleston Academy.At age 16, Karen decided she wanted to pursue her acting career further and, studied under the renowned theatre director Scott Johnston at the Performing Arts Studio Scotlond. She later attended the prestigious Italia Conti academy in London. During her first year, she landed a role in Rebus (2000) and soon appeared in a variety of programs including Channel 4&apos;s Stacked (2008) and The Kevin Bishop Show (2008), as well as a two-year stint in the long-running series Doctor Who (2005). Karen also stars in the film Outcast (2010), starring James Nesbitt. Her most recent starring role is as Eliza Dooley in &quot;Selfie&quot; (2014).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>158</ID>
<Name>Karine Vanasse</Name>
<Description>Born in Drummondville, Québec, Canada in 1983, Karine Vanasse is the daughter of Conrad Vanasse and Renée Gamache. From as young as 9 years old, Karine expressed her desire to become a singer or an actress and that desire became an ambition when she appeared in Quebec&apos;s teen show &quot;Club des 100 watts&quot; after winning a lip sync competition. It was then, with the help of her mother Gamache and TV show host France Beaudoin, that she begun to audition and take part in TV commercials as well as playing minor and supporting roles in French-Canadian TV movies.In 1998, Karine was approached by what is now known as the &quot;Motion International&quot; production company to co-host the once very popular children&apos;s science show in Quebec, &quot;Les Petits Debrouillards&quot; in an attempt to re-brand its &quot;comeback&quot; with a new, friendlier image. It was during her time on this show that she was spotted and hired by a producer Lorraine Richard and director Léa Pool to play the role of &apos;Hanna&apos; in her first big break &apos;Emporte-moi (1999)_, a film telling the story of a teenager trying to find her identity in a tormented family environment. The film was presented in 40 festivals, shown across 20 countries and earned two Oscar nominations for best foreign film. Her performance was highly acclaimed both nationally and internationally and earned her the title of best actress at the Gala of Jutra, in Quebec.Karine then moved on to play Zac (Benoit Langlais)&apos;s love interest in the controversial Quebec TV series: 2 frères (1999). Her character, Lucie, became much more prominent and realistic in 2000-2001 and the debate stirred by the realistic and violent reality revealed led her to become, together with Langlais, a spokesperson for the government-funded TV program &quot;Parler, c&apos;est grandir&quot;, a broadcast aimed at youngsters from unstable backgrounds.Her teen roles begun to stick and at the risk of becoming typecast she took on the main role for the feature film Du pic au coeur (2001), a trendy production by Céline Baril on the intricacies of today&apos;s youngsters&apos; love lives. In the spring of 2001, Karine applied for the ITHAKA program and took a six-month break in Greece to devote her time to traveling and academic work.Karine&apos;s acting career does not stop at TV and the Cinema, she has also appeared in various Theatrical productions both French and Canadian and she will soon join Elisha Cuthbert and Mia Kirshnerin in the Holywood stepladder by performing next to Charlize Theron and Penélope Cruz in John Duigan&apos;s 2004 production: Head in the Clouds (2004).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>159</ID>
<Name>Kate Walsh</Name>
<Description>Kate Walsh was born in San Jose, California, on October 13, 1967. She grew up partly in San Jose and partly in Tucson, Arizona, later attending the University of Arizona, where she got involved in regional theater. She later moved to Chicago where she began working with the Piven Theatre Workshop and, later, the Chicago Shakespeare Repertory. She performed on National Public Radio in the production of the radio play &quot;Born Guilty&quot;. Walsh later moved to New York City and joined the comedy troupe &quot;Burn Manhattan&quot;, performing in a number of Off-Broadway plays.Her first major television appearance came on The Drew Carey Show (1995) where she portrayed Niki Fifer, Drew&apos;s girlfriend and a woman struggling with her weight. She went on to portray Carol Nelson in HBO&apos;s The Mind of the Married Man (2001) television series, and played Norm MacDonald&apos;s romantic interest in the sitcom The Norm Show (1999). She continues to appear on television programs in supporting or bit parts.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>160</ID>
<Name>Katherine Heigl</Name>
<Description>Katherine Marie Heigl was born on November 24, 1978 in Washington, D.C., to Nancy Heigl (née Engelhardt), a personnel manager, and Paul Heigl, an accountant and executive. Her father is of German/Swiss-German and Irish descent, and her mother is of German ancestry.Following a number of commercials and modeling assignments for Sears and Lord &amp; Taylor, she made her big-screen debut in That Night (1992), which starred Juliette Lewis and C. Thomas Howell. It was then that she realized that acting rather than modeling was her passion. In 1993, Katherine appeared in Steven Soderbergh&apos;s critically-acclaimed Depression-era drama, King of the Hill (1993), before landing her first leading role as a rebellious teenager, alongside Gérard Depardieu, in My Father the Hero (1994). In 1995, she played &quot;Sarah Ryback&quot;, the niece of Steven Seagal&apos;s character, in Under Siege 2: Dark Territory (1995), which was her &quot;debut&quot; in the action film genre. Television appearances on The Tonight Show with Jay Leno (1992) and Late Night with Conan O&apos;Brien (1993) soon followed, before she took the lead role in Disney&apos;s Wish Upon a Star (1996) in 1996. In 1997, Katherine portrayed &quot;Taffy Entwhistle&quot;, Rita Hayworth&apos;s stand-in, in Stand-ins (1997) and was also cast as the beauteous &quot;Princess Ilene&quot; in the European production, Prince Valiant (1997).During the summer of 2002, Katherine made a major decision in the direction of her career when she signed on for representation in all areas with the William Morris Agency, one of the biggest and most prestigious agencies in the entertainment industry. She is now being represented by Norman Aladjem at Paradigm Agency and being managed by Nancy Heigl and Stephanie Simon and Jason Newman at Untitled Entertainment.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>161</ID>
<Name>Kathryn Joosten</Name>
<Description>Kathryn is best known for her portrayals of &quot;Karen McCluskey&quot; on Desperate Housewives (2004) on ABC and of &quot;Mrs. Landingham&quot;, secretary to the President (Martin Sheen), on the critically-acclaimed NBC drama, The West Wing (1999). She has also recurred on Dharma &amp; Greg (1997), and guest-starred on many hit television series, such as Becker (1998), Arli$$ (1996), Ally McBeal (1997), Providence (1999), Scrubs (2001) and over twenty other prime-time shows. Kathryn will also be seen later this year on ABC&apos;s daytime drama, General Hospital (1963). Her credits are impressive for any actor, let alone one that only began the craft at age 42.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>162</ID>
<Name>Katie Cassidy</Name>
<Description>Katie Cassidy was born Katherine Evelyn Cassidy on November 25, 1986, in Los Angeles, California. Her father, David Cassidy, was a pop star in the 1970s. Her mother, Sherry Williams, was a high fashion model in the early 1970&apos;s. Sherry left her career to concentrate on raising her 3 daughters, with husband, Richard Benedon M.D., Katie&apos;s step-dad. Her famous relatives include uncles Shaun Cassidy, Patrick Cassidy and Ryan Cassidy, and grandparents Jack Cassidy, Evelyn Ward and Shirley Jones. As a child, Katie took gymnastics, studied piano, guitar and singing, then took dancing and acting lessons and eventually became a cheerleader for the California Flyers. She attended Calabasas High School in her neighborhood, where she also cheered as a freshman. Her mother insisted that she complete college prep classes in high school before she embarked on her acting career. For years prior to graduation in 2005, Katie was modeling and studying acting in community theater. Katie had just been accepted to &apos;Tisch&apos; at NYU when she was offered her first role as &quot;Dee Dee&quot;, which was one month before graduating. Katie has not stopped working since. Katie&apos;s early exposure to show business, the cosmopolitan culture of Los Angeles, her family upbringing, and her comprehensive education altogether produced a remarkable result. She grew up as a multifaceted person showing her many talents in a variety of professions such as recording her father&apos;s 1970s hit &quot;I Think I Love You&quot; and singing in VH1&apos;s TV special Bubblegum Babylon (2002), writing her own songs, modeling for Abercrombie and Fitch and Guess?&apos;s Rock and Republic clothing lines in 2004, and acting. However, she was publicly criticized by her father who would have liked for her to wait before she covered his classic hit. During her stint with Artemis Records, she was introduced to the popular boy band Dream Street. There she met Greg Raposo, who wrote the song &quot;We&apos;re In Love&quot; for her when they dated in 2002. She also met her ex-boyfriend, Jesse McCartney, there and later appeared as his love interest in his video hit &quot;She&apos;s No You&quot;. A story on Jesse and Katie appeared in the January 2006 issue of Teen People magazine. At that time she was busy working on five feature film productions going on almost simultaneously. Katie made several appearances in TV series, such as 7th Heaven (1996) and Sex, Love &amp; Secrets (2005), among others. She appeared as Samantha, the grown-up daughter of Adam Sandler and Kate Beckinsale in the comedy Click (2006). After the release of a teen horror film, When a Stranger Calls (2006), in which she co-starred as Tiffany, Cassidy went to Vancouver to work on her second horror film, Black Christmas (2006), in which she stars as a sorority girl. Katie recently beat out the likes of Jessica Simpson and Kristin Cavallari for the leading role opposite John Travolta as his daughter and the heir to the most powerful energy company in the world in Dallas, the big-screen remake of the cult TV series.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>163</ID>
<Name>Kaylee DeFer</Name>
<Description>Born in Tucson, Arizona. Began her career in musical theatre at the age of eight and continued through high school with the lead of Kim in Bye Bye Birdie. Came out to Los Angeles to pursue her love of acting in 2003. Is having a blast and enjoying every minute.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>164</ID>
<Name>Keegan Allen</Name>
<Description>Keegan Allen received his breakout role in ABC Family&apos;s hit series &quot;Pretty Little Liars&quot;, based on the novels by Sara Shepard He portrayed the mysterious &quot;Black Cat&quot; character Toby Cavanaugh.Allen has also made small appearances in TV shows such as Nickelodeon&apos;s &quot;Big Time Rush&quot; and &quot;CSI: Crime Scene Investigation&quot;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>165</ID>
<Name>Keegan Connor Tracy</Name>
<Description>Born in Windsor, Ontario, Canada, Tracy attended Wilfrid Laurier University in Waterloo, Ontario, Canada, where she orginally studied business. She later switched to psychology. She spent a year in Europe working in Dublin, Paris and Nice, where she was supposed to be completing her 4th year of study. She later returned to WLU to finish her degree. She moved to Vancouver, B.C. where she has had all of her acting jobs.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>166</ID>
<Name>Kelly McCreary</Name>
<Description>Kelly McCreary is an actress, known for Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005), Being Flynn (2012) and Emily Owens M.D. (2012).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>167</ID>
<Name>Kelly Rutherford</Name>
<Description>Best-known to television audiences as Lily van der Woodsen, on the hit show Gossip Girl, Kelly played the sophisticated, fashionable, matriarch on the Upper East Side of Manhattan for 6 seasons . Kelly is also known for her former roles in television shows Melrose Place and Homefront, and Brisco county Jr. As well as the film Steam 3. Her most recent projects include playing Laura Wyatt in the ABC hit series Quantico and an online talk show for The View airing soon.Kelly is an advocate of multiple women&apos;s and children&apos;s charities including StepUp Women&apos;s Network, Healthy Child Healthy World, and she is currently a member of the Board of Directors for Free Arts NYC.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>168</ID>
<Name>Kendall Applegate</Name>
<Description>Kendall Applegate was born on March 12, 1999 in Versailles, Kentucky, USA. She is an actress, known for Desperate Housewives (2004), Opposite Day (2009) and Ranger Rob: The Movie (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>169</ID>
<Name>Kevin McKidd</Name>
<Description>Kevin McKidd was born and raised in Elgin, Scotland, the son of Kathleen, a secretary, and Neil McKidd, a plumber. He was a member of the Moray Youth Theatre, before going on to study Engineering at the University of Edinburgh. While at the university, Kevin became involved with Bedlam Theatre, the university&apos;s student theatre company. At this point, Kevin decided to give up on engineering and dropped out of the university to pursue acting full-time. In 1994, he landed the leading role in the stageplay, &quot;The Silver Darlings&quot;, produced by Robert Carlyle&apos;s Rain Dog Theatre Company. It was only a matter of time before Kevin made his screen debut as the vicious gangleader, &quot;Malky Johnson&quot;, in Gillies MacKinnon&apos;s Small Faces (1996). His next role was as the tragic, gentle giant, &quot;Tommy&quot;, in Trainspotting (1996).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>170</ID>
<Name>Kevin Rahm</Name>
<Description>Born in Mineral Wells, Texas and raised in Bossier City, Louisiana, Rahm enrolled in the Brigham Young University theater program.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>171</ID>
<Name>Kevin Zegers</Name>
<Description>Kevin Joseph Zegers was born in Woodstock, Ontario, to Mary-Ellen (Veldman), a teacher, and James Zegers, a quarry worker. All of his grandparents were Dutch immigrants.Zegers started acting at the tender age of 6. He has been in more than 40 films and has also done several modeling campaigns. Zegers lives in Los Angeles, CA with his wife, agent Jaime Feld (CAA)Twin daughters Zoë Madison and Blake Everleigh, born on Aug 17, 2015.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>172</ID>
<Name>Kim Raver</Name>
<Description>Kim Raver was born on March 15, 1969 in New York City, New York, USA as Kimberly Jayne Raver. She is an actress and producer, known for 24 (2001), Third Watch (1999) and Night at the Museum (2006). She has been married to Manu Boyer since July 2000. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>173</ID>
<Name>Kit Harington</Name>
<Description>Kit Harington was born Christopher Catesby Harington in Acton, London, to Deborah Jane (Catesby), a former playwright, and David Richard Harington, a businessman. His mother named him after 16th century British playwright and poet Christopher Marlowe, whose first name was shortened to Kit, a name Harington prefers. Harington&apos;s uncle is Sir Nicholas John Harington, the 14th Baronet Harington, and his paternal great-grandfather was Sir Richard Harington, the 12th Baronet Harington. Through his paternal grandmother, Lavender Cecilia Denny, Kit&apos;s eight times great-grandfather was King Charles II of England. Also through his father, Harington descends from politician Henry Dundas, 1st Viscount Melville, the bacon merchant T. A. Denny, clergyman Baptist Wriothesley Noel, merchant and politician Peter Baillie, peer William Legge, 4th Earl of Dartmouth, and MP Sir William Molesworth, 6th Baronet.Harington was a pupil at the Southfield Primary School from 1992 to 1998. When he was 11, his family moved to Worcestershire, and he studied at the Chantry High School in Martley until 2003. He became interested in acting after watching a production of Waiting for Godot when he was 14, and he performed in several school productions. He attended Worcester Sixth Form College, where he studied Drama and Theatre Studies, between 2003 and 2005. When he was 17, he was inspired to study acting in a drama school after watching a performance by Ben Whishaw playing Hamlet in 2004. He moved back to London when he was eighteen and a year later attended the Central School of Speech and Drama, from which he graduated in 2008.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>174</ID>
<Name>Kristian Nairn</Name>
<Description>Kristian Nairn is a Northern Irish Actor and Musician. He is a successful DJ, having performed alongside acts such as the Scissor Sisters. He has worked Worldwide. Game of Thrones marks Nairn&apos;s first major acting role. He plays the role of the enigmatic fan favorite character, Hodor. He also appeared as a guest on episode 37 of the comedy podcast the Yogpod, discussing his role in a Game Of Thrones with the hosts Simon Lane and Lewis Brindley.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>175</ID>
<Name>Kristin Bauer van Straten</Name>
<Description>Kristin grew up in Wisconsin playing sports, riding horses, and shooting guns. Her father was an avid horseman and gun collector and her mother a housewife involved in charities. Kristin moved to Los Angeles and began acting in 1994 after studying fine arts in St. Louis, Boston and New York. She still studies drawing and painting, and does commissioned portraits in between shooting and working to better the environment. Bauer lives in L.A. with her many rescued animals and her South African husband, musician Abri Van Straten, of the band, &quot;The Lemmings&quot;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>176</ID>
<Name>Kristofer Hivju</Name>
<Description>A second generation Norwegian actor, Kristofer Hivju was born on 7 December 1978 in Oslo. His father Erik Hivju is a prominent character actor who appeared with his son in the short film Flax where Kristofer shared screenwriting credit with director Bård Ivar Engelsås.Kristofer made his American Film debut in Matthijs van Heijningen Jr.&apos;s 2011 remake of John Carpenter&apos;s The Thing. Next he was seen in M. Night Shyamalan&apos;s After Earth but he is most recognizable as fan favorite Tormund Giantsbane on HBO&apos;s Game of Thrones.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>177</ID>
<Name>Kyle MacLachlan</Name>
<Description>MacLachlan was born and raised in Yakima, Washington, to Catherine Louise (Stone), a public relations director, and Kent Alan McLachlan, a lawyer and stockbroker. He has Scottish, English, Cornish, and German ancestry. MacLachlan graduated from the University of Washington in 1982. The darkly handsome actor made his feature film debut when he starred in the big-budget David Lynch adaptation of Frank Herbert&apos;s Dune (1984), but only enjoyed real success after appearing in a second Lynch project, the moody and perverse classic, Blue Velvet (1986).The following year saw MacLachlan appearing as an otherworldly FBI agent in the cult classic sci-fi film, The Hidden (1987). This turned out to be a sign of things to come, as MacLachlan soon took on another oddball G-man, &quot;Special Agent Dale Cooper&quot;, on Lynch&apos;s cryptic ABC-TV series, Twin Peaks (1990), perhaps, along with Blue Velvet (1986), his most famous role. MacLachlan&apos;s remarkable work as Agent Cooper earned him a Golden Globe award and a pair of Emmy nominations, as well as steady work in television and films, including a part as Ray Manzarek in the Oliver Stone film, The Doors (1991), and villain &quot;Cliff Vandercave&quot; in the live action version of The Flintstones (1994).His career took a hit after he appeared in the infamous flop, Showgirls (1995). However, MacLachlan returned to prominence in the early 2000s with a re-occurring role on HBO&apos;s Sex and the City (1998), as well as a starring role in the TV movie, The Spring (2000), and a turn as &quot;Claudius&quot; in director Michael Almereyda&apos;s version of Hamlet (2000). MacLachlan later took advantage of his resemblance to Cary Grant, when he played the classic actor&apos;s spirit in Touch of Pink (2004).MacLachlan has remained a popular actor with independent filmmakers, and he has also been a familiar face on television, appearing on the ABC-TV shows, In Justice (2006) and Desperate Housewives (2004).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>178</ID>
<Name>Lana Parrilla</Name>
<Description>Lana Parrilla was born on July 15, 1977 in Brooklyn, New York City, New York, USA as Lana Maria Parilla. She is an actress, known for Once Upon a Time (2011), Spiders (2000) and Boomtown (2002). She has been married to Fred di Blasio since July 5, 2014.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>179</ID>
<Name>Laura Leighton</Name>
<Description>Laura Leighton was born on July 24, 1968 in Iowa City, Iowa, USA as Laura Miller. She is an actress, known for Pretty Little Liars (2010), Melrose Place (1992) and Seven Girlfriends (1999). She has been married to Doug Savant since May 1998. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>180</ID>
<Name>Lee Arenberg</Name>
<Description>Lee Arenberg has the remarkable ability to morph himself into frightening aliens, twisted psychotherapists, lascivious entertainment executives and everything in between. Most frequently referred to as a character actor, Arenberg maintains a flourishing acting career--almost 20 years spanning television, stage and film. Arenberg has appeared in more than 30 movies, including Cradle Will Rock (1999), RoboCop 3 (1993), Waterworld (1995), Bob Roberts (1992), The Apocalypse (1997), Cross My Heart (1987) and the fantasy adventure feature Dungeons &amp; Dragons (2000). Bitten by the acting bug at age eight when he portrayed David in his Hebrew school play, &quot;Killing Goliath&quot;, Arenberg notes that the parable &quot;could be the title of any actor&apos;s chances in this game.&quot; A native Angeleno, Lee attended Santa Monica high school with &quot;brat packers&quot; Sean Penn, Robert Downey Jr. and Emilio Estevez, and co-wrote a play with Estevez which was directed by Penn. Lee&apos;s first professional job was in 1986 at the Mark Taper Forum in &quot;Ghetto&quot;, a play directed by Gordon Davidson. Within weeks he was cast in three films, including the role of Norton in the feature Tapeheads (1988)opposite Tim Robbins and John Cusack. Guest appearances on television began in 1987 with the hit sitcom Perfect Strangers (1986), and have continued with memorable roles such as the parking space-stealing New Yorker on Seinfeld (1989) and as the murderous rock promoter opposite Katey Sagal and Sam Kinison in Tales from the Crypt (1989), as well as roles on Arli$$ (1996), Friends (1994), Star Trek: The Next Generation (1987), Star Trek: Deep Space Nine (1993) and Star Trek: Voyager (1995). Arenberg can also be seen in the role of the notoriously huge studio head, Bobby G., on the controversial syndicated comedy Action (1999) opposite series star Jay Mohr. Arenberg names his family and friends as his inspirations, and states that having grown up on Los Angeles&apos; Westside, he was able to see actors as the parents of friends and classmates, not as just as movie stars. &quot;It also gave me an honest assessment of the industry and what I was getting myself into,&quot; he laughs. He credits &quot;fear of failure&quot; as his main motivation, and admires the talents and creativity of such legendary actors Paul Muni, Lon Chaney and Boris Karloff. Lee also credits much of his development as an actor to his participation in the Actors&apos; Gang, one of Los Angeles&apos; oldest theater companies. The Actors&apos; Gang was founded by Lee in 1981 with Tim Robbins and other friends from UCLA. After 20 years as an actor in the group, Lee recently made his writing and directing debut with Foursome, a play about golf, sex and witchcraft. In his leisure time, Arenberg enjoys golf, cooking, blues harmonica, video games and pitching for his softball team Bubblin&apos; Crude, which is made up of other actors, many of whom are friends from high school. He is involved with St. Jude&apos;s Children&apos;s Hospital and other children&apos;s health causes, and animal rights organizations, participating regularly in fund raising efforts on behalf of those charitable causes.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>181</ID>
<Name>Leighton Meester</Name>
<Description>Leighton Marissa Meester was born in Fort Worth, Texas, to Constance (Haas) and Douglas Meester. Although born in Texas when her mother was serving a jail sentence for her part in a marijuana-smuggling ring, Meester spent her early years in Marco Island, Florida with her grandparents. There, she became involved with the local playhouse and made her stage debut in a production of &quot;The Wizard of Oz&quot;.She moved to New York with her mother at the age of 11 and was soon working as a model and appearing in TV commercials. A few years later, at age 14, she and her mother moved again, this time to Los Angeles where she soon began to pick up TV work, making her debut in Law &amp; Order: Disciple (1999).A steady stream of TV work followed until in 2007 she landed the role in Gossip Girl (2007) which made her famous. This led to more TV and movie work, and in 2009 she launched a recording career with a single entitled, &quot;Somebody to Love&quot;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>182</ID>
<Name>Lena Headey</Name>
<Description>Lena Headey is a British actress, she was born in Bermuda, to parents from Yorkshire, England, where she was also raised. She is the daughter of Sue and John Headey, a police officer. Headey is best-known for her role as &quot;Cersei Lannister&quot; in Game of Thrones (2011) (2011-present) and The Brothers Grimm (2005), Possession (2002), and The Remains of the Day (1993). Headey stars as &quot;Queen Gorgo&quot;, a heroic Spartan woman in the period film, 300 (2006), by director Zack Snyder.Headey was born in Hamilton, Bermuda, to British parents Sue and John Headey. Her father, a Yorkshire police cadet, was sent to Bermuda shortly before her birth. She was raised there, living by the ocean until she was five. Back in England, she was brought up in Yorkshire before moving to London in her teens. Headey had not gone to drama school before she became an actress. At the age of 17, Headey&apos;s performance in a one-off show in the company of six school friends caught the attention of a casting agent, who took a photo and asked her to audition. Eventually, Headey was cast in Waterland (1992), which became her big-screen debut. She honed her natural acting talent while filming and also took archery classes and horse training. She also took boxing classes in clubs in south London, where a former boxer had been teaching her to spar. During her film career, spanning over 15 years, Headey has shown her range in a variety of roles, playing characters from Amazon-type warriors and action-minded women in The Cave (2005) and The Brothers Grimm (2005), to a lesbian florist in Imagine Me &amp; You (2005).Headey&apos;s film career has taken her all over the world. She was in India for the filming of The Jungle Book (1994), then in St. Petersburg, Russia, for filming Onegin (1999), and in Norway for filming of Aberdeen (2000). In 2005 Headey was filming in Romania and in Mexico, then spent four months in Prague, Czech Republic, where a forest was designed and built for filming The Brothers Grimm (2005), with Matt Damon and Heath Ledger. During 2006 Headey was in Canada for the filming of 300 (2006), then went to locations in Bulgaria for shooting The Contractor (2007), and Germany and in Czech Republic for the filming of Der rote Baron (2008).She also played Gina McVey in the horror thriller The Broken (2008), and Elizabeth in Tell-Tale (2009). In addition to her film-work, Heady appeared as Sarah Connor in a TV spin-off of the popular &quot;Terminator&quot; film franchise, the FOX&apos;s television series Terminator: The Sarah Connor Chronicles (2008).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>183</ID>
<Name>Leo Bill</Name>
<Description>Leo Bill was born on August 31, 1980 in Warwickshire, England. He is an actor, known for Alice in Wonderland (2010), 28 Days Later... (2002) and The Girl with the Dragon Tattoo (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>184</ID>
<Name>Lesley Fera</Name>
<Description>A native Californian, Lesley was born on November 23, 1971. Perhaps best known for her role as Veronica Hastings on the hit television series Pretty Little Liars, Lesley is also known for her recurring roles on Southland, 24, C.S.I. Miami, and Justice. A lover of the stage, she is very active in L.A. theatre and has also enjoyed working at numerous regional theaters.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>185</ID>
<Name>Liam Cunningham</Name>
<Description>Irish actor Liam Cunningham was an electrician in the mid 80&apos;s. He saw an ad for an acting school and he decided to give acting a try. His first film role was as a policeman in &quot;Into the West.&quot; Since then, he has been involved in many films and theater productions on both sides of the Atlantic.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>186</ID>
<Name>Liam Garrigan</Name>
<Description>Liam Garrigan was born in Kingston upon Hull, East Riding of Yorkshire, England. He developed an interest in theatre at an early age taking part in amateur theatre around the age of five and also attended youth classes at Hull&apos;s Northern Stage Company. Later he attended Hull&apos;s Wyke College and then trained as a professional actor at Guildhall School of Music and Drama in London. Garrigan has become a notable Theatre and Television actor making appearances in several BBC television drama series as well as in RTE&apos;s &quot;Raw&quot; and Starz TV&apos;s miniseries &quot;The Pillars of the Earth&quot;. Aside from his love for theatre, Garrigan also enjoys surfing.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>187</ID>
<Name>Liam Hemsworth</Name>
<Description>Liam Hemsworth was born on January 13, 1990, in Melbourne, Australia, and is the younger brother of actors Chris Hemsworth and Luke Hemsworth. He is the son of Leonie (van Os), a teacher of English, and Craig Hemsworth, a social-services counselor. He is of Dutch (from his immigrant maternal grandfather), Irish, English, Scottish, and German ancestry. His uncle, by marriage, was Rod Ansell, the bushman who inspired the film Crocodile Dundee (1986).The Hemsworth family lived primarily on Phillip Island, a small island located south of Melbourne. Following in the footsteps of his older brothers, who went into acting in their teens, Liam scored his first audition at age 16 and appeared on the Australian TV series Home and Away (1988) and McLeod&apos;s Daughters (2001) before taking on a recurring character role on the soap opera Neighbours (1985), in which his brother Luke had also appeared. Roles on TV shows The Elephant Princess (2008) and Satisfaction (2007) followed before Liam moved to the United States to pursue a big-screen career.After suffering two setbacks - his character was written out of the script for The Expendables (2010) days before filming and he lost the title role of Thor (2011) to his brother Chris - Liam was cast opposite Miley Cyrus in the Nicholas Sparks drama The Last Song (2010). The two, who played love interests in the film, soon started dating, and Liam appeared in Cyrus&apos; music video &quot;When I Look at You.&quot; Following that film&apos;s modest commercial success, and the attendant press coverage of his rising career and high-profile romance, he was almost immediately thrust into leading man status, and was cast as Gale Hawthorne in the big-screen adaptation of the best-selling novel The Hunger Games (2012). Following the blockbuster success of that film, Liam nabbed a number of roles, including a supporting part in The Expendables 2 (2012) and leading roles in the war drama Love and Honor (2013), the crime drama Empire State (2013), and the thriller Paranoia (2013). He will also star as Ali Baba in a 3D production of Arabian Nights and will reprise the role of Gale Hawthorne in The Hunger Games: Catching Fire (2013).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>188</ID>
<Name>Lindsay Duncan</Name>
<Description>Lindsay Duncan was born on November 7, 1950 in Edinburgh, Scotland as Lindsay Vere Duncan. She is known for her work on About Time (2013), Birdman or (The Unexpected Virtue of Ignorance) (2014) and Alice in Wonderland (2010). She is married to Hilton McRae. They have one child.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>189</ID>
<Name>Lindsey Shaw</Name>
<Description>Lindsey Shaw was born in Lincoln, Nebraska. Before relocating to Los Angeles to pursue acting, Lindsey and her mother traveled from Lincoln to Kansas City twice a month to do local print ads and commercials. In 2002, Shaw and her mother moved to Los Angeles. Almost immediately, Lindsey was introduced to acting teacher Jeremiah Comey, who has been her mentor ever since. Jerry referred Lindsey to her longtime manager, Pat Cutler, of Cutler Management. Shaw landed her first big role in Ned&apos;s Declassified School Survival Guide (2004), playing &apos;Jennifer &quot;Moze&quot; Mosely&apos;, the best friend and next-door neighbor of the show&apos;s main character, &quot;Ned Bigby&quot;. Shaw next appeared as popular younger sister &quot;Claire&quot; in the CW&apos;s short-lived sitcom, Aliens in America (2007). Lindsey most recently played &quot;Kat&quot; in ABC Family&apos;s revival of the 1999 rom-com, 10 Things I Hate About You (2009).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>190</ID>
<Name>Lucy Hale</Name>
<Description>Lucy Hale is an American actress and singer. She was born Karen Lucille Hale in Memphis, Tennessee, to Julia (Caperton) Knight and John Preston Hale. She started out as a singer, appearing on American Juniors (2003) in a search for band members. She successfully won her place in the band. The group disbanded in 2005. Lucy turned to acting. She is best known for roles in TV shows Privileged (2008) and Pretty Little Liars (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>191</ID>
<Name>Madeleine Stowe</Name>
<Description>Madeleine Stowe was born in Los Angeles, California, to Mireya Maria (Mora Steinvorth) and Robert Alfred Stowe, a civil engineer. Her mother was a from a prominent political family in Costa Rica, while her father was of English and German ancestry. Stowe grew up in Eagle Rock, a working-class neighborhood of Los Angeles. At age ten she started practicing for a career as a concert pianist and trained every day for hours. However, when her instructor died in 1976 she more or less quit playing.She went to University of Southern California and studied cinema and journalism before taking up acting at Beverly Hills&apos; Solaris Theater. She made a few appearances in TV and on film but her breakthrough came in 1987 with Stakeout (1987). Other major credits include The Last of the Mohicans (1992) and Short Cuts (1993).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>192</ID>
<Name>Madison De La Garza</Name>
<Description>Madison De La Garza was born to Eddie DeLaGarza and Dianna Hart on December 28, 2001 in Dallas, Texas. She is the maternal younger half-sister of Demi Lovato and Dallas Lovato. She is best known for her role as &quot;Juanita Solis&quot; on Desperate Housewives (2004). Madison has been made fun of for her weight but her sister, Demi Lovato, has spoken out about her and her own bullying/weight issues.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>193</ID>
<Name>Maiara Walsh</Name>
<Description>Maiara Walsh was born on February 18, 1988 in Seattle, Washington, USA. She is an actress, known for The Starving Games (2013), Cory in the House (2007) and Zombieland (2013).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>194</ID>
<Name>Maisie Williams</Name>
<Description>Maisie Williams was born on April 15, 1997 in Bristol, England as Margaret Constance Williams. She is an actress and publicist, known for Game of Thrones (2011), Cyberbully (2015) and The Falling (2014).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>195</ID>
<Name>Marcia Cross</Name>
<Description>Marcia Anne Cross was born on March 25, 1962 in Marlborough, Massachusetts. As a child, Marcia always wanted to be an actress, so she set out to have a career in acting. Cross graduated from the Julliard School in New York, a naturally gifted girl. Her career began in 1984, when she joined the cast of the daytime soap opera The Edge of Night (1956). After six months, the show ended its 28-year run. The following year, in 1985, she starred opposite Carroll O&apos;Connor in the television film Brass (1985). Then she landed the lead role in Pros &amp; Cons (1986) with comedienne Sheryl Lee Ralph. She kept busy by starring in The Last Days of Frank and Jesse James (1986) with many famous figures in Hollywood - including June Carter Cash, Willie Nelson, Johnny Cash and Kris Kristofferson. Marcia&apos;s career was looking up when she was cast as Kate Roberts in another daytime soap opera, One Life to Live (1968), and as Tanya in Another World (1964). Marcia was then seen opposite Tim Daly in the tearjerker romance Almost Grown (1988). Almost Grown (1988) was a television pilot that never got picked up, but is still very acclaimed to this day. Marcia was then cast as Ruth Fielding in Bad Influence (1990), a thriller that starred Cross, Rob Lowe and James Spader.She joined the cast of Knots Landing (1979) - an incredibly famous nighttime soap opera in 1991. After a year, she left to do work on a new television series called Melrose Place (1992). She was cast as the psychotic Dr. Kimberly Shaw on the prime-time soap opera. The show was a pop-culture phenomenon, going down in history as one of the most entertaining and memorable shows of the 1990s. Marcia, who was starring opposite Heather Locklear, Courtney Thorne-Smith and others, emerged as the fan favorite of the show. Then her longtime companion and fiancé, Richard Jordan, died in 1993. Marcia reigned on, starring in films like Female Perversions (1996) opposite Tilda Swinton and Always Say Goodbye (1997) opposite Emmy-nominee Polly Draper, throughout her long run on &quot;Melrose Place&quot;. In 1997, she left the show in order to get her Master&apos;s Degree in Psychology. From 1997 to 2003, she continued to act regularly. She starred in Dancing in September (2000).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>196</ID>
<Name>Margaret Colin</Name>
<Description>Margaret Colin was born in Brooklyn, New York and raised on Long Island. She graduated from Baldwin Senior High School in 1976. Margaret began acting in The Edge of Night (1956) (her character was a heiress and former terrorist, with seven murder attempts), and was employed next on As the World Turns (1956), portraying character Margo Montgomery. Margaret&apos;s first film appearance were as a teacher in John Hughes&apos;s Pretty in Pink (1986), followed by a role in Jonathan Demme&apos;s Something Wild (1986), where she played Irene, girlfriend to Ray Liotta&apos;s character. The following year, she had supporting roles in Like Father Like Son (1987), and 3 Men and a Baby (1987). In film, Margaret either had minor, or supporting, roles; it&apos;s her work in television that perhaps makes her most memorable. Ms Colin continued acting with parts in Chicago Hope (1994), and The Wright Verdicts (1995). In 2000, Margaret earned a Saturn Award for Best Genre TV Actress for her role as Lisa Wiseman in the series Now and Again (1999). From 2007 to 2013, she played Eleanor Waldorf in the series Gossip Girl (2007).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>197</ID>
<Name>Margarita Levieva</Name>
<Description>Margarita Levieva is an American actress. Born in the Soviet Union. Levieva, was born in Leningrad, Russian Soviet Federative Socialist Republic, (now Saint Petersburg, Russian Federation). At the age of three, she began the rigorous training program of a competitive rhythmic gymnast. Levieva continued to train for the next 13 years, winning competitions in Russia and eventually going on to compete in the United States after emigrating. When she was 11, Levieva&apos;s mother moved her and her twin brother to Sheepshead Bay, Brooklyn in New York City. She attended high school in Secaucus, New Jersey. Levieva majored in economics at NYU and worked as a fashion buyer. Her continuing interest in acting led her to be accepted into the Meisner Training Program at the William Esper Studio. In 2005, New York Magazine featured her as one of the 50 Most Beautiful People in New York.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>198</ID>
<Name>Mark Moses</Name>
<Description>Mark Moses was born in New York City and grew up in Evanston, Illinois. He played quarterback for his high school in Evanston, and went on to play another year at Ithaca College, in upstate New York, where he majored in English before dropping out and traveling abroad. Mark then got into NYU&apos;s Tisch School of the Arts and graduated with a degree in theater. He immediately landed a role in the Broadway production, &quot;Slab Boys&quot;, with Sean Penn and Kevin Bacon, and was working off-Broadway and in regional theaters when he met Oliver Stone, who cast him as &quot;Lt. Wolfe&quot; in the academy award-winning film, Platoon (1986). Oliver also cast Mark in Born on the Fourth of July (1989) and The Doors (1991). He played a club owner who dies by ice-pick in Ridley Scott&apos;s Someone to Watch Over Me (1987), charged down Little Round Top in Gettysburg (1993), charged up San Juan Hill in Rough Riders (1997) and gave a pearl-handled revolver to a future enemy in Clint Eastwood&apos;s Letters from Iwo Jima (2006). Mark played Kris Kristofferson&apos;s son in the HBO western, The Tracker (1988), announced the world was coming to an end in Deep Impact (1998), played the bad guy in Big Momma&apos;s House 2 (2006) and played &quot;Attorney General Wyatt&quot; in Swing Vote (2008). He&apos;s appeared in numerous television shows, including a recurring role in Grand (1990), as Pamela Reed&apos;s boyfriend, the role of &quot;Matt Parker&quot; in NBC&apos;s short-lived comedy, The Single Guy (1995), many of David E. Kelley&apos;s legal dramas, and played &quot;Paul Young&quot; in the ABC television smash hit, Desperate Housewives (2004). He plays the alcohol-challenged, &quot;Duck Philips&quot;, on the Emmy award-winning drama, Mad Men (2007).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>199</ID>
<Name>Mark Ruffalo</Name>
<Description>Ruffalo won NY success in Lonergan&apos;s play &quot;This Is Our Youth&quot;, which led to the male lead in Lonergan&apos;s film You Can Count on Me (2000), playing the ne&apos;er-do-well brother of Laura Linney. The performance drew rave reviews and invited comparisons to an early Marlon Brando. Notable roles in The Last Castle (2001), XX/XY (2002), and Windtalkers (2002) followed, although in 2002 Ruffalo was diagnosed with an acoustic neuroma, a type of brain tumor. Though the tumor was benign, the resulting surgery led to a period of partial facial paralysis, from which he fully recovered. In 2003, Ruffalo scored leading roles alongside two popular female stars, playing a police detective opposite Meg Ryan in In the Cut (2003) and the love interest of Gwyneth Paltrow in the comedy View from the Top (2003). Though both films were high-profile box office disappointments, Ruffalo went on to four notable (if highly disparate) films in 2004 - We Don&apos;t Live Here Anymore (2004), Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind (2004), 13 Going on 30 (2004), and Collateral (2004) - which solidified his ability to be both a popular leading man and an acclaimed ensemble player in either comedy or drama.After 2004, Ruffalo was consistently at work, with leads in popular Hollywood films and independent productions that continued to solidify him as one of film&apos;s most consistently strong actors: Just Like Heaven (2005), All the King&apos;s Men (2006), Zodiac (2007), Reservation Road (2007), and The Brothers Bloom (2008). In 2010 Ruffalo achieved something of a breakthrough, by directing the indie film Sympathy for Delicious (2010), which won him the Special Jury Prize at the Sundance Film Festival, and co-starring as the sperm-donor father to lesbian couple Annette Bening and Julianne Moore in The Kids Are All Right (2010). His role in the idiosyncratic domestic comedy/drama earned him Academy Award, Independent Spirit Award, Screen Actors Guild, and BAFTA nominations for Best Supporting Actor.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>200</ID>
<Name>Mark Stanley</Name>
<Description>Mark Stanley is an actor, known for Star Wars: Episode VII - The Force Awakens (2015), Kajaki (2014) and Game of Thrones (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>201</ID>
<Name>Mason Vale Cotton</Name>
<Description>Mason Vale Cotton is an actor, known for Desperate Housewives (2004), Mad Men (2007) and Prep &amp; Landing (2009).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>202</ID>
<Name>Matt Lucas</Name>
<Description>Matt Lucas was born on March 5, 1974 in Paddington, London, England as Matthew Richard Lucas. He is an actor and writer, known for Alice in Wonderland (2010), Bridesmaids (2011) and Little Britain (2003). He was previously married to Kevin McGee.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>203</ID>
<Name>Matt Smith</Name>
<Description>Matt Smith is an English actor who shot to fame in the UK aged 26 when he was cast by producer Steven Moffat as the Eleventh Doctor in the BBC&apos;s iconic science-fiction adventure series Doctor Who (2005).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>204</ID>
<Name>Matthew Settle</Name>
<Description>Matthew Settle continues to evolve into a respected actor of Stage and Screen. Known in households, around the world, for his work in the cultural phenomenon, Gossip Girl (2007), as &quot;Rufus Humphrey&quot;, as well as the celebrated &quot;Capt. Ronald Speirs&quot; from the Emmy and Golden Globe award-winning Band of Brothers (2001), Settle has worked with such notables as Steven Spielberg, Sir David Frost, Jonathan Mostow and Peter Bogdanovich.Settle recently appeared as the lead character, &quot;Billy Flynn&quot;, in Broadway&apos;s &quot;Chicago&quot; for 64 acclaimed performances. He was nominated for a teen choice award for his role in Gossip Girl (2007) and shares an award with Steven Spielberg for his portrayal as the lead &quot;Jacob Wheeler&quot; in TNT&apos;s Emmy award-winning mini-series, Into the West (2005).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>205</ID>
<Name>Max Carver</Name>
<Description>Max Carver was born in San Francisco, CA to parents Robert Martensen, a doctor and writer, and Anne Carver, a philanthropist and community activist. He made his acting debut with his twin brother, Charlie, in the ABC hit television series, Desperate Housewives. They played sons to Felicity Huffman and Doug Savant. Carver has also guest starred on a number of shows, including NBC&apos;s The Office and Nickelodeon&apos;s Victorious.In 2012, Carver graduated from the University of Southern California with a bachelor&apos;s degree in English. Next year, he will make his film debut opposite Britt Robertson in the novel adaptation of Undiscovered Gyrl, written and directed by Allison Burnett.Currently, Carver recurs as a pair of twin Alpha werewolves in Season 3 of MTV&apos;s Teen Wolf. He resides in Los Angeles and is represented by Rebel Entertainment Partners and Sweeney Entertainment.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>206</ID>
<Name>Meghan Ory</Name>
<Description>Meghan Ory is a Canadian actress, she was born in Victoria, British Columbia. She Started acting in theater before her teens, but was prohibited by her mother-a drama teacher-from auditioning for film and TV roles until she could pay for her own head shots. She also made film debut in The Darklings, a 1999 cable movie starring Suzanne Somers and Timothy Bus-field. She Has written a series of teen books called Chronicles of the Girl Wars, inspired by her experiences in high school, that she has described as &quot;Mean Girls meets Ugly Betty.&quot; She and her husband were accepted to study Shakespeare at the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art in London in the summer of 2012.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>207</ID>
<Name>Merrin Dungey</Name>
<Description>Merrin Dungey was born on August 6, 1971 in Sacramento, California, USA. She is an actress, known for Alias (2001), Deep Impact (1998) and The King of Queens (1998). She has been married to Matthew Drake since May 2007. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>208</ID>
<Name>Mia Wasikowska</Name>
<Description>Mia is an Australian actress, born and raised in the country&apos;s capital, Canberra. She is the daughter of photographers Marzena Wasikowska and John Reid. Her mother is Polish and her father is an Australian of British ancestry. She has an older sister, Jess, and a younger brother, Kai. At age eight, her family moved to Poland for a year.At age nine, Mia took ballet classes with dreams of becoming a professional ballerina. However, an injury prevented this from happening and she quit at age fourteen. Mia turned to acting, having been excited by European and Australian cinema. She was attending Canberra High School, but left to pursue her career as an actor.She had just turned 15 when she landed the role of Lilya in Suburban Mayhem (2006). Her breakthrough role came when she was cast as Alice in Tim Burton&apos;s Alice in Wonderland (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>209</ID>
<Name>Michael Coleman</Name>
<Description>Best known for his role as Happy on ABC&apos;s Once Upon a Time (2011) he has also played memorable characters on Supernatural, Smallville, Fringe, Stargate, Blood Ties, and Eureka. As a voice-over artist he has voices hundreds of commercials roles and voiced characters in X-Men: Evolution, Hello Kitty, Inuyasha, Dragonball Z, Mary-Kate &amp; Ashley in Action, Hamtaro, Gundam Seed: Destiny and many more. </Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>210</ID>
<Name>Michael Raymond-James</Name>
<Description>Michael Raymond-James was born on December 24, 1977 in Michigan, USA as Michael Weverstad. He is an actor and director, known for Jack Reacher (2012), Black Snake Moan (2006) and The Finest Hours (2016).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>211</ID>
<Name>Michael Socha</Name>
<Description>Michael Robert Socha is an actor, known for his role as Tom in Being Human (2008).He was born December 13, 1987 in Derby, Derbyshire, England, to Kathleen (Lyons) and Robert Socha, and has Polish and British ancestry. Socha was a rebellious pupil who often skipped school. At the age of 11, he unsuccessfully auditioned for the lead role in a school musical play, but won the lead role of Bugsy Malone in another play years later.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>212</ID>
<Name>Michelle Fairley</Name>
<Description>Michelle was born in July 1965, the second child of publican Brian and nurse Theresa Fairley. As a teenager she attended the Ulster Youth Theatre before moving to Belfast , where she was a member of Fringe Benefit, a repertory company where she acted alongside Conleth Hill, with whom she would later appear in television juggernaut &apos;Game of Thrones&apos;. In 1986 she came to London and established herself as a considerable stage actress in &apos;Oleanna &apos;at the Royal Court, &apos;Dancing at Lughnasa&apos; at the Old Vic, as Lady Macbeth with the West Yorkshire Playhouse and as Emilia, wife of the villainous Iago in the Donmar Warehouse&apos;s production of &apos;Othello&apos;, for which she was nominated for an Olivier award and on the strength of which she was offered the part of the fiercely matriarchal Lady Stark in &apos;Game of Thrones&apos;. Following that character&apos;s demise she appeared in several American television series - &apos;24&apos;, &apos;Suits&apos; and &apos;The Lizzie Borden Chronicles &apos; - as well as playing the wife of (Southern) Irish Brendan Gleeson in the epic period film &apos;In the Heart of the Sea&apos;. In 2015 she returned to Britain to appear in the play &apos;Splendour&apos; in London and the television series &apos;Rebellion&apos; chronicling the 1916 Easter Rising.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>213</ID>
<Name>Michelle Gomez</Name>
<Description>Michelle Gomez was born on November 23, 1966 in Glasgow, Scotland. She is known for her work on The Acid House (1998), Green Wing (2004) and The Wedding Video (2012). She has been married to Jack Davenport since May 1, 2000. They have one child.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>214</ID>
<Name>Michelle Trachtenberg</Name>
<Description>Trachtenberg grew up in Brooklyn and started her acting career young; she began appearing in commercials at the age of 3.She continued to act and dance through her school years, making regular television appearances from the age of 10. She landed a recurring role in the kids&apos; TV show The Adventures of Pete &amp; Pete (1992) and starred in Harriet the Spy (1996), but it was her role as Buffy&apos;s sister Dawn from the fifth season of Buffy the Vampire Slayer (1997) that really brought her to worldwide attention, and all before she was 18 years old.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>215</ID>
<Name>Mig Macario</Name>
<Description>With nearly 25 years experience in the entertainment industry, he has appeared in over 40 Film and Television projects; working with artists such as Johnny Depp, Maury Chaykin, Paul Sorvino, Dean McDermott and super mom come activist Jenny McCarthy. Mig made history when he was cast as George Amahit on the Gemini award winning, dark comedy &quot;Less Than Kind&quot;. It&apos;s the first comedic series regular role written specifically for a Filipino in Canada if not North America.Recent projects find him recurring on not just one but two hit series! You&apos;ll see his familiar face on TV&apos;s blockbuster FRINGE for Fox and Nickelodeon&apos;s The Troop. He&apos;ll also be seen opposite Aaron Douglas (The Bridge, Battlestar Galactica) and a stellar cast including Emanuelle Vaugier (Two and a Half Men, CSI NY), Paul Campbell, Torrance Coombs, Andrew Airlie and Crystal Lowe in Killer Mountain airing on the SyFy network.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>216</ID>
<Name>Nan Zhang</Name>
<Description>Nan Zhang was born on November 1, 1986 in Anhui, China. She is an actress, known for Gossip Girl (2007), Shanghai Hotel (2011) and West 32nd (2007).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>217</ID>
<Name>Natalie Dormer</Name>
<Description>Natalie Dormer born 11 February 1982 is an English actress. She is best known for her roles as Anne Boleyn on the Showtime series The Tudors (2007-10), as Margaery Tyrell on the HBO series Game of Thrones (2012-present), Irene Adler on the CBS series Elementary (2013-15), and as Cressida in the science-fiction adventure films The Hunger Games: Mockingjay - Part 1 (2014) and Part 2 (2015). She has been nominated for Best Performance at the Gemini Awards for her work in The Tudors. She has also been nominated for a Screen Actor&apos;s Guild Award for her performance in Game of Thrones.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>218</ID>
<Name>Nathalie Emmanuel</Name>
<Description>Nathalie Joanne Emmanuel is an English actress, known for playing Ramsey in &apos;Furious 7&apos; (2015).Nathalie was born in Southend-on-Sea, Essex, England, to a father of Saint Lucian and English descent and a mother of Dominican origin. Nathalie credits her mother for the initial motivation to become an actress. At the age of 10, she played Young Nala in the West End production of The Lion King. In 2006, she made her television break by starring as Sasha Valentine in the teen soap opera Hollyoaks. Emmanuel appeared on the show until 2010, her character&apos;s story-lines included prostitution, and heroin addiction.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>219</ID>
<Name>Neal McDonough</Name>
<Description>Neal McDonough was born on February 13, 1966 in Dorchester, Massachusetts, to Catherine (Bushe) and Frank McDonough, motel owners who were born in Ireland. He grew up in Barnstable, Massachusetts, graduated from Barnstable High School, and attended Syracuse University. He was a member of the Sigma Chi Fraternity and graduated with a Bachelor&apos;s degree in Fine Arts in 1988. McDonough frequently appeared as Captain Laser, inspiring young students to bring their studies to completion. Fron there, he trained for a short time at the London Academy of Music and Dramatic Art. McDonough has made many television and film appearances since 1991, including Star Trek: First Contact (1996), Minority Report (2002), Timeline (2003), Walking Tall (2004), The Guardian (2006) and Flags of Our Fathers (2006). His most recent television appearances include Band of Brothers (2001), Boomtown (2002) Desperate Housewives (2004), Medical Investigation (2004), Tin Man (2007) and Justified (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>220</ID>
<Name>Neve McIntosh</Name>
<Description>Neve McIntosh was born on April 9, 1972 in Paisley, Scotland as Carol McIntosh. She is an actress, known for Rare Books and Manuscripts (2005), Plunkett &amp; Macleane (1999) and Lady Audley&apos;s Secret (2000).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>221</ID>
<Name>Nia Peeples</Name>
<Description>She accompanied a friend to a rehearsal one day and was spotted by the producers, who cast her in the play &quot;Music Shop&quot;. This led to guest appearances in such TV series as Hardcastle and McCormick (1983) and T.J. Hooker (1982). Her first starring role came when she played a deaf girl opposite William Atherton in the HBO film A Single Light (1981). She auditioned for and won the part of Nicole Chapman in the series Fame (1982). Her hobbies include hiking, tandem surfing, rollerblading and skiing. She also does a lot of charity work. She is of Scottish/Filipino descent.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>222</ID>
<Name>Nicholas Briggs</Name>
<Description>Nicholas Briggs was born on September 29, 1961 in London, England. He is an actor and writer, known for Doctor Who (2005), Auton 2: Sentinel (1998) and The Stranger: In Memory Alone (1993).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>223</ID>
<Name>Nick Wechsler</Name>
<Description>Nick Wechsler has been building a quality career as an actor since he was a teen. Currently and most notably, he plays series regular, Jack Porter, on the ABC&apos;s Critics&apos; Choice nominated series &quot;Revenge,&quot; premiering soon for season two. Nick quickly became a fan favorite on the series for his brooding, dramatic but surprisingly funny personality, which has been compared to that of James Franco.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>224</ID>
<Name>Nicole Fiscella</Name>
<Description>Nicole Fiscella was born on September 15, 1979 in Rochester, New York, USA. She is an actress, known for Gossip Girl (2007) and Luxury Unveiled (2006).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>225</ID>
<Name>Nicollette Sheridan</Name>
<Description>Nicollette Sheridan has won a worldwide audience with her past television and film roles. She exploded on the small screen with her Golden Globe-nominated role of &quot;Edie Britt&quot;, the blonde bombshell of Wisteria Lane, on ABC&apos;s hit show Desperate Housewives (2004). Sheridan was honored in her native England, receiving the 2006 Glamour Women of the Year Award for Best U.S. TV Actress, adding to her back-to-back 2005-2006 Screen Actors Guild Awards.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>226</ID>
<Name>Nikolaj Coster-Waldau</Name>
<Description>Nikolaj Coster-Waldau was born on July 27, 1970 in Rudkøbing, Denmark. He is an actor and producer, known for Game of Thrones (2011), Oblivion (2013) and Mama (2013). He has been married to Nukâka since 1998. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>227</ID>
<Name>Noel Clarke</Name>
<Description>Noel Clarke was born on December 6, 1975 in London, England as Noel Anthony Clarke. He is an actor and writer, known for Star Trek Into Darkness (2013), Adulthood (2008) and Kidulthood (2006). He is married to Iris Da-Silva. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>228</ID>
<Name>Nolan North</Name>
<Description>Nolan North was born on October 31, 1970 in New Haven, Connecticut, USA as Nolan Ramsay North. He is known for his work on General Hospital (1963), Uncharted 2: Among Thieves (2009) and Uncharted 3: Drake&apos;s Deception (2011). He has been married to Jill Murray since June 4, 1999. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>229</ID>
<Name>Olivia Steele Falconer</Name>
<Description>Olivia Steele Falconer is an actress, known for Red Riding Hood (2011), The Client List (2010) and Crowsnest (2012).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>230</ID>
<Name>Parker Croft</Name>
<Description>Parker Croft grew up in Vermont, and now lives in Los Angeles. Falling Overnight was his screenwriting debut as well as his first leading role. His performance earned him Best Actor Awards at the Nashville Film Festival, the Jax Film Fest, The Blue Whiskey Independent Film Festival, and earned him the Jack Nance Breakthrough Performance Award at the Visionfest Film Festival.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>231</ID>
<Name>Pat Crawford Brown</Name>
<Description>Pat Crawford Brown was born on June 29, 1929 in New York City, New York, USA. She is an actress, known for Stuck on You (2003), Daredevil (2003) and Sister Act (1992).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>232</ID>
<Name>Patrick Dempsey</Name>
<Description>He made his movie debut in the secondary part of a Catholic student in the 1960s-era school-age comedy Heaven Help Us (1985) starring &quot;Brat Pack&quot; actor Andrew McCarthy. More silliness followed with Meatballs III: Summer Job (1986) and a ripe turn in the socially aware television-movie Disneyland: A Fighting Choice (1986) in which he played an epileptic teen who sues his parents (Beau Bridges and Karen Valentine) in order to have risky brain surgery. Around the same time, he found himself in a television series entitled Fast Times (1986), based on the ultimate school-age film Fast Times at Ridgemont High (1982), which made a star out of Sean Penn. Inheriting the Robert Romanus cool guy role of con artist Mike Damone, expectations were far too big and the television series died a quick death.However, his movie career got on a faster track and he scored well co-starring with the worldly Beverly D&apos;Angelo in the movie In the Mood (1987), as a young man who makes headlines pursuing older women. Life resembled art that same year when Patrick married actress and drama coach Rocky Parker, who played a bit part in the film. He was 21 and she was 48. By this time, his trademark cuteness and appeal started taking shape. The youthful 21-year old Patrick played a nerd role next in the very funny high school comedy Can&apos;t Buy Me Love (1987) with Amanda Peterson. A movie favorite for many, Patrick had reached the peak of his early career popularity. He showed a more serious side in the World War II-era drama In a Shallow Grave (1988), which presented a Cyrano de Bergerac-like storyline with Patrick as the Christian de Neuvillette counterpart, but then he went straight back to familiar territory with the college-themed comedies Some Girls (1988) with Jennifer Connelly, Loverboy (1989), and Happy Together (1989).Stretching more in the 1990s, Patrick co-starred on stage in a 1991 production of &quot;The Subject Was Roses&quot; (playing the Martin Sheen film role) as the World War II soldier readjusting to civilian life with his parents (Dana Ivey and &quot;Frasier&quot; co-star John Mahoney). Films included the cross-country comedy-drama Coupe de Ville (1990), the action thriller Run (1991), Mobsters (1991), in which he made a stab at playing major Mafioso Meyer Lansky, Face the Music (1993) opposite &quot;Brat Pack&quot; femme Molly Ringwald, the title role in Bank Robber (1993), and the Mark Twain family-geared Ava&apos;s Magical Adventure (1998), co-directed by Patrick and wife Rocky. However, the couple divorced that same year. On television, Patrick played a young John Fitzgerald Kennedy in the miniseries J.F.K.: Reckless Youth (1993), Pierre Arronax in the television remake of 20,000 Leagues Under the Sea (1997), and Raskolnikov in a small screen version of Crime and Punishment (1998). The rest of the decade on film was less newsworthy with co-starring or featured movie roles in Hugo Pool (1997), Denial (1998), There&apos;s No Fish Food in Heaven (1998) and Me and Will (1999).It was television that gave Patrick a shot in the arm as he progressed into the new millennium. A recurring role as Will&apos;s closeted sportscaster amour in the sitcom Will &amp; Grace (1998) presented Patrick in a more mature, wry and sexier fashion. Another recurring role in Once and Again (1999) earned him a dramatic Emmy nomination in 2001 as Outstanding Guest Actor, and a third on The Practice (1997) was also extremely well-received. While the romantic comedy film Sweet Home Alabama (2002) opposite Reese Witherspoon really nailed the direction Dempsey was headed, the medical series Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005), as neurosurgeon Dr. Derek Shepherd (aka &quot;Dr. McDreamy&quot;), gave distaff audiences the whole heartthrob package. The perfect vehicle to showcase his undeniable charisma and sharp talent for offbeat comedy, he is a two-time Golden Globe nominee and his popularity has absolutely skyrocketed. This reawakening has also swung the door open again on high-profile film offers, registering with the ladies once again in a number of light leading man parts, notably Enchanted (2007) and Made of Honor (2008).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>233</ID>
<Name>Patrick Fischler</Name>
<Description>Patrick Fischler was born on December 29, 1969 in Los Angeles, California, USA. He is an actor and producer, known for Mulholland Dr. (2001), Speed (1994) and Old School (2003). He is married to Lauren Bowles. They have one child.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>234</ID>
<Name>Paul Kasey</Name>
<Description>Studied theatre arts at Laine Theatre Art in Surrey, England. Paul is an accomplished actor, dancer and gymnast.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>235</ID>
<Name>Paula Malcomson</Name>
<Description>Born in 1970 in Belfast, Northern Ireland, Paula Malcomson is an extremely prolific film and television actress with numerous credits to her name. Malcomson began her career in the early 1990s with small parts primarily in film before scoring higher-profiles roles in the Oscar-nominated film The Green Mile (1999) and Artificial Intelligence: AI (2001). In 2006, she joined the cast of HBO&apos;s Deadwood (2004) in the role of Trixie, and would also go on to appear in creator David Milch&apos;s next series, John from Cincinnati (2007). From then on, Malcomson made appearances in a number of high-profile series, including ER (1994), Lost (2004), Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit (1999), CSI: Crime Scene Investigation (2000), and had regular roles on both Sons of Anarchy (2008) and Caprica (2009) in 2010. As her list of television appearances steadily grew, she also was cast in the role of Katniss&apos; unnamed Mother in the blockbuster adaptation of The Hunger Games (2012). After the release of that film, she also filmed the pilot for Liev Schreiber&apos;s Showtime series Ray Donovan (2013).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>236</ID>
<Name>Penn Badgley</Name>
<Description>Penn Badgley was born in Baltimore, Maryland, to Lynne Murphy Badgley and Duff Badgley, who worked as a newspaper reporter and carpenter. Badgley split his childhood years between Richmond, Virginia. and Seattle, Washington. In Seattle, he was involved in the Seattle Children&apos;s Theater and did voice-overs for a children&apos;s radio station. It was through these experiences that Badgley discovered his love of acting. This passion brought him one summer to Hollywood, where he landed an agent and his first big break guest-starring on Will &amp; Grace (1998). After relocating with his mother to Los Angeles, Badgley secured several recurring roles on The Young and the Restless (1973), The Brothers Garcia (2000), and Daddio (2000).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>237</ID>
<Name>Peter Capaldi</Name>
<Description>Peter Capaldi was born in Glasgow, Scotland, to Nancy (Soutar) and Gerald John Capaldi. His parents owned an ice cream business. He is of Italian (from his paternal grandfather), Scottish, and Irish descent. Capaldi attended drama classes and was accepted into the Glasgow School of Art. After graduating he secured his breakthrough role in Local Hero (1983).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>238</ID>
<Name>Peter Dinklage</Name>
<Description>Peter Dinklage received acclaim for his first film, Living in Oblivion (1995), where he played an actor frustrated with the limited and caricatured roles offered to dwarf actors. In 2003, he starred in The Station Agent (2003), written and directed by Tom McCarthy. The movie received critical praise and Peter was nominated for best actor at the &quot;Screen Actors Guild&quot; and &quot;Independent Spirit Awards&quot;. He played &quot;Miles Finch&quot;, an acclaimed children&apos;s book author, in Elf (2003). The English Death at a Funeral (2007) and American Death at a Funeral (2010), Penelope (2006) and The Chronicles of Narnia: Prince Caspian (2008) are a few more of his feature films.He had recurring appearances in such television shows as HBO&apos;s Entourage (2004) and ABC&apos;s Life As We Know It (2004). He played a larger role in the critically-acclaimed, yet short-lived CBS show, Threshold (2005). In 2011, he landed a primary role, as &quot;Tyrion Lannister&quot;, on the HBO series, Game of Thrones (2011). Tyrion&apos;s wit made him a favorite character on the series. At The 63rd Primetime Emmy Awards (2011) and The 67th Primetime Emmy Awards (2015), Peter Dinklage won 2 Emmy Awards for Outstanding Supporting Actor in a Drama Series category for his role as &quot;Tyrion Lannister&quot;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>239</ID>
<Name>Rachel G. Fox</Name>
<Description>Rachel was casted as Rosie Donohue on CBS&apos;s Vince Uncensored, starring Michael Chiklis and Elizabeth Perkins. Rachel had the pleasure of working with Chiklis and Perkins as her parents, and Paul Dooley and Georgia Engel as her grandparents, in addition to being directed by Kelsey Grammer.Rachel is currently recurring on ABC Family&apos;s number-one-comedy hit series &quot;Melissa &amp; Joey.&quot; She plays Holly Reback, girlfriend of Ryder (Nick Robinson), in this hilarious multi-camera sitcom.Outside of acting, Rachel is lead singer and rhythm guitar player for two rock bands, playing songs by Led Zeppelin, Rolling Stones, Muse, My Chemical Romance, and others as well as originals she has written. Rachel plays tennis, loves the beach, and is active and adventurous.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>240</ID>
<Name>Raphael Alejandro</Name>
<Description>Raphael Alejandro was born on August 22, 2007 in Montreal, Quebec, Canada. He started his acting career at the age of 4. He is known for Once Upon a Time, Kindergarten Cop 2, Olympus, Badge of Honor, among others. He is the youngest child of three. Dalila Bela is his sister and Bruce Salomon is his brother, both also actors.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>241</ID>
<Name>Raphael Sbarge</Name>
<Description>Theater is Raphael&apos;s passion and his stage credits include work on Broadway in Ah, Wilderness with Jason Robards and Colleen Dewhurst; Curse of an Aching Heart with Faye Dunaway; Shadow Box with Mercedes Ruehl; Twilight of the Golds and Voices in the Dark. Extensive regional and off-Broadway credits include Picnic with Gwyneth Paltrow; Booth with Frank Langella; Hamlet, directed by Joseph Papp; and most recently, The Cherry Orchard with Annette Bening and Alfred Molina, among many others. On the big screen, he appeared in over 30 films, including appearing with Tom Cruise in Risky Business(1983), Independence Day (1996), Message in a Bottle (1999), Vision Quest (1985), Pearl Harbor (2001).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>242</ID>
<Name>Rebecca Mader</Name>
<Description>Rebecca Mader was born on April 24, 1977 in Cambridge, Cambridgeshire, England as Rebecca Leigh Mader. She is an actress and writer, known for The Devil Wears Prada (2006), One Life to Live (1968) and Iron Man Three (2013). She was previously married to Joseph Arongino.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>243</ID>
<Name>Rhoda Griffis</Name>
<Description>Her popular character she played was Jacqueline Kennedy in Love Field (1992).She worked alongside with her good friend Emmy Rossum in Songcatcher (2000), as the wife of the coal company head (Steve Boles), Clementine McFarland.Her favorite role is the General&apos;s vixen wife, Lenore Baker, on the Lifetime series Army Wives (2007).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>244</ID>
<Name>Rhys Ifans</Name>
<Description>Ifans made his small screen debut as the host of Welsh children&apos;s TV show, Stwnsh. Various roles in theater and Welsh language television also followed. His breakthrough on the big screen came in the British hit Twin Town (1997), where he acting alongside his younger brother Llyr Ifans. More film success followed, notably as Hugh Grant&apos;s scruffy housemate in Notting Hill (1999). Other projects include Dancing at Lughnasa (1998) , Little Nicky (2000), Enduring Love (2004), Elizabeth: The Golden Age (2007), Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows: Part 1 (2010) and The Amazing Spider-Man (2012).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>245</ID>
<Name>Ricardo Chavira</Name>
<Description>Ricardo Chavira was born on September 1, 1971 in San Antonio, Texas, USA as Ricardo Antonio Chavira. He is an actor, known for Desperate Housewives (2004), Piranha 3D (2010) and Superman/Batman: Public Enemies (2009). He has been married to Marcea Dietzel since September 22, 2007. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>246</ID>
<Name>Richard Burgi</Name>
<Description>Burgi began his acting career in the mid-1980s, and from 1986 through 1989 he had recurring roles on two daytime staples, Another World (1964) and As the World Turns (1956); he also appeared in one episode of One Life to Live (1968).Throughout the 1990s, Burgi continued working steadily in television series, along them Days of Our Lives (1965) and the crime drama The Sentinel (1996), where he was one of the leads, Det. James Ellison. He also had roles (some one-time, some recurring) on 24 (2001), Judging Amy (1999), Point Pleasant (2005), Las Vegas (2003), Chuck (2007), One Tree Hill (2003) and Desperate Housewives (2004).Burgi&apos;s film work includes the sci-fi &quot;alien bugs vs. humans&quot; sequel Starship Troopers 2: Hero of the Federation (2004), Cellular (2004), the Jim Carrey comedy Fun with Dick and Jane (2005), the Cameron Diaz comedy In Her Shoes (2005), Hostel: Part II (2007), and Friday the 13th (2009). In 2013, he landed a recurring role as D.A. Dan Russell on the series Body of Proof (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>247</ID>
<Name>Robbie Kay</Name>
<Description>Robbie Kay was born on September 13, 1995 in Lymington, Hampshire, England. He is an actor, known for Pirates of the Caribbean: On Stranger Tides (2011), Fugitive Pieces (2007) and Ways to Live Forever (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>248</ID>
<Name>Robert Carlyle</Name>
<Description>Robert Carlyle was born in Maryhill, Glasgow, Scotland, to Elizabeth, a bus company employee, and Joseph Carlyle, a painter and decorator. He was raised by his father after his mother left him when he was four. At the age of 21, after reading Arthur Miller&apos;s &quot;The Crucible,&quot; he enrolled in acting classes at the Glasgow Arts Centre. In 1991, together with four other actors, he founded the Raindog theatre company (named after Tom Waits&apos; album &quot;Rain Dog,&quot; one of Carlyle&apos;s favorites), a company dedicated to innovative work.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>249</ID>
<Name>Robert Downey Jr.</Name>
<Description>Downey Jr. made his debut as an actor at the age of five in the film Pound (1970), written and directed by his father, Robert Downey Sr.. He built his film repertoire throughout the 1980s and 1990s with roles in Tuff Turf (1985), Weird Science (1985), True Believer (1989), and Wonder Boys (2000) among many others. In 1992, Downey received an Academy Award nomination and won the BAFTA (British Academy Award) for Best Actor for his performance in the title role of Chaplin (1992).In Robert Altman&apos;s Short Cuts (1993), he appeared as an aspiring film make-up artist whose best friend commits murder. In Oliver Stone&apos;s Natural Born Killers (1994), with Woody Harrelson and Juliette Lewis, Downey starred as a tabloid TV journalist who exploits a murderous couple&apos;s killing spree to boost his ratings. For the comedy Heart and Souls (1993), Downey starred as a young man with a special relationship with four ghosts. In 1995, Downey starred in Restoration (1995), with Hugh Grant, Meg Ryan and Ian McKellen, directed by Michael Hoffman. Also that year, he starred in Richard III (1995), in which he appears opposite his Restoration (1995) co-star McKellen.In 1997, Downey was seen in Robert Altman&apos;s The Gingerbread Man (1998), alongside Kenneth Branagh, Daryl Hannah and Embeth Davidtz; in One Night Stand (1997), directed by Mike Figgis and starring Wesley Snipes and Nastassja Kinski; and in Hugo Pool (1997), directed by his father, Robert Downey Sr. and starring Sean Penn and Patrick Dempsey. In September of 1999, Downey appeared in Black and White (1999), written and directed by James Toback, along with Ben Stiller, Elijah Wood, Gaby Hoffmann, Brooke Shields and Claudia Schiffer. In January of 1999, he starred with Annette Bening and Aidan Quinn in In Dreams (1999), directed by Neil Jordan.In May 2008, Downey achieved critical acclaim and worldwide box office success for his starring role in Iron Man (2008), Jon Favreau&apos;s big-screen rendering of the Marvel comic book superhero. The film co-starred Gwyneth Paltrow, Jeff Bridges and Terrence Howard. In August of 2008, Downey starred with Ben Stiller and Jack Black in the comedy Tropic Thunder (2008), and went on to receive an Academy Award®-nomination for Best Supporting Actor for his, Kirk Lazarus.In December 2009, Downey starred in the action-adventure Sherlock Holmes (2009). The film, directed by Guy Ritchie, co-starred Jude Law and Rachel McAdams and earned Downey a Golden Globe for Best Performance by an Actor in a Motion Picture - Comedy or Musical in January of 2010. In early Summer 2010, Downey re-teamed with director Jon Favreau and reprised his role as &quot;Tony Stark/Iron Man&quot; in the hugely successful sequel to the original film, Iron Man 2 (2010), starring Gwyneth Paltrow, Scarlett Johansson, Samuel L. Jackson and Mickey Rourke.Downey next starred in Due Date (2010), a comedy directed by Todd Phillips, in which he plays the role of an expectant father on a road trip racing to get back in time for the birth of his first child. Due Date (2010), starring The Hangover (2009)&apos;s Zach Galifianakis, was released in November 2010.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>250</ID>
<Name>Robert John Burke</Name>
<Description>Robert John Burke was born on September 12, 1960 in Washington Heights, New York, USA as John Burke. He is an actor, known for Limitless (2011), RoboCop 3 (1993) and 2 Guns (2013).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>251</ID>
<Name>Roma Maffia</Name>
<Description>Additional feature credits include &quot;I Am Sam&quot; with Sean Penn and Michelle Pfeiffer; &quot;Kiss The Girls&quot; with Morgan Freeman; &quot;Holes,&quot; &quot;Things You Can Tell Just By Looking At Her&quot; with Glenn Close and Holly Hunter.For television, Roma played the dedicated and intelligent &apos;Grace Alvarez,&apos; forensic pathologist for the Violent Crimes Task Force, for four seasons on NBC&apos;s primetime series &quot;Profiler.&quot; Her telefilm credits include &quot;Consensual Relations&quot; for NBC; HBO&apos;s &quot;Mistrial&quot; with Bill Pullman; and Showtime&apos;s &quot;The Defenders.&quot; She had recurring roles on NBC&apos;s &quot;Law &amp; Order&quot; and &quot;ER,&quot; and she has guest-starred on numerous television shows, including CBS&apos;s &quot;Ghost Whisperer,&quot; Lifetime&apos;s &quot;Strong Medicine,&quot; NBC&apos;s &quot;The West Wing&quot; and HBO&apos;s &quot;The Sopranos.&quot;</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>252</ID>
<Name>Rory McCann</Name>
<Description>Six foot six inches tall, with brown eyes and dark hair, Rory McCann from Glasgow began his working life at the top - as a painter on the Forth Bridge in Scotland. He came to notice in a television commercial for Scotts&apos; Porridge Oats, in which he appeared as a scantily-clad hunk in a vest and kilt and little else wandering snowbound streets but warmed by the inner glow of the porridge. He claims that as a consequence he was often approached by people demanding that he &quot;lift his kilt.&quot; In 2002 he was seen in the TV comedy-drama &apos;The Book Group&apos; playing a wheelchair-bound lifeguard, a part for which he won a Scottish BAFTA award for the best television performance of 2002. Since then he has taken television roles as Peter the Great and a priest in &apos;Shameless&apos;. He made his Hollywood debut in Oliver Stone&apos;s &apos;Alexander&apos;. He divides his time between homes in London and Glencoe, Scotland, where he aims to have his own castle. He is an accomplished singer, pianist and harmonica-player as well as an all-round sportsman. From 2012 to 2014 he was part of the international television block-buster &apos;Game of Thrones&apos;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>253</ID>
<Name>Rose McIver</Name>
<Description>Rose McIver was born on October 10, 1988 in Auckland, New Zealand as Frances Rose McIver. She is an actress, known for The Lovely Bones (2009), iZombie (2015) and Power Rangers R.P.M. (2009).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>254</ID>
<Name>Ruari Mears</Name>
<Description>Ruari Mears is an actor, known for Doctor Who (2005), Doctor Who at the Proms (2009) and The Sarah Jane Adventures (2007).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>255</ID>
<Name>Ryan Merriman</Name>
<Description>Among his television credits is &quot;Comanche moon&quot; a 6-hour mini-series, with an all-star cast including Val Kilmer, Karl Urban, Steve Zahn, Rachel Griffiths, Linda Cardellini and Graham Greene, is written by Larry McMurtry and Diana Ossana.Merriman has also starred in several television films including Lifetime&apos;s &quot;Dangerous Child,&quot; &quot;Backwoods&quot; a psychological thriller co-starring with Haylie Duff, &quot;Rocket&apos;s Red Glare,&quot; &quot;Luck of the Irish,&quot; &quot;Smart House,&quot; &quot;Ring of Endless Light,&quot; Hallmark&apos;s &quot;Night Ride Home,&quot; &quot;Lansky,&quot; &quot;Everything That Rises&quot; and &quot;Taken&quot; on the Sci-Fi Channel produced by Steven Spielberg. In addition Ryan has starred in three feature films. &quot;Deep End of the Ocean&quot; with Michelle Pfeiffer, &quot;Halloween: Resurrection&quot; and &quot;Just Looking,&quot; that was directed by Jason Alexander. Merriman also starred in the ABC series &quot;Veritas&quot; and the recurring role of &quot;Young Jarod&quot; on the NBC hit series &quot;The Pretender,&quot; which ran for four successful seasons on NBC. He was also a series regular on the NBC television sitcom, &quot;The Mommies.&quot;</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>256</ID>
<Name>Sacha Baron Cohen</Name>
<Description>Feature film work followed with Baron Cohen providing the voice of Julien in Madagascar (2005) and appearing as Jean Girard alongside Will Ferrell in Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby (2006). He followed this with the smash-hit Borat: Cultural Learnings of America for Make Benefit Glorious Nation of Kazakhstan (2006), for which he won a Golden Globe and was nominated for a writing Oscar. His other film work includes supporting roles in Sweeney Todd: The Demon Barber of Fleet Street (2007) and Hugo (2011), and starring in the title roles of Brüno (2009), The Dictator (2012), and Grimsby (2016).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>257</ID>
<Name>Sam Robards</Name>
<Description>Sam Robards was born on December 16, 1961 in New York City, New York, USA as Sam Prideaux Robards. He is an actor and producer, known for American Beauty (1999), Artificial Intelligence: AI (2001) and Awake (2007). He has been married to Sidsel Jensen since November 8, 1997. They have two children. He was previously married to Suzy Amis.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>258</ID>
<Name>Samuel Anderson</Name>
<Description>Samuel Anderson was born in 1984 in England. He is an actor and producer, known for The History Boys (2006), Emmerdale Farm (1972) and Doctor Who (2005).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>259</ID>
<Name>Sandra Ellis Lafferty</Name>
<Description>Sandra Ellis Lafferty is known for her roles in Walk the Line(2005), Hunger Games(2012),Prisoners(2013) Self/Less(2015), and A Walk in the Woods(2015) . Sandra began her career as a stage actor and was named best actress for a season by the Denver drama critics, when she was a member of The Denver Center Theatre Company. She also was named best actress by Westword Magazine. Sandra has a recurring role on the The C.W series &quot;Containment&quot;.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>260</ID>
<Name>Sandra Oh</Name>
<Description>Sandra Oh was born to Korean parents in the Ottawa suburb of Nepean, Ontario, Canada. Her father, Oh Junsu, a businessman, and her mother, Oh Young-nam, a biochemist, were married in Seoul, South Korea. They both attended graduate school at the University of Toronto. Sandra began her career as a ballet dancer and eventually studied drama at the National Theatre School in Montreal. She then starred in a London (Ontario) stage production of David Mamet&apos;s &quot;Oleanna&quot; and appeared as the title character in the Canadian television production The Diary of Evelyn Lau (1994), beating out over 1,000 applicants. Her list of awards includes the FIPA d&apos;Or for Best Actress at the 1994 Festival International de Programmes Audiovisuels at Cannes, France, two Genie Awards (the Canadian Oscar), a Cable Ace Award, a Theatre World Award and a Screen Actors Guild Award. In 2003, she married writer-director Alexander Payne and their first film together was the Oscar-winning Sideways (2004).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>261</ID>
<Name>Sara Ramirez</Name>
<Description>Sara Ramirez was born on August 31, 1975 in Mazatlan, Sinaloa, Mexico. She is an actress, known for Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005), Spider-Man (2002) and You&apos;ve Got Mail (1998). She has been married to Ryan DeBolt since July 4, 2012.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>262</ID>
<Name>Sarah Bolger</Name>
<Description>Sarah Lee Bolger (born 28 February 1991) is an Irish actress. She is best known for her roles in the films In America, Stormbreaker, and The Spiderwick Chronicles, as well as her award winning role as Lady Mary Tudor in the TV series The Tudors, and for guest starring as Princess Aurora in Once Upon a Time.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>263</ID>
<Name>Sarah Drew</Name>
<Description>Her first job was providing the voice role of &quot;Stacy Rowe&quot; on the animated series, Daria (1997), when Drew was still in high school. Beginning in 2004, she was a featured cast member on the western series, Everwood (2002). After having minor roles in the series, Private Practice (2007) and as &quot;Kitty Romano&quot; on Mad Men (2007), Drew was cast in a recurring role as &quot;Dr. April Kepner&quot; on the acclaimed medical drama, Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005).She has also had supporting roles in the films, Radio (2003) and American Pastime (2007), as well as a starring role in the comedy, Moms&apos; Night Out (2014).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>264</ID>
<Name>Sasha Pieterse</Name>
<Description>Sasha Pieterse was born in Johannesburg, South Africa, to acrobatic dancer parents. At 6 years old, Sasha got her start in television, co-starring as &quot;Buffy&quot; on The WB comedy series Family Affair (2002), opposite Gary Cole. She now returns to series television playing Cole&apos;s daughter on Wanted (2005). Born in Johannesburg, South Africa and raised in Las Vegas before moving to Los Angeles, this 9-year-old grew up around show business. Her parents were professional dance partners who performed all over the world, and Pieterse loved being on stage with them. She soon met with an agent who quickly signed her, and she&apos;s been busy acting and modeling ever since.Pieterse has appeared in numerous television commercials including long-running national spots for &quot;Nesquick&quot; and &quot;Firestone Tires&quot;. She was featured on a billboard for &quot;Supercuts&quot; that appeared throughout the country and more recently, sang and modeled in the Macy&apos;s Passport Fashion Show, performing throughout California. On television, she has also guest starred as &quot;Grace&quot; on the Sci-Fi series Stargate SG-1 (1997). Pieterse will next be seen as the &quot;Ice Princess&quot; in Robert Rodriguez&apos;s (Spy Kids (2001)) feature film The Adventures of Sharkboy and Lavagirl 3-D (2005), with George Lopez.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>265</ID>
<Name>Scarlett Johansson</Name>
<Description>In 2003, she was nominated for two Golden Globe Awards, one for drama (Girl with a Pearl Earring (2003)) and one for comedy (Lost in Translation (2003)), her breakout role, starring opposite Bill Murray, and receiving rave reviews and a Best Actress Award at the Venice Film Festival. Her 2004 film roles include the critically acclaimed Weitz brothers&apos; film &quot;In Good Company,&quot; as well as starring opposite John Travolta in &quot;A Love Song For Bobby Long,&quot; which garnered her a Golden Globe nomination (her third in two years).She dropped out of Mission: Impossible III (2006) due to scheduling conflicts. Her next film role was in The Island (2005) alongside Ewan McGregor which earned weak reviews from U.S. critics. After this, she appeared in Woody Allen&apos;s Match Point (2005) and was nominated again for a Golden Globe Award. In May 2008, she released her album &quot;Anywhere I Lay My Head,&quot; a collection of Tom Waits covers featuring one original song. Also that year, she starred in Frank Miller&apos;s The Spirit (2008), the Woody Allen film Vicky Cristina Barcelona (2008), and played Mary Boleyn opposite Natalie Portman in The Other Boleyn Girl (2008).Since then, she has appeared as part of an ensemble cast in the romantic comedy He&apos;s Just Not That Into You (2009), the action superhero film Iron Man 2 (2010), the comedy-drama We Bought a Zoo (2011) and started as the original scream queen, Janet Leigh, in Hitchcock (2012). She then played her Iron Man 2 character, Black Widow, in the blockbuster action films The Avengers (2012), Captain America: The Winter Soldier (2014), and Avengers: Age of Ultron (2015), and also headlined the science-fiction thriller Lucy (2014), a box office success. With more than a decade of work already under her belt, Scarlett has proven to be one of Hollywood&apos;s most talented young actresses.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>266</ID>
<Name>Scott Michael Foster</Name>
<Description>Born in Illinois and raised in the Dallas-Fort Worth area of Texas, Foster knew from an early age that he wanted to be an actor. He grew up just outside of Chicago until he was 12 years old, where his family lived on a farm and he was home schooled. When Foster&apos;s older sisters started to dabble in theatre he immediately became interested in the entertainment industry. Soon after moving to Dallas with his family he chose theatre as an elective in middle school, pursued the arts in high school, and went on to study at the Quad C Theatre Program at Collin County Community College. In 2004 Foster decided to make the big move to Los Angeles. Once in LA, Foster joined an acting class, met his manager, and started booking commercials. In 2005 he landed several independent films, and in 2007 he booked what would become his regular acting gig for the next five years: a series regular role starring as &quot;Cappie&quot; on the hit series &quot;Greek&quot; for ABC Family. While putting in time on &quot;Greek&quot; Foster wrote, produced, and starred in his own script that he sold to Comedy Central entitled &quot;Neighbros.&quot; The show sold in the fall of 2010 for fall&apos;s 2011 pilot season. Although the experience of putting together a show was something Foster loved, he decided to put all side projects on hold and focus on booking new acting roles. By the time &quot;Greek&quot; had ended its run in 2011 Foster had made his mark at ABC through his work on the show, and his relationship with the network would continue to grow over the next several years. Foster went on to score a handful of guest star roles including appearances on: TNT&apos;s &quot;The Closer,&quot; NBC&apos;s &quot;Friends with Benefits,&quot; &quot;Law and Order: LA,&quot; and &quot;Parenthood,&quot; and ABC Family&apos;s &quot;Melissa &amp; Joey.&quot; He also held a recurring role on &quot;Quarterlife&quot; for NBC and starred in the 2009 fan favorite independent feature TEENAGE DIRTBAG. In 2012 Foster had the opportunity to play characters that were far from the happy go lucky teen he portrayed on &quot;Greek.&quot; First, he was seen in 10 episodes of the hit Showtime series &quot;Californication&quot; starring opposite David Duchovny as &quot;Tyler,&quot; and went on to play &quot;Jonas Beckett&quot; in five episodes of ABC&apos;s Emmy Nominated series &quot;The River.&quot; Soon after filming &quot;The River,&quot; ABC enlisted Foster once again, casting him in &quot;Zero Hour&quot; [2013] opposite Anthony Edwards, Jacinda Barrett, Addison Timlin, and Carmen Ejogo. When not acting Foster is an active supporter of The Sue Weaver Cause, an organization that promotes consumer awareness of unsafe service employment - their quest is to require proper annual criminal background checks on all workers sent to people&apos;s homes. Foster is also a musician, making music for over nine years and released an EP in 2009 with his band Siren&apos;s Eye. He recently became a certified scuba diver, and currently lives in the Los Angeles area with his two dogs, Oliver and Charlie.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>267</ID>
<Name>Sean Faris</Name>
<Description>Faris moved to Ohio at age 12 and has been honing his craft in Los Angeles since moving four years upon his high school graduation. He received an MTV Movie Award for his lead role in Summit Entertainment&apos;s hit Never Back Down, and starred as Betty White&apos;s grandson and Jennifer Love Hewitt&apos;s love interest in the CBS Hallmark Hall of Fame telefilm The Lost Valentine. In addition to his central role in the rugby-inspired feature Forever Strong, he appeared as Dennis Quaid&apos;s eldest son in Paramount&apos;s hit remake of the classic Yours, Mine &amp; Ours and previously starred as the hunky object of affection in MGM&apos;s comedy romp Sleepover. Next on the horizon is the crime thriller Pawn in which he stars opposite Academy Award-winner Forest Whitaker, and the coveted title role in The Story of Bonnie &amp; Clyde. In direct contrast, Faris starred as the lead in FOX&apos;s acclaimed drama series Reunion which followed six close friends from their high school graduation to their 20th reunion. He previously led the cast of ABC&apos;s dramatic series Life As We Know It. Based upon British author Melvin Burgess&apos; controversial novel Doing It, the acclaimed show chronicled the sexual antics of a group of high school friends in Seattle. For his role as sensitive jock Dino Whitman, he was heralded as a breakout talent by the likes of Daily Variety, The Hollywood Reporter, and USA Today. A more recent foray into television included a multi-episode arc on The CW&apos;s top-rated Vampire Diaries. No stranger to television, Faris has also guest-starred on such shows as Smallville, One Tree Hill, and Boston Public. His big screen debut featured him alongside the likes of Ben Affleck and Josh Hartnett in Michael Bay&apos;s epic Pearl Harbor.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>268</ID>
<Name>Sean Maguire</Name>
<Description>Sean was born on 18 April 1976 in Ilford, Essex, England. He made his acting debut at the age of five in Voyage Around My Father with Sir Laurence Olivier. Many TV roles for UK television followed including, Tegs in Grange Hill, Aiden Brosnan in Eastenders, Marty in Dangerfield and Lee in Sunburn (all BBC). Sean played the role of Euan in The WB sitcom, Off Centre, and most recently he has been playing the role of Robin Hood in ABC&apos;s hit series Once Upon A Time (2013) replacing Tom Ellis in the role. He currently lives in LA.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>269</ID>
<Name>Sebastian Stan</Name>
<Description>Sebastian Stan was born on August 13, 1982, in Constanta, Romania. He moved with his mother to Vienna, Austria, when he was eight, and then to New York when he was twelve. Stan studied at Rutgers Mason Gross School of the Arts and spent a year at Shakespeare&apos;s Globe Theatre in London.When he went back to New York he started working in some projects like Law &amp; Order (1990), Tony &apos;n&apos; Tina&apos;s Wedding (2004) and Red Doors (2005). Upon finishing college, he played Martin Waters in The Architect (2006), Chase Collins in The Covenant (2006) and worked in Eric Bogosian&apos;s theater play The Talk (2007). Also in 2007, Stan started playing Carter Baizen in Gossip Girl (2007). His following projects were Spread (2009), Kings (2009), Hot Tub Time Machine (2010), and Black Swan (2010). He landed also the role of Bucky Barnes in Captain America: The First Avenger (2011). In 2012, Stan worked in several projects: Gone (2012), Political Animals (2012), The Apparition (2012), Once Upon a Time (2011) and the mini series Labyrinth (2012). In 2013, he was in Broadway&apos;s Picnic and in 2014 he became The Winter Soldier in Captain America: The Winter Soldier (2014). His recent projects include Ricki and the Flash (2015), The Martian (2015), The Bronze (2015) and Captain America: Civil War (2016).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>270</ID>
<Name>Shawn Pyfrom </Name>
<Description>Shawn is originally from FL. but started coming out to LA when he was 7 years old, along with his brother, Chris and sister, Amber. He has a natural talent for acting and a real love for the entertainment business. He has two very supportive parents that have helped him fulfill his dream. His future plans are to go to continue with his incredible art paintings, creating music and his acting career.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>271</ID>
<Name>Shay Mitchell</Name>
<Description>By her late teens, Shay had successfully modeled for a variety of companies in cities as varied as Bangkok, Hong Kong and Barcelona. Wanting to focus on her true passion, Mitchell returned to Toronto and began to study acting with great focus and determination.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>272</ID>
<Name>Sheila Kelley</Name>
<Description>Her roles on L.A. Law (1986), Sisters (1991), ER (1994) and The Sopranos (1999) and in films including Singles (1992), Matchstick Men (2003), Nurse Betty (2000) and One Fine Day (1996) have earned her respect, as an actress who is not afraid of embracing the power of her femininity.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>273</ID>
<Name>Sinqua Walls</Name>
<Description>His Break Through role was came when Walls was cast as the character Jamarcus Halls on the critically acclaimed series &apos;Friday Night Lights.&apos; He is perhaps best known for his role of Daniel in &apos;The Secret Life of the American Teenager.&apos; His work has included guest appearances on &apos;Californication,&apos; &apos;Grey&apos;s Anatomy,&apos; &apos;Chuck,&apos; &apos;CSI&apos;, &apos;Blue Mountain State&apos; and &apos;Savage County,&apos; as well as the dramatic short &apos;The Second Half&apos; which garnered him Several Independent film festival Awards. In 2011 Walls appeared in his first Studio Feature Film Lead role in the Relativity Media Suspense film &apos;Shark Night 3-D.&apos; Before Landing the Legendary Role of &quot;Sir Lancelot&quot; on ABC&apos;s Once Upon A Time.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>274</ID>
<Name>Sofia Black-D&apos;Elia</Name>
<Description>Sofia Black-D&apos;Elia grew up in northern New Jersey with her parents and older brother, Kyle. Her mother is of Russian Jewish descent and her father is of Italian ancestry. Prior to graduating Clifton High School, Sofia booked her first role in All My Children and discovered an affinity for acting. Soon after, she began her study of the craft at The William Esper Studio under the wonderful instruction of Mr. Bill Esper. Now a dedicated graduate of his two year Meisner program, Sofia happily lives in New York City.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>275</ID>
<Name>Sonequa Martin-Green</Name>
<Description>Sonequa Martin-Green was born on March 21, 1985 in Russellville, Alabama, USA. She is an actress and writer, known for The Walking Dead (2010), Toe to Toe (2009) and Shockwave Darkside (2014). She is married to Kenric Green. They have one child.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>276</ID>
<Name>Sophie Turner</Name>
<Description>Sophie Turner was born in Northampton in England and grew up in Warwick. She attended Kings High School there and was a member of a local theatre group from a young age.Her breakthrough role was as Sansa Stark in the HBO hit series Game of Thrones (2011).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>277</ID>
<Name>Stanley Tucci</Name>
<Description>Tucci took an interest in acting while in high school, and went on to attend the State University of New York&apos;s Conservatory of Theater Arts in Purchase. He began his professional career on the stage, making his Broadway debut in 1982, and then made his film debut in Prizzi&apos;s Honor (1985).In 2009, Tucci received his first Academy Award nomination for his turn as a child murderer in The Lovely Bones (2009). He also received a BAFTA nomination and a Golden Globe nomination for the same role. Other than The Lovely Bones, Tucci has recently had noteworthy supporting turns in a broad range of movies including Lucky Number Slevin (2006), The Devil Wears Prada (2006) and Captain America: The First Avenger (2011). Tucci reached his widest audience yet when he played Caesar Flickerman in box office sensation The Hunger Games (2012).While maintaining an active career in movies, Tucci received major accolades for some work in television. He won an Emmy and a Golden Globe for his role in TV movie Winchell (1998), an Emmy for a guest turn on Monk (2002), and a Golden Globe for his role in HBO movie Conspiracy (2001).Tucci has also had an extensive career behind the camera. His directorial efforts include Big Night (1996), The Impostors (1998), Joe Gould&apos;s Secret (2000) and Blind Date (2007), and he did credited work on all of those screenplays with the exception of Joe Gould&apos;s Secret (2000).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>278</ID>
<Name>Stephen Dillane</Name>
<Description>Stephen Dillane was born on March 27, 1957 in London, England. He is an actor, known for The Hours (2002), Spy Game (2001) and King Arthur (2004).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>279</ID>
<Name>Steven Culp</Name>
<Description>Steven Culp was born on December 3, 1955 in La Jolla, California, USA as Steven Bradford Culp. He is an actor, known for One Life to Live (1968), Captain America: The Winter Soldier (2014) and James and the Giant Peach (1996). He is married to Barbara Ayers. They have two children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>280</ID>
<Name>T.R. Knight</Name>
<Description>T.R. Knight was a member of the acting company of Minneapolis&apos; Guthrie Theater. Roles there included Richard Miller in Eugene O&apos;Neill&apos;s &quot;Ah, Wilderness!&quot; and Amadeus in Peter Shaffer&apos;s &quot;Amadeus&quot;.On the New York stage, he portrayed Tim Allgood in &quot;Noises Off&quot;, Damis in &quot;Tartuffe&quot;, Joe in &quot;This Lime Tree Bower&quot; and Brendan Hilliard in &quot;Anto Scattergood&quot;.He received a Drama Desk nomination for Outstanding Featured Actor in a Play for his performance in &quot;Scattergood&quot;.His first role was as a five year old when he played Tiny Tim in the Guthrie Theater&apos;s annual production of A Christmas Carol.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>281</ID>
<Name>Tammin Sursok</Name>
<Description>Tammin Sursok was born on August 19, 1983 in Johannesburg, South Africa as Tammin Pamela Sursok. She is an actress and writer, known for Home and Away (1988), The Young and the Restless (1973) and Aquamarine (2006). She has been married to Sean McEwen since August 24, 2011. They have one child.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>282</ID>
<Name>Taylor Momsen</Name>
<Description>Taylor Mikel Momsen was born on July 26th, 1993 in St Louis, Missouri to parents Michael and Colette Momsen. Her Mom took her to NYC because she was so bubbly, outgoing and so talented for her young age. She began her acting career at age 3 with a national commercial for &quot;Shake-N-Bake&quot;. She also appeared in commercials for &quot;Snuggle&quot; fabric softener. She first landed the role of &quot;Honey Bee Swan&quot; in The Prophet&apos;s Game (2000). Her first big role was as &quot;Cindy Lou Who&quot; in Jim Carrey&apos;s How the Grinch Stole Christmas (2000). After that, Taylor landed the role of &quot;Julie Moore&quot; in We Were Soldiers (2002), which also starred her younger sister, Sloane Momsen. After landing roles in movies such as Hansel &amp; Gretel (2002),Spy Kids 2: Island of Lost Dreams (2002),Saving Shiloh (2006), Spy School (2008), Taylor landed Gossip Girl (2007) a few years later and is known as the infamous &quot;Lil-J&quot;! Taylor starting touring with The Pretty Reckless when she appeared on Van&apos;s Warp Tour summer of 2010. Taylor is the lead singer and she writes all of her own lyrics. She has toured all over the UK, topping rock charts right away! Then touring U.S. cities in 2011.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>283</ID>
<Name>Teri Hatcher</Name>
<Description>Hatcher went to Hollywood to lend moral support to a friend during a open casting call. She, however, auditioned and won the role of the singing and dancing mermaid for the television series The Love Boat (1977). She went on to play &quot;Penny Parker,&quot; a ditsy but sweet-hearted struggling actress on MacGyver (1985). When that show ended, she auditioned for and won the role of smart and savvy &quot;Lois Lane&quot; on Lois &amp; Clark: The New Adventures of Superman (1993), saying that she didn&apos;t want to be stuck with the pretty airhead image she had acquired as &quot;Penny Parker.&quot;</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>284</ID>
<Name>Tessa Ferrer</Name>
<Description>Tessa Ferrer was born on March 30, 1986 in Los Angeles, California, USA as Tessa Rose Ferrer. She is an actress, known for Excision (2008), Grey&apos;s Anatomy (2005) and Abducted (2013).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>285</ID>
<Name>Tika Sumpter</Name>
<Description>Tika Sumpter was born in New York and graduated from Marymount Manhattan College. Sumpter began her career as model, before she landed the role of &quot;Layla Williamson&quot; in ABC&apos;s daytime soap opera, One Life to Live (1968) (2005-2010, 2011).After she left the soap, Sumpter won a recurring role in the CW series, Gossip Girl (2007), and appeared in the BET sitcom, The Game (2006). After supporting roles in the films, Stomp the Yard 2: Homecoming (2010), Salt (2010), What&apos;s Your Number? (2011) and Think Like a Man (2012), she was cast alongside Jordin Sparks and Whitney Houston in the 2012 musical film, Sparkle (2012). In 2013, she was cast as vixen &quot;Candace Young&quot; in the OWN drama series, The Haves and the Have Nots (2013).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>286</ID>
<Name>Timothy Webber</Name>
<Description>Timothy Webber is an actor, known for Cypher (2002), North of 60 (1992) and Seventh Son (2014).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>287</ID>
<Name>Tom Hiddleston</Name>
<Description>Thomas William Hiddleston was born in Westminster, London, to English-born Diana Patricia (Servaes) and Scottish-born James Norman Hiddleston. His mother is a former stage manager, and his father, a scientist, was the managing director of a pharmaceutical company.He started off at the preparatory school, The Dragon School in Oxford, and by the time he was 13, he boarded at Eton College, at the same time that his parents were going through a divorce. He continued on to the University of Cambridge, where he earned a double first in Classics. He graduated from the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art in 2005.Whilst at University of Cambridge, he was seen by the agency &apos;Hamilton Hodell&apos; in the play &apos;A Streetcar named Desire&apos; and was signed. Following this, he was cast in his first television role in The Life and Adventures of Nicholas Nickleby (2001). Hiddleston won his first film role as Oakley in Joanna Hogg&apos;s award-winning first feature, Unrelated (2007). His breakthrough role came when he portrayed Loki in the 2011 Marvel Studios feature film Thor (2011) and he reprised this role in The Avengers (2012).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>288</ID>
<Name>Tony Amendola</Name>
<Description>Tony was born and raised in New Haven, Connecticut.He attended Southern Connecticut State University and graduated in 1974.While an undergraduate student at Southern Connecticut State University, he performed as the leading man in several musicals at Sacred Heart Academy, an all-girls college preparatory high school in Hamden, Connecticut.After that, he went on to attend Temple University in Philadelphia, graduating in 1977 with a Master of Fine Arts Degree.Tony taught theater classes at Southern Connecticut State University, including a course in Stage Speaking, during the Spring semester of 1978.In 1978, he decided to make the move to Los Angeles to find work in film and television.Though this move was originally meant to be temporary, he lives there with his wife to this day.Tony is a theater-trained actor, and he has a long history of stage performances. Some of these include: &quot;American Buffalo&quot; as &quot;Teach&quot;; &quot;Othello&quot; as &quot;Iago&quot;; &quot;Filumena&quot; as &quot;Domenico&quot;; and &quot;Taming of the Shrew&quot; as &quot;Petruchio&quot;.He speaks Spanish and Italian.Some of his interests include: Italian cooking, museums, art galleries and yoga.His favorite play is &quot;Taming of the Shrew&quot; and his favorite Stargate SG-1 (1997) episode is &quot;Threshold&quot;.Tony&apos;s favorite charities are: Doctor&apos;s Without Borders, Habitat for Humanity, and the American Red Cross.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>289</ID>
<Name>Tony Perez</Name>
<Description>Tony Perez was born Jose Anthony Perez of Puerto Rican/Pilipino descent. He grew up San Diego, Virginia, and in Manhattan on the West Side of New York City; 68th street to be exact. Before being torn down his neighborhood was immortalized in the movie West Side Story. His father proudly served in the United States Navy during WWII. Tony paints and writes poetry, some of which has been published. He has been married to his wonderful wife, Marie Gagne since August 30, 1961. They have a beautiful daughter named Linda Marie Lawrence.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>290</ID>
<Name>Torrey DeVitto</Name>
<Description>Torrey Joël DeVitto stars in the NBC drama, Chicago Med (2015). From the same creators of Chicago Fire (2012) and Chicago P.D. (2014), the latest spin-off focuses on the day-to-day chaos of the team of doctors running the ER. Torrey plays &quot;Natalie Manning&quot;, doctor in the ER Pediatrics division. Natalie is your typical America&apos;s sweetheart, girl-next-door who is reserved and very focused on her career. The new series premiered Fall 2015 and has been renewed for a second season.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>291</ID>
<Name>Troian Bellisario</Name>
<Description>Troian Bellisario, daughter of producers Donald P. Bellisario and Deborah Pratt, made her film debut at the age of 3 in Last Rites (1988). She made several TV and movie appearances in her teens (most of the TV appearances were in shows produced by her father) before attending the University of Southern California.She rose to worldwide prominence as Spencer in the hit TV series, Pretty Little Liars (2010).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>292</ID>
<Name>Tuc Watkins</Name>
<Description>Tuc Watkins was born on September 2, 1966 in Kansas City, Missouri, USA as Charles Curtis Watkins III. He is an actor and producer, known for The Mummy (1999), General Hospital (1963) and One Life to Live (1968).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>293</ID>
<Name>Tyler Blackburn</Name>
<Description>Tyler Blackburn stars as Caleb Rivers, the bad boy with a soft side who swept Hanna off her feet on &quot;Pretty Little Liars.&quot; Caleb is drawn to stay in Rosewood after witnessing some strange events that are seemingly connected to him.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>294</ID>
<Name>Vanessa Ray</Name>
<Description>Vanessa Ray was born on June 24, 1981 in Alameda County, California, USA as Vanessa Rae Liptak. She is an actress, known for Frances Ha (2012), Blue Bloods (2010) and Devil&apos;s Due (2014). She has been married to Landon Beard since June 14, 2015. She was previously married to Derek Baynham.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>295</ID>
<Name>Vanessa Williams</Name>
<Description>Vanessa made her film debut in 1986 in Under the Gun (1988) and appeared in the films The Pick-up Artist (1987), Another You (1991) and Harley Davidson and the Marlboro Man (1991). She starred opposite Arnold Schwarzenegger in Eraser (1996), opposite Laurence Fishburne and Andy Garcia in Hoodlum (1997) and the box office hit, Soul Food (1997). She also starred in Dance with Me (1998), Light It Up (1999), Shaft (2000), opposite Samuel L. Jackson and Johnson Family Vacation (2004). She starred recently in the independent features, My Brother (2006) and And Then Came Love (2007) (aka &quot;Somebody Like You&quot;). On television, Vanessa starred in such movies and mini-series as Stompin&apos; at the Savoy (1992), The Kid Who Loved Christmas (1990), The Jacksons: An American Dream (1992), ABC&apos;s revival of Bye Bye Birdie (1995), Nothing Lasts Forever (1995), The Odyssey (1997), Don Quixote (2000) and Keep the Faith, Baby (2002), and she executive-produced and starred in Lifetime&apos;s The Courage to Love (2000) for Lifetime and the VH1 Original Movie, A Diva&apos;s Christmas Carol (2000).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>296</ID>
<Name>Victoria Smurfit</Name>
<Description>Victoria Smurfit was born on March 31, 1974 in Dublin, Ireland. She is an actress, known for The Beach (2000), Bulletproof Monk (2003) and About a Boy (2002). She has been married to Douglas Baxter since August 3, 2000. They have three children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>297</ID>
<Name>Wallace Shawn</Name>
<Description>Born to privilege on November 12, 1943 in New York City, Wallace was the son of renowned editor William Shawn of &quot;The New Yorker&quot; fame and educated at both Harvard University, where he studied history, and Magdalen College, Oxford. Wallace initially taught English in India on a Fulbright scholarship, and then English, Latin and drama back in New York. However, a keen interest in writing and acting soon compelled him to leave his cushy position and pursue a stage career as both playwright and actor. During his distinguished career, Wallace turned out several plays. &quot;Our Late Night&quot;, the first of his works to be performed, was awarded an off-Broadway Obie in 1975. &quot;A Thought in Three Parts&quot; (1976); &quot;The Mandrake&quot; (1977), which he translated from the original Italian and in which he made his acting debut; &quot;Marie and Bruce&quot; (1979); &quot;Aunt Dan and Lemon&quot; (1985) and &quot;The Fever&quot;, for which he received his second Obie Award for &quot;Best New Play&quot; during the 1990-91 season, then followed. A popular support player in both comedy and occasional drama, his assorted kooks, creeps, eggheads and schmucks possessed both endearing and unappetizing qualities. He earned some of his best early notices partnered with theatre director/actor Andre Gregory in the unique Louis Malle-directed film My Dinner with Andre (1981). Shawn co-wrote the improvisatory, humanistic piece and his brother, Allen Shawn, was the composer. Shawn and Gregory would collaborate again for Malle in another superb, original-concept film Vanya on 42nd Street (1994). Among the quality offbeat filming involving has been Bruce Paltrow&apos;s A Little Sex (1982); James Ivory&apos;s The Bostonians (1984); Stephen Frears&apos; Prick Up Your Ears (1987); Rob Reiner&apos;s The Princess Bride (1987); Alan Rudolph&apos;s The Moderns (1988) and Mrs. Parker and the Vicious Circle (1994); Paul Bartel&apos;s Scenes from the Class Struggle in Beverly Hills (1989); and several others for Woody Allen: Radio Days (1987), Shadows and Fog (1991), The Curse of the Jade Scorpion (2001) and Melinda and Melinda (2004). Of late, he has lent his vocal talents to a considerable number of animated pictures including A Goofy Movie (1995), Toy Story (1995) (and its sequel), The Jungle Book: Mowgli&apos;s Story (1998), The Incredibles (2004), Chicken Little (2005) and Happily N&apos;Ever After (2006).</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>298</ID>
<Name>Wes Bentley</Name>
<Description>Wes Bentley is an American actor who first became well-known via his role in the Oscar-winning film American Beauty (1999), in which he played the soulful, artistic next-door neighbor Ricky Fitts. He also portrayed gamemaker Seneca Crane in The Hunger Games (2012), and co-stars in Lovelace (2013) as photographer Thomas.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>299</ID>
<Name>William Baldwin</Name>
<Description>William Baldwin was born on February 21, 1963 in Massapequa, Long Island, New York, USA as William Joseph Baldwin. He is an actor and producer, known for Backdraft (1991), The Squid and the Whale (2005) and Flatliners (1990). He has been married to Chynna Phillips since September 9, 1995. They have three children.</Description>
</Celebrity>
<Celebrity>
<ID>300</ID>
<Name>Willow Shields</Name>
<Description>Willow Shields was born on June 1, 2000 in Albuquerque, New Mexico. She has a twin sister, actress Autumn Shields, and an older brother, actor River Shields. Willow got her first job in 2008, narrating the short film Las Vegas New Mexico 1875 (2008), the story of a dying gunfighter who returns home after 10 years to make peace with his wife and daughter. Her first television role was a guest appearance in the USA series In Plain Sight (2008), which was filmed in her hometown of Albuquerque, followed by an episode in the teen-oriented horror anthology series R.L. Stine&apos;s The Haunting Hour (2010) and a supporting role in the Hallmark Hall of Fame television movie Beyond the Blackboard (2011) opposite Emily VanCamp. On the strength of those appearances alone, Willow was cast as Primrose Everdeen, the younger sister of heroine Katniss Everdeen, in The Hunger Games (2012), and will appear in the same role in all the upcoming films adapted from the bestselling novels by Suzanne Collins.</Description>
</Celebrity>
</ArrayOfCelebrity>
